<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Webinar_Pivotal/Aridhia Disrupts Tech Approach_Q316.Invitation 6-23-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Webinar: Challenges in Clinical Research - Aridhia Disrupts Technology Approach to Research Analytics</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/challenges-in-clinical-research]]&gt;
Join Aridhia and Pivotal &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/challenges-in-clinical-research]]&gt; in this upcoming webinar to learn how Big Data and data science are being applied to clinical research. Learn…

 - Why research-oriented healthcare delivery organizations and academic medical centers need an ACRIS 
 - How improving collaboration and productivity accelerates the discovery of insights and increases competitiveness 
 - Why robust data security is critical to modernizing engagement between academia, industry and healthcare 
 - How to reduce research costs while improving commercialization opportunities 
 - Why enabling transparent analysis and reproducibility of research are key to scientific progress 
 - Best practices to get started on your digital transformation and Big Data journey 

Aridhia &lt;[[http://www.aridhia.com/]]&gt;, creators of AnalytiXagility &lt;[[http://www.aridhia.com/services/analytixagility/]]&gt;, the ground-breaking research and healthcare data analysis platform, is now enabling its customers to rapidly analyse massive amounts of data in meaningful ways to change how diseases are understood, managed and treated. Powered by Pivotal Greenplum &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-greenplum]]&gt;, AnalytiXagility enables collaborative research teams to quickly collate and analyze huge volumes of data associated with real-world research, drug trials and patient outcomes to develop new, data-driven approaches to healthcare. 

Event details: 
Wednesday, July 20
7:00AM PDT (San Francisco, CA) 
 
Register Here  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/challenges-in-clinical-research]]&gt;

We look forward to you joining us.

The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
