<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>this is a clone of the November 16 asset</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.012 November 30 2018 News</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal 5-Point Friday</subject>
    <textOnly>November 30, 2018

Hello - I’m Jim Quercetti, a 14 year EMC veteran. Most folks know me as “Q”. I joined Pivotal in April this year and I’m excited to be a part of the new Pivotal Synergy Sales Team covering the South. My focus is working with the joint SAB teams driving digital transformation opportunities with focus on Pivotal Ready Architecture adoption for our customers.

 


 



 


 

1. VPay Win in Commercial: WIN FAST with PKS

Working with our friends at Dell EMC and VMware, we were able to secure a competitive win with an electronic payment solution customer:


	- Dell EMC team uncovered a container opportunity. The competition had gotten there first. 

	- The account executive registered the opportunity on Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/pivotalpulse]]&gt;. 

	- We jumped on a quick call to discuss the opportunity. 

	- We had only a few days to showcase the power of PKS to VPay. VMware’s PKS Team leaned in to help us as out since our technical folks were booked - they killed it.

	- From our first call to verbal commitment from the CIO was just over (6) weeks. VMware was able to convert this into a Enterprise License Agreement (ELA) and add additional products.



Great SAB collaborative WIN that proves we can go down market and run fast to win! #BetterTogether

 


 



 


 


2. need to identify a Target Pivotal Customer? We built a Tool.


Clinton Reeves, one of our inside sales wizards, created a “propensity BI tool” to help all of us dial into our joint account targets quickly. The tool leverages data pools from from Discover.Org to help us score accounts, determine which ones have started down the digital transformation path and identify accounts which would benefit from joint sales discussions.
Use the Opportunity Registration form &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#salesopportunityreg]]&gt; to start the conversation with your Pivotal peer and leverage this tool to learn more about joint accounts with higher propensity for buying a Pivotal solution.

 


 



 


 


3. What&apos;s all the hubbub about Application Containers?

First, let&apos;s talk about explosive growth. The server virtualization market which we all fell in love with back in the early 2000’s is expected to grow at approximately USD 8 Billion by 2023, at 7% of CAGR &lt;[[https://www.marketresearchfuture.com/reports/server-virtualization-market-3981]]&gt; between 2017 and 2023 compared to the emerging 
Application Container market, which is expected to grow from USD 0.89 billion in 2017 to USD 4.42 billion by 2023, at a CAGR of 31.1% &lt;[[https://www.marketresearchfuture.com/reports/application-container-market-6582]]&gt; during the same forecasted period. 
Second, Containers are the fastest growing technology in the Data Center - Faster, lighter, adds to our virtualization story, enables hybrid cloud and it’s an infrastructure led sales play. Are you getting your fair share of the business? Start by asking a few simple questions:


	- Are you using Kubernetes or Docker?

	- Are you using multiple clouds? Which ones?

	- Are developers asking for container/Kubernetes solution?

	- Do you have COTS apps that are distributed as Docker Images?

	- Are you familiar with the steps involved in building a K8s environment?




If you think you have a Pivotal Container Service opportunity register it here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#salesopportunityreg]]&gt; for Pivotal field support.

 


 



 


 


4. Pivotal Enablement: Excited to learn about Pivotal, but not sure where to go?


YouTube is your friend. Here are some of my favorites:



	- Pivotal Company Overview Introduction &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ohREsVH5ND8]]&gt;
	- The Pivotal Effect &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YyJbSFRjkuI]]&gt;
	- How Pivotal Helps You Become a Modern Software Company &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O8LAXvwpRSo]]&gt; with Onsi Fakhouri, Pivotal 
	- Jumpstarting Digital Transformation and Reducing Time to Value Are Key to Success &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bg-uHJY6E]]&gt; with Michael Dell
	- SpringOne Platform Session “The What and How of Enterprise Kubernetes” &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQKra0CB5zE]]&gt; with Cornelia Davis &amp; Fred Melo, Pivotal
	- What is PKS? &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2g1KE5zdbRs]]&gt; with Roland Glenn, VMWare
	- Dell World - A Discussion on PRA &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yGuc-_UsUzA]]&gt;



 


 



 


 


5. Pivotal Days : Enterprise Grade Kubernetes on VxRail

New offering! Pivotal is hosting a half day customer event consisting of presentations and a demo to learn more about building an enterprise ready Container Orchestration solution that will enable you to provide on-premise &quot;Kubernetes as a Service&quot; model with Pivotal Container Service (PKS) and Pivotal Ready Architecture (PRA built on VxRail) in a stable, scalable and secure way. Dates 
and locations include:


	- Los Angeles &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Los-Angeles.html]]&gt;, Dec 3
	- Washington DC &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Washington-DC.html]]&gt;, Dec 4
	- Austin, TX &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Austin.html]]&gt;, Dec 17



- Q


 









 
 
 


 


Upcoming Events

Webex: Pivotal Learning Series &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSc6Km9Ifg5-74OBRjRYjEVSN0fs9Mps-mE-g2h9bExFC32fYQ/viewform?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0RjM09XTTRNVFEyTnpGbCIsInQiOiJMXC9zcXBPSG1Zd1loRzcwZXF0YW5kN0JSTXpmaGZPV0hqVmdDdHVkMUVSMmpHV3VKWWNqV2t6Rm10NW84Zk44RURmUHVOU3UrSjl2K1Y2Y3ZLQ2lsVVE9PSJ9]]&gt;
Pivotal Pulse Podcast: PRA &amp; PKS Win at Telecom Italia &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pra-pks-win-at-telecom-italia/s-TTCUE]]&gt;

Digital Knowledge

Website: Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx]]&gt;, designed exclusively for Dell Tech
Now Available! Pivotal Pulse Exclusive &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/?ReturnUrl=%2fEnglish%2fGlobal%2fsales%2fdell-tech.aspx]]&gt;, CONFIDENTIAL assets for Dell Tech
Win of the Week:  Chow Sang Sang, largest jewelry retailer in China buys PRA &amp; PKS &lt;[[https://www.cloudhq.net/s/431c269e2d]]&gt;
Chad Sakac Blog: IBM Acquires RedHat; My Two Cents &lt;[[https://virtualgeek.io/ibm-and-redhat-seeing-the-forest-for-the-trees/]]&gt; &amp; PKS, What’s Next &lt;[[https://virtualgeek.io/pks-whats-next-ending-with-a-fun-new-toy-for-you/]]&gt;
SpringOne Playlist Now Available! Transformation &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-transformation]]&gt;, Architecture &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-architecture]]&gt;, Security &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-security]]&gt;, Geode &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-apache-geode-summit]]&gt;, 
Data &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-data]]&gt;, Cloud Foundry &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-cloud-foundry]]&gt;, Core Framework &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-core-framework]]&gt;, Serverless / Microservices &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-serverless-microserivces]]&gt;, Modern Web &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-modern-web]]&gt;, DevOps &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-devops]]&gt;, Kubernetes &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-kubernetes]]&gt;, and Reactive &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-reactive]]&gt;.

 


 









 







James Quercetti
Account Executive, Pivotal
AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io &lt;[[mailto:AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io]]&gt; 
 Forwarded this email? Sign up here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
