<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Cloned from interview layout template, Content: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SFpXsn-09mlpM-T2Tv59gU_s_bw3T31ds9Yv5w0fnDs/edit</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_GET Partner Newsletter_2018.007 October 2018 GET Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Partner October Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>Our mission is to enable partners to build deep expertise and 
a thriving business practice with Pivotal.



 

 


 
 
 


 

Serverless



 
 
 
 



In September, our editorial focus was on Serverless. As interest in on-demand computing grows, learn how Pivotal is at the forefront of this exciting development practice. 

 
 

Our crack team of curators has been hard at work gathering high quality content on our featured topic &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/serverless-computing]]&gt;. Below you’ll find a few pieces selected for our partner community.





 

Podcast:







	- Dormain Drewitz and Jeff Kelly discuss patterns in serverless adoption &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-podcasts/bringing-observability-to-serverless-with-iopipe-ep-79]]&gt; and observability best practices with IOPipe CEO Adam Johnson.







 

Video:







	- Mark Fisher talks about Pivotal’s function framework &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/mark-fisher-pivotal-springone-platform-2018]]&gt; Riff, and its operation on Google’s knative project.

	- On the 2018 SpringOne main stage, Google’s Mark Chmarny talked about serverless and knative &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/day-1-keynote-mark-chmarny]]&gt;.







 

Article:







	- Is &apos;native&apos; just a trendy word for anything related to the cloud? This article &lt;[[https://www.solstice.com/fwd/knative-as-inversion-of-native-serverless-applications]]&gt; looks at the value propositions of “nativeness” in Knative beyond the hype.




Don’t forget! You can embed the content stream of your choice in your own site! Find the embed code for Serverless and other content streams on the Partner Portal &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/partner-information.aspx#contentstream]]&gt;.





 


 

 


 




 


October Partner Webinar: Please join us for the next Pivotal Global Ecosystem webinar on Application Transformation! Matt Russell and BJ Cooper will talk about how large organizations plan and execute their application transformation, and how partners are making it possible.
Register here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/webinars-events.aspx]]&gt;
Date: October 17, 2018
Time: 1PM EDT


 




 












 

Enablement



 
 
 
 



With the speed of development in this industry, it can sometimes feel hard to stay abreast of the latest and greatest. We’d like to point out some of our best educational and enablement resources here.

 










 

Platform Acceleration Lab:







	- Oct 8-26: Java Cloud-Native Architect in Boulder

	- Oct 22-Nov 9: Java Cloud-Native Architect in London



For the most up-to-date schedule, check here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform-acceleration-lab]]&gt;, or talk with your Pivotal Alliances Manager.




 

Partner Portal:






	- The Key Concepts page &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/key-concepts.aspx#Explain%20the%20business%20value]]&gt; has resources for understanding how Pivotal defines CI/CD, Cloud Native, Agile, and more.







 

Partner Platform Architect Spotlight:







	- Buildpacks, a staple of CF and Heroku for years, has been accepted as a CNCF Sandbox project &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/peace-of-mind-for-developers-and-operators-buildpacks-is-now-a-cncf-project-welcome-cloud-native-buildpacks]]&gt;.

	- In case you missed it, there’s a new Service Broker for AWS services &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/meet-the-new-aws-service-broker-for-pcf-now-an-open-beta-heres-why-its-the-easiest-way-to-add-18-aws-services-to-your-cloud-native-apps]]&gt;. 18 services at your CF marketplace fingertips.







 

Public Webinars:







	- Oct 11: The Accelerate State of DevOps Report &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/oct-11-the-accelerate-state-of-devops-report-webinar]]&gt; with DORA’s Dr. Nicole Forsgren and Pivotal’s Richard Seroter.

	- Oct 17: GET Webinar on AppTx. Register here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/webinars-events.aspx]]&gt;.

	- Oct 24: Monitor and Measure Your Way to Successful Digital Transformation Webinar &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/oct-24-monitor-and-measure-your-way-to-successful-digital-transformation-webinar]]&gt;.



View our previous and upcoming public webinars here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;.




 

Greenplum Partner Spotlight:







	- Pivotal Greenplum on Kubernetes &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/containerizing-a-data-warehouse-for-kubernetes?utm_campaign=content-social&amp;utm_medium=social-sprout&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_content=1538500646]]&gt; (experimental release) was presented at S1P. Try it out yourself &lt;[[https://network.pivotal.io/products/greenplum-for-kubernetes]]&gt; on Pivotal Network.

	- The partner marketplace for Pivotal Greenplum &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/pivotal-greenplum-marketplace]]&gt; has been launched. Look for integrated solution descriptions here.








 


 

 


 




 

Spotlight: SpringOne Platform 2018 ReCap

We were fortunate to have many incredible SpringOne sessions from Pivots, partners, and customers. Below we’ve highlighted some of the best for you.

Partner Sessions:



	- Accenture’s Paul Daugherty took the main stage to talk about Digital Transformation and Artificial Intelligence &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/day-2-keynote-paul-daugherty]]&gt;.

	- Bruno Borges of Microsoft talks about their work in Open Source, Spring, Java and Azure &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/day-2-keynote-bruno-borges]]&gt;.




Customer Sessions:



	- Dick’s Sporting Goods Jason Williams talks about the sporting goods retailers transition to digital commerce &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jip10Fz693U&amp;list=PLAdzTan_eSPQsR_aqYBQxpYTEQZnjhTN6&amp;t=0s&amp;index=5]]&gt;. 

	- Who says the DoD can’t move fast? Lauren Knausenberger &amp; Bryon Kroger talk about how the US Air Force leverages PCF to deploy software in days &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/day-2-keynote-lauren-knausenberger-and-bryon-kroger]]&gt;, not months.

	- What do The Jetsons, The Boeing 787 Dreamliner, and digital transformation have in common? Find out in Boeing CIO Ted Colbert’s engaging keynote &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018/day-1-keynote-ted-colbert]]&gt;.



Check out the SpringOne playlist &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018]]&gt; to see all 
workshops and session recordings

The Monday prior to SpringOne The Global Ecosystem team brought together over 200 executives from key partner organizations to discuss our business and products strategy, roundtable discussions, and partner awards.

Congratulations to all our 2018 Partner Award winners &lt;[[https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20180924005289/en/Pivotal-Announces-Winners-2018-Partner-Awards]]&gt;! 

 




 







 

Marketing



 
 
 
 



Last month, we talked about how make the most of your time at SpringOne. This month, we have more exciting events, and a fantastic marketing resource.



 
 





 

Upcoming Events






	- Oct - Dec: SpringOne Tour &lt;[[https://springonetour.io/]]&gt; is Pivotal’s multi-city roadshow running through the end of 2018. Sponsorships still available on a per-city basis! Learn how to sponsor a city &lt;[[https://springonetour.io/2018/sponsor]]&gt; that is critical to your practice.

	- Oct 10-11: Do you have a presence in Europe? Cloud Foundry Summit Europe &lt;[[https://www.cloudfoundry.org/event/eusummit2018/]]&gt; is happening in Basel, Switzerland - Don’t forget to look at the Cloud Foundry Foundation’s CF Summit Europe.

	- April 2-4, 2019: Cloud Foundry Summit North America &lt;[[https://www.cloudfoundry.org/event/nasummit2019/]]&gt; is coming to Philadelphia.






 


MARKETING BEST PRACTICE OF THE MONTH: SI Marketing Guidelines
 Our marketing department has built this guide &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/home.aspx#Guide]]&gt; to help you successfully conduct joint partner marketing with Pivotal. You will learn how to leverage:



	- Press releases, blogs, and win reports

	- Joint webinars and case studies

	- Event and roadshow participation




 






 
 
 






 













October Interview







 














For this month&apos;s Q&amp;A, we spoke with Melissa Larson, who leads our efforts with boutique system integrators. 


1. Ten months on the job, what do you now see as the biggest opportunities for Pivotal’s ecosystem?





&quot;Hands down, the biggest opportunity I see is our opinionated application transformation solutions. There are many companies that are selling IT solutions or customized tools. But few are taking on the work of guiding customers through the process of modernizing their legacy applications. I realize that it’s not as sexy as a new mobile application or blockchain experiment, but what is more important than reducing costs and getting software to market faster? By operating legacy applications more efficiently, you free up resources to compete as a software company in the digital world. The keys to application modernization success for partners are:



	- Align to quantifiable business outcomes.

	- Have a productized approach that makes it easy for customers to start

	- Have an opinion on methods and tooling 

	- Use the abstractions to do the right thing




There is a lot of opportunity in digitizing existing processes, let alone transforming you your business operates through software. But you need to get your house in order first. Simplifying legacy applications must be done first to truly free the enterprise to innovate at start-up pace.&quot;




2. What is your number one piece of advice for new partners joining the Pivotal Ready Partner Program?





&quot;At Pivotal, we partner differently. Our mission is to transform the way the world builds software. We do this with a maniacal focus on customer outcomes that is ingrained in every function of our business. Our measurement of success are the outcomes we deliver for customers. My best advice to a new partner is to set aside expectations based on other technology partnerships and focus on how we could accelerate the outcomes we deliver to our customers together. And be patient, selling transformation is hard work. :) &quot;




3. What keeps you busy when you’re not engaged with partners?





&quot;I am a partner and a parent. I spend my time exploring the world with my wife and our 2 year old daughter. Lately, we’ve also been preparing for twin girls expected in March! Other than that, I’m a proud midwestern nerd, with the stereotypical hobbies of ice-fishing, cross-country skiing, reading memoirs and historical fiction, social justice activism and growing vegetables. #GoT&quot;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
