<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>May Emails 2018.Debunking Myths - Microsoft - 5-1-18</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>5/31 Webinar: Debunking Myths About Cloud Portability</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 

Please join us for the webinar, Debunking Myths About Cloud Portability &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/may-31-debunking-myths-about-cloud-portability-webinar?utm_source=digest&amp;utm_medium=webinars&amp;utm_campaign=myths-microsoft&amp;utm_term=q218]]&gt;, on May 31, 2018. 

When moving workloads to the cloud, enterprise architects often ask things like, “Are we losing the ability to choose our stack and change vendors? How easily can I move my 
workloads in and out of the cloud? To keep workloads portable, do I lose out on innovation?” 

There are a lot of misconceptions about cloud portability. The term itself implies moving workloads with no work (not true), suggests completeness in what’s moved (mileage may vary), and ignores the laws of data gravity (at your peril!). Platforms, like Pivotal Cloud Foundry (PCF), can make it much simpler to move workloads between clouds. But PCF fits within a broader set of concerns and decisions that need to be made. 

In this webinar, Pivotal’s Joshua McKenty and Microsoft’s Ulrich Homann will debunk some common misconceptions about cloud portability, while explaining things like: 


	- 
The framework of developer efficiency (versus operational efficiency) tradeoffs across levels of abstraction 

	- 
The spectrum of standards that exist to support movability, and the tradeoffs therein

	- 
Emerging abstractions at the data layer that simplify data access and digital twin development… and the realities 
of the cloud movability they support



Presenters: 
Ulrich Homann, Distinguished Architect at Microsoft
Josh McKenty, Vice President 
of Technology at Pivotal

Date: Thursday, May 31, 2018
Time: 
10:00am PDT / 1:00pm EDT


Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/may-31-debunking-myths-about-cloud-portability-webinar?utm_source=digest&amp;utm_medium=webinars&amp;utm_campaign=myths-microsoft&amp;utm_term=q218]]&gt;

We thank you in advance for joining us.
The Pivotal Team

  © 2018 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g]]&gt;, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103.
Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/c000200I0NAU0rCJC001O00]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/TDAIO000r0000U220N00CJ0]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
