<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.EH 8-20 Org Details</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Organization details</subject>
    <textOnly>All,

This is a truly exciting moment for Pivotal. I’m thrilled that Rob has stepped up to be our new CEO. I’ve had the privilege of working with him for over 15 years, and those of you who know him will agree with me that his instincts and experience position us for future success and give us an unfair advantage over our competitors.

For those not familiar with my background: for the first 10 years of my career I worked as a software 
engineer, first at startups and then for Rob at Pivotal Labs, during which time I became a passionate advocate for the approach and ways of working for which Labs stands. In 2008, I began to help lead and build the Pivotal Labs business, and after acquisition by EMC in 2012 I took over its operations. Helping lead a Pivotal Labs that grew very fast reinforced not just how transformative our software approach can be, but how important our culture is 
to a company’s long-term success.

As we all know, our products and 
services represent a different, modern approach to building and running software. Because our offerings are transformational, our client-facing technical teams have the critical role of helping customers change their mindset as they adopt our products and services. And now that we are a fully subscription-based business, it’s more important than ever to make our customers successful.

Over the past few months, an important discussion has taken place around how we can best organize our client-facing technical teams and what their interface to our sales team and our customers should be. The result of that dialogue was two-fold:

 - We believe that bringing our various client-facing teams under one umbrella will help us improve communication and develop a common, Labs-inspired 
culture. 
 - We need a technical role for each account that helps the salesperson and customer navigate our overall technical team, and which has overall responsibility for the successful adoption of our products and services.

 We expect these two changes (a) to give our customers a smoother introduction and 
more successful long-term experience with our offerings, and (b) to make our sales team more productive by freeing them up to pursue new business.

To accomplish the first, Rob and Bill have asked me to take on an expanded role that encompasses our overall customer-facing technical team, which we will call the Customer Success Organization (CSO). For the second, we will introduce a technologist role and team focussed on customer success per account, reporting to me. CSO will be made up of the following groups:

 - Pivotal Cloud Foundry Solutions (PCFS, led by Dino Cicciarelli and Arni Raghvender). This new team will ultimately be responsible for all technical sales and delivery phases, with specialization maintained in pre- and post-sale roles. Those FEs who have been focussed on PCF pre-sales will join this team under Arni, and Dino will continue to run and build out the services delivery team. Arni and Dino will partner on running the team to ensure technical pre- and post-sale customer success.
 
 As you know, our company’s biggest opportunity is PCF, and we need to do all we can to 
improve our performance in selling and driving client adoption of PCF. Given the pace of change in the PCF world, it is critical at this point to keep our customer-facing and R&amp;D teams as close as possible. That led us to the decision to move this team under James Watters, although it will operate as part of the overall CSO group.

 - Pivotal Data Engineering (PDE, led by Jacque Istok). Jacque will continue to build on the success of his PDE team, providing both pre- and post-sale support for our sales team and customers. Those FEs who have been focussed on our Data play will join this team, and the overall team will continue to grow according to Jacque’s direction. Data continues to be an important part of the Pivotal vision, and as we look to grow our financial targets and market momentum, this technical team will grow to drive that agenda.

 - A technical customer success account team. This critical new technical team, built to accomplish point (2), represents an overarching function responsible for the long-term success of accounts. The function will drive customer satisfaction and renewal performance. Bill and I consider this new team crucial to the success of our subscription business, and it will report directly to me. We have yet to choose a leader for this team, so for now I will manage it directly. Look for more detail here in the coming weeks.
 
 This new team partners with sales reps on accounts, and is responsible for helping position our products and services pre-sale, pulling together the right technical team during the various stages of our customer workflow, and, 
crucially, ensuring that our customers successfully adopt what they have bought. Initially it will be a relatively small team, but over time we will scale the team to support our target account base.
 
 

 - Pivotal Labs (operated by Drew McManus). Given my new role, I’ve asked Drew McManus to take over the day-to-day operations at Pivotal Labs, still reporting to me. Drew has been an important member of the Labs leadership team for years; he has been a client, a partner, and a leader at Labs so he understands the organization deeply. Drew will help coordinate and maintain consistency in the fast-growing Labs business in the regions run by David Goudreau, Mike Barinek, Rahul Singh, and Josh Knowles. I will still be heavily involved in all things Labs, of course—Drew and I will maintain a close relationship.
 
 It’s important that we include Labs explicitly, because I think it helps 
complete the alignment of the Labs business with Pivotal’s mission. I expect the Labs team will have better insight into the other technical groups and vice-versa, and as a result we will see smoother interactions in the sales and post-sales workflow. Over time, I think we’ll see closer alignment in terms of technical philosophy between Labs and the rest of the company. I’d like to thank Mike Barinek for his ongoing work in this last area; Mike has the additional role of CTO at Labs, and I’ve asked him to help drive consistency between Labs and the other technical teams.

 - Global Support Services (GSS, led by Johnny Scarborough). Johnny will continue to run and grow this important team. We expect to define clearer operational integration points between GSS and the other groups, under the guidance of the CST. 

 - Education, Enablement and Alliances Engineers (led by Michael Wood). Many of you will have seen communications from Michael and his team about the exciting new ideas coming from this group. I’m looking forward to seeing the results of his efforts in equipping our technical teams, our customers and partners. We want it to fall under the CSO umbrella so that we can position it as closely as we can to our customer-facing teams.

 - Transformation (led by Siobhan McFeeney). As you probably know, Siobhan joined the company recently with the mission to define and drive our Transformation offering, to centralize what we learn over time, and to articulate to the Sales Field how to position it. You can expect to see her initial output around Transformation definition this quarter. I expect this team to grow over time given its importance to our company.

Overall the CSO team is a large group (approaching 1000 people). As I said, its mission is critical and we are investing and growing the overall team. I’m looking forward to helping to align the groups, define how best to measure success and lead the overall organization in helping our sales team and our customers be successful with Pivotal’s transformational offerings. For the EMEA and APJ regions, we will look to align the structures with the Americas over time.

Rob and Bill have asked me to take on two other important teams at Pivotal:

 - Pivotal Tracker (led by Dan Podsedly). The Tracker product and team have always been a core part of our Labs business. Today we consider them a separate group from Labs, but to keep them closely aligned, we think it makes sense to have Tracker sit next to Labs rather than in R&amp;D. Dan and I have worked together for many years and I’m excited to work more closely with him and the overall Tracker team. I think Tracker has huge potential to drive Labs and PCF business, and I’m looking forward to working with Dan on growing the business and linking more closely to our company’s core plays.
 
 - IT (led by Drew Kramer). Drew considers our IT group to be a place to practice what we preach to our clients. It sets the example for our clients on how to do IT in a way that supports our transformational product and services offerings. For example, our IT staff helps us “dogfood” our own products internally by standing up Cloud Foundry and other instances of our products; IT sets up our Labs offices as a model for our clients; and IT provides internal “Ask” service for our R&amp;D and Labs teams. As a result, it makes sense for IT to sit next to our client-facing offerings. I’m looking forward to partnering with Drew on this mission.

I’m more than happy to talk with anyone who has questions on these changes. In the coming weeks I plan to hold a session with each of the above teams, and I’m looking forward to meeting those of you I don’t know well.

I’d like to thank Rob and Bill for 
giving me a terrific opportunity to help Pivotal in a broader way at this moment in our journey. The privilege to work with this stellar cast is certainly mine.
 
I look forward to working with all of you as we continue to transform the way the world builds software!
 
Edward</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
