<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Tracker Newsletter.PROD STACK 2019 FEB 20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Feb 20 Webinar] Key Ingredients for Successful Product Roadmaps</subject>
    <textOnly>Many product managers struggle to effectively manage their product roadmaps. In fact, planning and prioritizing the product roadmap is the single biggest product management issue, according to a recent Product Planning Report survey of 1,300 product managers.

Join our panel discussion &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/563469319288490243?source=Pivotal]]&gt; and find out how you stack up, hear the key ingredients for successful product roadmaps, and get your own questions answered from our expert panel.

Here’s what you’ll learn in this free webinar:

	- Common product planning pitfalls to avoid

	- How to prioritize roadmap initiatives and get consensus on your roadmap

	- How to make your product roadmaps more collaborative 

Submit your questions when you register, and we&apos;ll address as many as possible. 

RSVP today &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/563469319288490243?source=Pivotal]]&gt; to take advantage of this free webinar.
RSVP &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/563469319288490243?source=Pivotal]]&gt;

THE PANEL

Aloka Penmetcha is a Director of Product Management at Pivotal Software. She has deep experience dealing with the thorniest of product issues, from inspiring people and teams to logically prioritizing business needs in order to continuously deliver measurable value in a lean way. She has an MBA from the Ross School of Business and an MS in Computer Science from the University of Southern California.

Annie Dunham is the Director of Product Management at ProductPlan. She has worked with product and engineering teams for the last 15 years to bring technology products to market. Prior to ProductPlan, she worked with teams at Elite Meetings, LogicMonitor, BlueCasa Communications, and Microsoft. 

Julie Goodner is a Senior Product Manager at Jama Software. She has worked in Product Management for the last seven years, bringing a wide variety of products to market. Prior to Jama Software, she worked with teams at Nike, CDK Global, and Sage Software.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
