<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Badge Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Badges Coming Soon!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello to all Pivotal employees!
We are pleased to announce that we have begun the distribution of our new Pivotal badges! You will be receiving a new security badge soon to replace your EMC badge. Schedule for delivery of new badges in your area is included in this mail. 
There will be 2 different types of badges for Pivotal employees, a Pivotal badge and a Blank badge - each have different access capabilities. 
You will receive one of these badge types: 


 - Pivotal Badges (Non-Labs) - will have your picture, name and employee ID # on the front.  Non-Labs employees will receive this badge type. 
 - Blank Badges (Labs) - will have your employee ID # printed on the back and will be blank on the front. 


These badges are for the interior doors within our Pivotal space only, you will still need to use the building security badge for access into the building after working hours.Exception is Palo Alto where we occupy the whole building so your badge will have 24/7 access into the building.
Access for each badge type:



 - Pivotal Badges  


 - will have access to Pivotal locations with security access systems installed. These are: Palo Alto, NYC, Toronto, London and Bentonville.
 - will have access to any EMC location which you previously had access




 - Blank Badges 


 - will have access to your primary work location only.  You will use a temporary badge at the visiting Pivotal office
 - will not have access to any EMC locations. You will use a temporary badge at the visiting EMC office
 - If you travel between Pivotal offices and prefer a Pivotal badge we are happy to replace it. You can send an email to requests_badge@emc.com &lt;mailto:requests_badge@emc.com&gt; to acquire a Pivotal badge.





Your new Pivotal badge will have the same access as your old EMC badge, including your current access to EMC locations.
When will I receive my new badge?
Scheduled badge distribution is as follows:


 - Week of March  3,  2014: New York City - already distributed
 - Week of March 10, 2014: Toronto  - already distributed, everyone received Pivotal badges
 - Week of March 17, 2014: Palo Alto - everyone will receive Pivotal badges
 - Week of March 24, 2014: San Francisco  - Pivotal Badges only for use in other locations. SF office uses the building security system and does not require the use of a Pivotal or Blank badge
 - Week of March 31, 2014: U.S. Home Office Workers - will be sent to your home address
 - Weeks of April 1-15, 2014: All Other U.S. Locations - including EMC and VMware locations 
 - April 15-30, 2014: EMEA &amp; APJ employees - all locations, home office, EMC and VMware offices


Further instructions will be sent to you prior to distributing badges in your location.
More information can be found here:


 - Pivotal Badge FAQs &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/document/d/1ISuV3r6Ge-HZcHaqp2R-bRuzbWCEeI0LGi8yyDFuTyg/edit&gt; 
 - Blank Badge FAQs &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/document/d/1ISuV3r6Ge-HZcHaqp2R-bRuzbWCEeI0LGi8yyDFuTyg/edit&gt; 


Regards,
Lisa Davern
Real Estate &amp; Facilities</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
