<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Bill Cook 11/12 Org Announcement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Organization Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,
 
 As many of you know, the majority of our business comes from North America with APJ and EMEA representing opportunity for massive future growth. As we plan for 2016 and beyond, we believe that now is the time to shape and energize our effort in APJ. We have learned a lot over the past two and a half years and the view into our future—and what we need to do to be successful—has never been more definitive.

In my discussions with 
Melissa Ries about our plans forward, she expressed a desire to contribute to Pivotal in a way that allows her to move back to Sydney in a new role doing something meaningful that helps accelerate the growth of the company. We have agreed to a new role working for Leo Spiegel, where she essentially represents the portfolio of Corporate Development activities. Melissa’s responsibilities will include investments, M&amp;A, strategic partners &amp; alliances, and transformation engagements. Melissa’s leadership and valuable experience in running our business (Greenplum and Pivotal) makes her the ideal person to manage and drive these strategic activities in APJ. Melissa will move into this new role once we identify a new sales executive to own and manage our day-to-day business pursuits in APJ. 

We will continue to focus our efforts in APJ on our way to becoming the global company of choice for digital transformation and the cloud native future. I am confident that 2016 is the year that APJ will break into new markets, gain new customers and build an effective ecosystem of partners.

Special thanks to Melissa and the entire team for their 
continued dedication and support of the Pivotal mission. I’ll be in the region later this month and look forward to seeing many of you. 

Let’s make Q4 the best quarter ever!
Bill</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
