<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Content Syndication_SecureHybridBankingRefArch_WP_Q117.B - Invitation to</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Complimentary White Paper: Secure, Hybrid FinServ Reference Architectures for Cloud-Native Applications</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
We invite you to download our new white paper: Secure, Hybrid FinServ Reference Architectures for Cloud-Native Applications &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/white-papers/secure-hybrid-banking-reference-architectures-for-cloud-native-applications?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q2-2017-WP]]&gt; authored by Pivotal’s Jared Ruckle, Matt Stine, Ford Donald, and Guillermo Tantachuco.
Running IT for a financial institution is not for the faint of heart. The job requires a unique mix of creativity, agility, pragmatism, and plenty of grit. There are constant generational changes to navigate, like:



 - 
Rising consumer expectations. The market now expects your apps to behave like their favorite mobile apps. You need to deliver fast, responsive, and engaging experiences to be relevant.


 - 
Increased competition from FinTech. Your competitors aren&apos;t only your neighbors on Wall Street. Silicon Valley&apos;s best and brightest aim to disrupt the financial services industry.


 - 
Regulatory requirements &amp; compliance. Industry rules and regulations must inform how you innovate and where you invest.


 - 
Security. The most successful financial services institutions of the next decade will go fast and go secure. Choosing one or the other isn&apos;t an option.



How can you capitalize on these seismic shifts and gain market share? By becoming a cloud-native enterprise. Download &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/white-papers/secure-hybrid-banking-reference-architectures-for-cloud-native-applications?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q2-2017-WP]]&gt; this free white paper and learn how to deliver software continuously, in a secure and scalable way.
Download Today! &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/white-papers/secure-hybrid-banking-reference-architectures-for-cloud-native-applications?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q2-2017-WP]]&gt;
Enjoy!
The Pivotal Team
 
© 2017 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103. Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://connect.pivotal.io/UnsubscribePage.html]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://connect.pivotal.io/subscription-management.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
