<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Tracker Newsletter.MAR 21 PROD STACK</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Mar 21 Webinar] Managing Complex Requirements in an Agile World</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/6246187415904966915?source=pivotal]]&gt;

More and more, teams are looking to develop faster, react faster, and plan faster—even 
companies building complex software and hardware products. Do you have the skills to properly balance moving fast while still documenting and maintaining complicated requirements?

Join our expert panel &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/6246187415904966915?source=pivotal]]&gt; as we discuss the tools, tricks, and processes that can be used to achieve success and avoid failure when 
managing complex requirements. We’ll hear from seasoned pros like Mark Barbir, SVP Engineering at ProductPlan; Bryon Kroger, COO at Kessel Run; and Robin Calhoun, Senior Product Manager at Jama Software.

Here’s what you’ll learn from this webinar:

	- Requirements management done the right way
	- Tips for managing requirements across teams and products
	- Best practices for traceability and change management

Submit your questions when you register, and we&apos;ll address as many as possible. 

RSVP today &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/6246187415904966915?source=pivotal]]&gt; to take advantage of this free 
webinar.
RSVP &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/563469319288490243?source=Pivotal]]&gt;

THE PANEL

MARK BARBIR is the Senior Vice President of Engineering at ProductPlan. He has more than 20 years of design and development experience and is driven by building great teams that make great products. Prior to ProductPlan, Mark led software engineering at MINDBODY, Inc. serving 60,000 boutique wellness clients and millions of consumers. A Bay Area native, Mark now lives in San Luis Obispo with his wife and three sons. He enjoys hanging out at the local beaches, hiking, and going to concerts. 

BRYON KROGER is Chief Operating Officer at Kessel Run. His team made headlines for the incredible fuel savings from the tanker planner application and for taking their deployment frequency from 5 years to 1 week. Behind the scenes, he and his leadership team were transforming the requirements process—generation, testing, and delivery—in a domain where failure can carry serious consequences. Breaking through the &quot;fuzzy front end&quot; and the &quot;last mile&quot; allowed the Air Force to move from Water-Scrum-Fail to #agileAF!

ROBIN CALHOUN is a Senior Product Manager with Jama Software. She uses her education in human behavior and economics to identify and understand patterns in the way people work, and patterns in product development data, to help people make better decisions. Robin’s goal is to enable people to understand, manage, and gain insights from the rich data we already have access to. Before joining Jama, Robin was a product manager at Tendril, defining data-driven Energy Service Management Products. She holds a degree from Columbia University in Neuroscience and Behavior, and Economics.

MODERATOR KEVIN STEIGERWALD is the VP of Products and UX at Jama Software. He&apos;s a full-stack product designer with over 10 years of experience designing, researching, marketing, planning, and building products.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
