<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.BC - 9-14 Org Memo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Marketing and Sales Ops Organization Changes</subject>
    <textOnly>All,
 
 Todd Paoletti, who has led our global operations effort, has recently decided to pursue new opportunities outside of Pivotal. Todd has played an important role in the company’s success, bringing his product and operational acumen to the table and delivering meaningful results. On behalf of the leadership team, I’d like to thank Todd for the role he has played in our Pivotal journey.

We also recently announced a series of moves that will help us continue to focus on 
customer adoption and success, and to accelerate growth. Making these changes from our position of strength gives us the opportunity to organize ourselves to better anticipate market opportunities, and to out execute the competition.

As part of these 
moves, we’re announcing the following changes within the Sales Operations and Marketing Teams. Effective immediately, I’ve asked Michelle Kerr to lead a newly formed team that combines Field Marketing and a number of strategic marketing resources out of Corporate Marketing, reporting to me. This organization, called Market Development, will combine and focus marketing and opportunity development resources on growing our overall pipeline, and making a positive impact on field productivity at the front end of the sales funnel.

The Market Development organization will include:


 - Lead Generation &amp; Marketing Program Support for our Cloud Platform Business
 - Inside Sales &amp; Renewals Team led by Miguel Montesinos
 - Proposal &amp; Customer Onsite Marketing Experience Team led by Kelli Robinson
 - Customer Marketing Team led by Sophia Tseng
 - Field Marketing, led in the Americas by Kim Marie Ruquet
 - Sales Training &amp; Enablement, led by Jennifer O’Neill
 - Marketing Operations, led by Christina Deex
 - Lead Generation &amp; Marketing Programs for Data, led by Michael Weir



Richard Snee will directly manage Brand 
&amp; Experience Marketing, leading the overall brand experience and efforts for Pivotal, including communications, digital, events, and brand identity. Additionally, Richard will join the Real Estate team to help in our pursuit of a consistent look, feel and experience in Pivotal offices around the world.

Second, the Sales Operations team formerly reporting to 
Todd Paoletti, will now report to Robert O’Donovan. This team, led by Greg Stroud, includes the Deal Desk and Analytics team under Eric Landon, Business Management team under Chris Braney, Salesforce team and our Sales 
Ops Project Office. Corinne Lewy and her Product Operations team will move to the Sales Ops team. The Product Operations team manages the Product Lifecycle process, Pricing and Licensing, and Product Fulfillment. Sales Operations will continue to align business practices with Pivotal’s strategic objectives, providing business insights to the field and maintaining deal velocity.

Please join me in thanking Todd and 
wishing him the best on his future endeavors, and in welcoming Michelle Kerr to Global Field Operations. We also thank all of the teams noted above, whose work is critical to our future success.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
