<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.1-11-16 RM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2016 Priorities and Organization</subject>
    <textOnly>Welcome back. I want to wish everyone a happy and healthy New Year.

The month of January is always a hopeful time, as we celebrate the end of one year and the beginning of another. While 2015 challenged all of us to extend our reach, find new solutions to complex problems, and execute with tenacity and speed, we should also look back on this year with tremendous pride and accomplishment.

There’s so much to be grateful for. Personally, I’m grateful for all of you, and for the privilege to lead you—because it’s your hard-work, dedication and commitment to our shared values that led us through 2015, and will keep leading us in 2016.

We now have 16 Pivotal office locations from San Francisco to London to Tokyo, all evangelizing the value proposition that Silicon Valley is no longer a geography, but a state of mind. It can be anywhere. Pivotal has always been a part of the fabric of the Valley, but we’re now using what we have learned to allow entire industries, around the world, to leverage the best of Silicon Valley.

Unleashing this mindset on companies with decades of industry know-how and global reach, combined with modern software development methodologies (Labs), a modern cloud platform (PCF) and modern data tools (BDS), changes the way the world builds software.

I’ve never been more optimistic about a year ahead. 

However, being in the vanguard of a software revolution is an opportunity, not a right. As a result, we need to continuously reorganize ourselves as we evolve and grow. To bring on the next 100 customers, the next 1000 Pivots, or open the next 10 offices, we need to continue to refactor our own structure. You’ll recall that we made organizational modifications last August to ensure we closed 2015 from a position of strength—and we ended up having our most financially successful year ever.

Effective immediately, in order to move faster and with greater focus, we’re announcing the following organizational changes: 

We are elevating Edward Hieatt, James Watters and Onsi Fakhouri with broader responsibilities. 

Last August, we temporarily brought PCF services and field engineering teams into James’ Cloud Platform Group to strengthen alignment between our Pivotal Cloud Foundry (PCF) product and field 
teams—where Dino Cicciarelli’s PCF Solutions team partnered closely with the pre-sales PCF team led by Raghvender Arni, now known as the Platform Architects team. The incubation period is over, and Dino, Arni and their respective teams will report to Edward, who leads the Customer Success Organization (CSO), comprised of Pivotal Labs and our Technical Field (Platform Architects, PCF Solutions, Pivotal 
Data Engineering), Global Support Services (GSS), Education &amp; Enablement, Customer Solutions, and Transformation. Edward is also responsible for the IT and the Pivotal Tracker teams.

The recent acquisition of CloudCredo has given us an opportunity to further distance ourselves from the competition. Colin Humphreys, CloudCredo’s CEO, will become our new CTO for Cloud. Also, Colin, James Bayer (CF Product), Ryan Morgan (Spring) and their respective teams will report to Onsi, who will now lead R&amp;D for all Cloud products. 

James Watters has been relentless in asserting our unique point of view to customers and the marketplace. In order to accelerate our momentum with customers, James will lead our integrated outbound marketing efforts. Corporate Marketing, Data Product Marketing, Pivotal Tracker Product Marketing, Field Marketing, and Inside Sales teams will now report to James, who continues to lead Cloud Product Marketing, Cloud Technology Evangelism, and Cloud Outbound 
Product Management teams.   

Over the holidays, I asked Richard Snee to take on the added responsibility of leading our Real Estate strategy and team. As I mentioned, our physical space is the biggest lever to closing the next big deal or on–boarding the next class of Pivots—this is an enormous responsibility that requires Richard’s creativity, relentless execution and singular focus. I thank Richard for his leadership as CMO. Richard will continue reporting to me, and lead Real Estate at Pivotal. 

Thank you all for your effort and contributions to–date. Even though being agile in how we organize ourselves is the right thing—and something larger competitors cannot easily do—change that affects people can be challenging. I encourage us all to be empathetic and show understanding, patience, and support as we take these steps with confidence, knowing that they better position us to make the potential that 2016 promises our reality.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
