<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Gartner App Strategies &amp; Solutions Summit NV_Q416.Post-event email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thanks for joining Pivotal at Gartner Application Strategies &amp; Solutions Summit</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},

Thank you for joining us at the Gartner Application Strategies &amp; Solutions Summit last week, we hope you found it valuable! 

 Pivotal is excited to help companies that are ready to take advantage of the opportunities facing IT today. Of course these opportunities also bring with them challenges, and Pivotal is uniquely positioned to help organizations as they embark on their journeys. Whether you’re just starting to investigate cloud, or looking to completely transform your IT architectures and processes to be more Agile and DevOps oriented, Pivotal can usher you on that journey; start today with a free trial of Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform/pcf-tutorials/getting-started-with-pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=menu&amp;utm_medium=link&amp;utm_campaign=gettingstartedwithpcf]]&gt;. 

 To hear about an organization that has successfully undertaken a transformative journey, check out &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLAdzTan_eSPQ1fuLSBhyB4eEZF7JQM0Mx]]&gt; the recorded sessions from Pivotal’s SpringOne Platform conference; they cover a 
wide range of topics including Cloud-Native Architectures, Java, Data Microservices, DevOps, and much more. 

 Finally, check out some of our online resources including webcasts &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/resources/1/webinars]]&gt; such as the upcoming Five Common Approaches to Application Modernization &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/agile/webinar/five-common-approaches-to-application-modernization]]&gt; with Forrester Research, eBooks &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/resources/1/ebooks]]&gt;, analyst 
reports like Gartner’s Market Guide for Application Platforms &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/gartner-market-guide-for-application-platforms]]&gt;, and white papers here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/resources/1/white-papers]]&gt;. 

 -The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
