<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.1-14-16 BC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2016 Priorities and Organization</subject>
    <textOnly>The leadership team is excited about the tremendous opportunity in front of us. Thank you for all of your contributions that have allowed us to start the new year from a position of strength. To ensure transparency, we want to share how we’re evolving our organizational structure to bring on the next 100 customers, the next 1000 Pivots, and open the next 10 offices. While this a lengthy note, it is important for everyone to have the same information regarding changes across all of our teams. Read on to learn about important updates to Sales &lt;[[#sales]]&gt;, Services &lt;[[#services]]&gt;, Labs &lt;[[#labs]]&gt;, Product &amp; Marketing &lt;[[#product-marketing]]&gt;, and Engineering &lt;[[#engineering]]&gt;.





SALES: Positioning Our Team for a Big Year


In the Americas, we have elevated Andrew Ettinger to lead four geographic and industry-focused regions in the United States: Telco/Media led by Craig Nowell; Financial led by Bill Serino; Southeast U.S. led by Brian Froehling; and a new Mid–South U.S. region led by Mat Wilcox. Andy O&apos;Brien will continue to lead our biggest geography, which encompasses Northeast U.S./Canada led by John Jahnke, Central/Western U.S. led by Rob Schmitt, U.S. Government led by Keith Salisbury, Industrial led by Steve Kutscher, and Latin America led by Ana Claudia 
Borges. We will now have a powerful duo in Andy and Andrew to drive a significant portion of our company&apos;s business. Special thanks to Andy for his ongoing leadership and teamwork with Andrew to position Pivotal for a big year.

In Europe, building 
on their 2015 progress, Alan Coad will continue to tighten the EMEA focus on the most important markets, sectors and accounts. Our 2016 plan is to drive scale with foundational wins in each targeted market—setting us up for rapid expansion across the region. Following some coverage changes this year, Alan’s sales regions and leaders are UK/Ireland led by Robbie Byrne, Germany, Switzerland, Austria &amp; Netherlands (DACH/NL) led by Michael Ramsperger, France &amp; Southern Europe led by Stephane Dubois, and Middle East led by Rached Dabboussi. We have already opened new Pivotal offices locations in Dublin and Berlin in 2015. We will shortly move into a much larger space in London and have Paris on the horizon for 2016.

In Asia, we mentioned Melissa Ries is moving 
into a new role in Corporate Development focused on strategic partnerships. As we continue our search for a new APJ Leader during the interim, the country leaders will report directly to Bill Cook. In addition, each country/region will have a Pivotal executive sponsor: Scott Yara (Japan–Takumi Masai-san), Leo Spiegel (Korea–YoungSoo “Scott” Lee), Edward Hieatt (South Asia–Waiyuen “Eric” Sin), James Watters (China–Patrick Liu), Bill Cook (Australia–Gavin Jones). Similar to Europe, we opened new Pivotal office locations in Sydney and Tokyo in 2015, and have Beijing on the horizon in 2016. These investments will accelerate growth in Asia, and we expect to expand our Asia footprint with major customer wins in 2016.

Alex Luttschyn will continue to lead Labs sales, and Tim Kalbas will continue lead our Data sales efforts. Both Alex and Tim will be primarily focused on our Americas business, but will provide support for the respective Labs and Data sales teams in the other geographic regions.

Lan Haarmann will now serve as Chief of Staff to both Bill Cook and James Watters, helping Bill and James work even closer together on sales strategy.

Finally, over the last two years, Michelle Kerr has given extraordinary service to Pivotal between her leadership and contributions in marketing and sales. While she explores new opportunities within Pivotal and the Federation, Michelle will continue reporting directly to Bill Cook in a new executive advisory role.
 



SERVICES: Fostering a Renewal Culture

In mid–2015 we introduced the newly formed Customer Success Organization (CSO), which now includes the entire technical field of pre- and post-sale technologists, who act as one team to help our clients adopt and become successful with our products and services. The CSO group is directed at the core of our company mission to transform how the world builds software—if customers renew their Pivotal Cloud Foundry or Big Data Suite subscription, it validates that our software is transforming their companies for the better. Renewals keeps customer “churn” low, and has quickly become one of our most critical areas of focus as we continue our journey to hyper-growth.

We have made significant progress in how the CSO group will align, communicate and operate in 2016. Among the most important developments is the concept of a “Consumption Plan” for each of our customers, which outlines how a customer will use our products and services. This document, created at the time of sale and with the input of our sales team, the CSO team, and the customer, helps to quickly align all the players. It then becomes the basis for us to measure, over time, if a customer is on track for renewal. This will be the most important indicator—along with a consistent approach to measuring Customer Satisfaction—for future renewals across our customer portfolio.

In order to foster better communication between our various account-focused teams, 
we have introduced the concept of standups and retrospectives. These practices have been so successful at Labs over the years because of their emphasis on continuous alignment and feedback among teams. They will help to align and build a unified culture in the field, and help our teams succeed in their mission to help clients transform over time.

Finally, we have made further organizational changes, listed below, to define our CSO structure more consistently across the globe. One important note is that we have renamed the pre-sales role known as PCF Field Engineer role (FE) to “Platform Architect”.

Leadership for CSO globally remains constant:


 - Global Support Services (GSS) continues to be led by Johnny Scarborough
 - Education &amp; Enablement continues to be led by Michael Wood 
 - Transformation continues to be led by Siobhan McFeeney
 - The new team of Customer Solutions Directors, responsible for technical strategy and oversight on strategic accounts for all our products and services, will be led by Mike Barinek 


In the Americas, the CSO Leadership team will be:


 - PCF Platform Architects team (pre-sales PCF), led by Raghvender Arni
 - PCF Solutions (post-sales PCF), led by Dino Cicciarelli 
 - Pivotal Data Engineering team (pre- and post-sales Data), led by Jacque Istok  


In EMEA and APJ, we will evolve the technical field team to reflect the structure pioneered in the US. The Americas leaders will be responsible for effectively communicating with the EMEA and APJ teams concerning the ongoing iteration of the operational CSO model as the year progresses.

In EMEA, the CSO Leadership team 
will be: 


 - The PCF group of Platform Architects (pre-sales) and PCF Solutions (post-sales) will be led by Andy Hawkins. Franck Sidi will continue to support post-sales during this transition
 - Data group combining pre- and post-sales engineers, led by Frank Sidi
 - Les Klein will assume the role of EMEA Field CTO for Data


In APJ, the CSO Leadership team will be:


 - Platform Architects team (pre-sales PCF), led by Jason Jackson
 - PCF Solutions (post-sales PCF), led by Matt Clark, who joins us from Pivotal EMEA
 - Pivotal Data Engineering team (pre- and post-sales Data), led by Peter Cooper
 - Customer Solutions team (technical account oversight and renewals focus), led by Roz Gregory


We’d like to thank everyone involved in helping to define the new organization, and we’re excited to see our sales and CSO teams partner to make our customers successful!
 



LABS: Alignment and Growth

Pivotal Labs continues to be led by Drew McManus, with regional leadership from David Goudreau (US West), Rahul Singh (US East), and Josh Knowles (EMEA). In 2015, Labs truly aligned with the PCF business—close to half of Labs projects now include the use of PCF, and that percentage will continue to grow. Further, over half of Labs projects now use Spring technologies.

The Labs and PCF joint-selling motion and the importance of each to the other for our customers is well ingrained, and Labs is now operational in 16 cities and stands at over 500 Pivots strong. We’re extremely proud of the Labs team for making a dramatic shift in focus in just two years. Time and time again we hear from our customers that they find Labs to be exactly what they are looking for during this time of disruption and change in industry. This represents a way of building software that is both disciplined and effective, and also fosters innovation, catalyzes change, and brings a relentless focus on the customer experience. Labs now serves dozens of these companies daily on what for them has become a critical journey.

2016 will be another year of growth for Labs, both in terms of the number of Pivots and the number of offices. We expect to open offices in at least four more cities, and to add more than 150 new Pivots over the year. In conjunction with the Labs and PCF offering, Siobhan McFeeney’s Transformation team provides us with a way to help companies as they lay out their plans for organizational change to support their goals of working differently. We have found that the transformation offering is a powerful means to enable all products and services as we work with very large clients such as Ford, Home Depot, and Allstate.

Through Labs and our Transformation team, we present customers both a vision and the well honed tactics that come from more than two decades of direct experience in helping companies change. We’re excited to continue to grow the presence of these offerings globally in 2016!
 



PRODUCT &amp; MARKETING: Leading Product Go-to-Market

James Watters&apos; new integrated marketing and product organization allows us to continue asserting our unique point of view with customers and the marketplace. Streamlining our corporate marketing, product marketing, and field marketing capabilities into a single cohesive team will further accelerate customer adoption of our transformative technology.

The Corporate Marketing team—consisting of Labs Marketing, Field Marketing, Digital Marketing, Design, Events and Marketing Operations—will be led by James. During this transition period, James and Scott Yara will work together to continue to define the corporate marketing team.

We&apos;re elevating Ian Andrews with 
broader responsibilities that includes Product Marketing for Data and Tracker, APJ &amp; EMEA Marketing &amp; Business Development, Inside Sales, as well as his current responsibilities for PCF Product Marketing, Platform Engineering, Business Development, and Analyst 
Relations. The Inside Sales team which have aligned with each Sales region, respectively, will now align to our top global sales objectives, and execute these in their respective Sales regions. Kelli Robinson, who will report to Ian, will lead the Inside Sales team, in addition to her current Sales Productivity and Customer Briefings team. Ian will continue to report directly to James.

Mark Kropf and the Outbound Product Management (Strategic Product Management) team remains part of James’ organization, and serves as the voice of the customer back to our engineering teams, which will influence and prioritize our product development efforts.

Andrew Clay Shafer and the Tech 
Evangelism team as well as Benjamin Black will also continue reporting directly to James. Andrew is focused on creating our first tentpole event called “Platform”, and Ben will continue to work with our top Internet of Things (IoT) customers.     

Finally, Michael Lee will now report directly to Rob Mee, where he will continue to lead the Global Communications team, responsible for corporate and 
international public relations and social media, as well as brand, executive, employee and financial communications.





ENGINEERING: Transforming How The World Builds Software

2016 is shaping up to be a big year for product innovation at Pivotal—Cloud and Data.

In Pivotal Cloud Foundry, the bets we&apos;ve made over the past two years are paying off. Diego, our next-generation container orchestrator and runtime, is now in production both on PWS and in PCF. Substantial improvements to BOSH are close to shipping, and will open up new opportunities for deploying and managing robust data services for our customers. And our efforts around application log and metrics visualization, analysis, and monitoring will be making their way to customers soon.

We are in a great position to iterate rapidly, and continue to deliver the industry&apos;s most comprehensive cloud native platform.

Spring has also had a banner year. In 2015, Spring Cloud Services entered general availability, and we have brought a powerful microservices stack to our PCF customers&apos; fingertips. And monthly downloads for Spring Boot, which unlocks the potential for rapid application development, have more than doubled over the past year—hitting 2.25 million monthly downloads.

The 
fact that Pivotal is responsible for both PCF and Spring gives us a substantial competitive advantage in the market. We now have a unique opportunity to bring these two powerful technologies closer together, and to ensure that PCF is the premier platform for running Spring microservices.

These organizational changes give us an opportunity to enable the 
ever-growing PCF engineering, PCF product, and Spring teams to collaborate more closely and efficiently. Under the broader Cloud R&amp;D organization headed by Onsi Fakhouri, James Bayer 
will continue to oversee product for PCF, and Ryan Morgan will continue to oversee Spring and App Fabric.

We’re also excited to welcome CloudCredo into the Pivotal Cloud R&amp;D family. The CloudCredo team are Pivots at their core. They’ve built their business upon and operate it using the Pivotal approach, and they bring a wealth of 
experience and expertise around helping customers deploy and iterate on top of Cloud Foundry. In particular, CloudCredo CEO Colin Humphreys has been a remarkably skilled, visionary, and empathic communicator of the power and versatility of the Cloud Foundry platform. In light of his skills and experience, we’re excited to announce that Colin will be joining us as CTO for Cloud. As CTO, Colin will help us articulate and communicate our big picture strategy and roadmap as we deepen our investments in our cloud offerings.

In Pivotal Big Data, we had a great year and overachieved on our most important metric—Big Data Suite bookings growth. In less than two years, we have transformed our business to be ~80% subscription based. Given our transition to open source for all data products over that same time period, we&apos;ve aligned our data business with market forces and trends in ways that few thought were possible.

And while our 2015 financial results give us much to be proud of, there’s still a lot of hard engineering work ahead around unifying our Data tools with our Cloud Platform in order to unlock the promise of our open source vision for big data. As a result, we are elevating Elisabeth Hendrickson with broader responsibilities. Elisabeth will now lead R&amp;D for all Data products, and Duncan Lord and the Data Product Management teams will report directly to Elisabeth.

Finally, we want to thank you all for your efforts and contributions. As Rob mentioned, being agile in how we organize ourselves is the right thing, but change that affects people requires empathy, understanding, patience, and support. We will take these steps with confidence, knowing that they better position us for another record-breaking year.

Bill, Scott, Edward, James, and Onsi</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
