<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Drew Dell email and EBC correction</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.09-05-16 DKramer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Dell EMC Integration Update—Email and EBC Guidance</subject>
    <textOnly>All,

We hope many of you are enjoying time with friends and family on this Labor Day holiday, and that our Pivots outside of the U.S. and Canada had a restful weekend.

In regards to the upcoming Dell and EMC merger, many of you erroneously received an email from EMC IT issuing a new Dell Technologies email address. EMC has acknowledged the error and expressed their regret. As a result, please disregard the before-mentioned email titled Getting Started on your first day at Dell Technologies. Your @pivotal.io address is still your only company-issued email.

Note: We have already arranged for the 50–75 Pivotal employees with existing access to backend EMC HR and Finance systems to receive the access they need to Dell email and systems.

In addition, some customer-facing Pivots have also erroneously received guidance on new Executive Briefing Center (EBC) 
procedures—e.g., exclusive use of Dell Technology templates and Dell devices. EMC regrets the error and confusion it may have caused. Please disregard that EBC guidance and continue to use Pivotal templates and rules of engagement.

 

Finally, other than an upcoming memo from Michael Dell, please disregard any future emails from non-@pivotal.io addresses in regards to the Dell EMC Integration. We are working hard behind the scenes to minimize any impact to Pivotal, and will reach out directly to folks if there are any specific actions required.

As Rob stated, it’s business as usual for all of us at Pivotal. If you have any questions or concerns, please don&apos;t hesitate to contact AskHR@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:AskHR@pivotal.io]]&gt; or your HR business partner &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/departments/human-resources/meet-the-people-team]]&gt;.
Drew
CIO</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
