<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Michael Dell Harvey note</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.09-01-2017 RMee</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Support for Disaster Relief</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Pivots,


I&apos;m forwarding this very important message from Michael Dell to all of us at Pivotal. Michael and his wife Susan have made a huge contribution to the relief and recovery effort for flood-stricken coastal Texas. Their leadership in this galvanizes an even larger effort to support the millions of people in need in the wake of this disaster.


Michael also reminds us that we in the US are not the only ones suffering from devastating weather patterns, and he has 
included links to resources for those of us who can help elsewhere.


I wholeheartedly support Michael&apos;s call for everyone to pitch in what they can. I&apos;m starting by adding my own contribution, to which Michael and Susan will add matching funds, to support the program.


It&apos;s self evident that this is the right and kind thing to do, but I&apos;d also like to point out that it&apos;s going to work: in the 
Dell&apos;s flood relief initiative, 100% of every donation goes to relief efforts, as the foundations involved will cover administrative costs.


Thank you.
Rob




From Michael Dell:


 
Team,
 
In the last week we have seen natural disasters of unprecedented proportions affecting communities from Houston, Texas to India and Nepal. Our thoughts go out to all our families and loved ones, our colleagues and friends who are living through such a terribly difficult time.
 
Outreach to all our affected team members, customers and partners is ongoing. It’s been difficult, because communication channels are still not functioning properly in many locations. We will update all of you as additional information is available.
 
While devastation anywhere in the world affects us all, Hurricane Harvey has been especially personal for me. I grew up in the now flooded neighborhoods of Houston, and my wife, Susan, and I are lifelong Texans. I know the tragedy is equally personal for everyone around the world who lost the place that they call home.  We share in broken hearts at the loss and in pride at the resilience and courage of our hometowns. Now, we owe it to them to help with the massive rebuilding effort that lies ahead.
 
At Dell, we have always tried to do more than our share to support our communities, and I have been so impressed with the Dell Technologies family’s outpour of support and passion to serve those impacted by recent hurricanes and floods. I encourage everyone to get involved.
 


	- To support the Texas rebuilding effort, Susan and I, through our family foundation, have helped establish the RebuildTexas Fund. To participate in the effort, visit https://www.rebuildtx.org/ &lt;[[https://www.rebuildtx.org/]]&gt;.  


 


	- To support disaster response in South Asia, please visit the Legacy of Good Community here &lt;[[https://dell.yourcause.com/home#/engagement/e91451ac-d171-455a-9166-d91d0bf30adc]]&gt; .


 


	- Of course, beyond dollars, our greatest asset is the expertise and passion of our Dell Technologies 
team.  Within Legacy of Good Community &lt;[[https://dell.yourcause.com/home]]&gt; you can support relief efforts as well as find volunteer opportunities from local organizations seeking assistance.


 
Wishing deeply for the continued safety and well-being of us all,
 
Michael</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
