<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Webinar_JK_DS-Neil Raden-Data Warehouse_Q117.Invite 1-25-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Data Warehouse in the Age of Digital Transformation</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.brighttalk.com/webcast/14891/241943?utm_source=Pivotal&amp;utm_medium=brighttalk&amp;utm_campaign=241943]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},

 In the past years of Big Data and digital transformation “euphoria”, Hadoop and Spark received most of the attention as platforms for large-scale data management and analytics. Data warehouses based on relational database technology, for a variety of reasons, came under scrutiny as perhaps no longer needed. 

 However, if there is anything users have learned recently it’s that the mission of data warehouses is as vital as ever. Cost and operational deficiencies can be overcome with a combination of cloud computing and open source software, and by leveraging the same economics of traditional big data projects - scale-up and scale-out at commodity pricing. 

 In this webinar, Neil Raden from Hired Brains Research makes the case that an evolved data warehouse implementation continues to play a vital role in the enterprise, providing unique business value that actually aids digital transformation. Attendees will learn:

 - How the role of the data warehouse has evolved over time 
 - Why Hadoop and Spark, though valuable for some, are not replacements for the data warehouse 
 - How the data warehouse supports digital transformation initiatives 
 - Real-life examples of data warehousing in digital transformation scenarios 
 - Advice and best practices for evolving your own data warehouse practice

Webinar details below:

Date: Wednesday, February 22, 2017
Time: 11:00am PST / 2:00pm EST 

Save My Seat &lt;[[https://www.brighttalk.com/webcast/14891/241943]]&gt;

 About the Speaker: 
Neil Raden is a founder and principal analyst at Hired Brains Research, Raden provides research, consulting and advisory services in data management, Analytics and Decision Management. He was part of the original faculty of the The Data Warehousing Institute (TDWI) and is the co-author of the book “Smart (Enough) Systems,” Prentice Hall. 

We look forward to you joining us!
 
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
