<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Spring Days_Q2Q317.Chicago Email #1 Send April 4</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You’re invited to a Spring event for the professional Java developer</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.springdays.io]]&gt;
May 30-31, 2017
 1871 
222 W Merchandise Mart Plaza #1212 
Chicago, IL 60654




Register &lt;[[https://www.springdays.io/ehome/spring-days/chicago?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=global-event-spring-days-2017]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 
 Cloud computing ushered in a software renaissance and Spring has never been more relevant and in-demand. We’re rapidly advancing the framework—adding flexibility to the programming model for cloud-native, reactive, and functional workloads. 
 
We invite you to join developers from the Chicago area for a two-day community event where we will share presentations and participate in open discussions about all things Spring. Don’t miss this opportunity to learn from and share with members of the Spring community. 
 
Featured Speakers

Josh Long with Mark Heckler
Spring team member &lt;[[https://spring.io/team/jlong?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=global-event-spring-days-2017]]&gt;

Reactive Spring
 Spring Framework 5.0 is almost here! One of the most exciting introductions in this release is support for reactive programming. In this talk, we&apos;ll look at the net-new Netty-based web runtime, how existing Servlet code can run on the new world, and how to integrate it with existing Spring-stack technologies.

Michael Minella
Spring team member &lt;[[https://spring.io/team/mminella?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=global-event-spring-days-2017]]&gt;

Cloud Native Batch Processing
 This talk will explore the latest release of Spring Batch as well as how to utilize it in a modern cloud environment. We will work through building a cloud native batch process using Spring’s stack including Spring Batch, Spring Cloud Task, and other cloud tools.
 
Register now &lt;[[https://www.springdays.io/ehome/spring-days/chicago?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=global-event-spring-days-2017]]&gt; for $200.00 USD; space is limited and it will sell out.
 
Have questions, or interested in sponsoring? Please contact us at springdays@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:springdays@pivotal.io]]&gt;.
 
We hope to see you there,
The Spring Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
