<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Greenplum Summit_New Jersey_Q118.GP Summit - White - 3/13</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Save on Greenplum Summit registration, pre-conference training announced</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://greenplumsummit.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=gp-summit-q118]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},

I’m super excited that Greenplum Summit &lt;[[http://greenplumsummit.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=gp-summit-q118]]&gt; at PostgresConf &lt;[[https://postgresconf.org/conferences/2018]]&gt; is just over a month away, and I want to make sure you don’t miss the opportunity to join us! This is where decision makers, data scientists, analysts, DBAs, and developers will meet to discuss, share, and shape the future of advanced data technologies. 

See the details below for 25% off your conference pass and hands-on pre-conference training that will jump start your knowledge into truly innovative technology. I look forward to seeing you there!
Save 25% off your conference pass
A single pass gives you full access to both PostgresConf and Greenplum Summit. Use code 2018_GPDB to get a 25% discount when you register &lt;[[https://postgresconf.org/conferences/2018/buytickets]]&gt;.
Pre-conference training April 17
Pivotal is offering accelerated, hands-on training workshops prior to Greenplum Summit at PostgresConf. Space is limited, so register now for in-depth training with Pivotal data engineers and data scientists!



	- Beyond Business Intelligence (BI): Data Science in the Open Source Greenplum Database &lt;[[https://postgresconf.org/conferences/2018/program/proposals/beyond-business-intelligence-bi-data-science-in-the-open-source-greenplum-database]]&gt;

	- Petabyte Scale Data Warehousing with Open Source Greenplum Database &lt;[[https://postgresconf.org/conferences/2018/program/proposals/petabyte-scale-data-warehousing-with-open-source-greenplum-database]]&gt;



Stay connected 
Join the conversation on Twitter #DataTellsTheStory, and follow @PivotalData &lt;[[https://twitter.com/PivotalData]]&gt; for news and updates.
See you in April,
Jacque</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
