<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Hadoop Summit_San Jose_Q216.Post event 7-14-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Software: The Time for Digital Transformation is Now</subject>
    <textOnly>What a week! We hope you had a great time at Hadoop Summit and thank you for coming by the Pivotal booth! With Hadoop Summit behind us, it’s time to take action on all of this new knowledge. It doesn’t matter what industry you’re in—your company has the opportunity to use data and analytics to redefine customer relationships, to drive new levels of profitability and efficiency, and even develop an entirely new business model. 

 To find out how Pivotal can help you on this journey, please consider joining us in Las Vegas at SpringOne Platform, August 1–4. SpringOne Platform &lt;[[http://springoneplatform.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=Hadoop-Summit-SJ-Q216]]&gt; brings together the people, process and tools for delivering and operating data-driven software. Whether you are just starting your transformation journey or already delivering at scale, there will be in-depth advanced technical topics and accessible introductory content covering data analytics, machine learning, microservices, agile methodology, continuous delivery, devops, and more. Register today &lt;[[https://2016.event.springoneplatform.io/register/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=Hadoop-Summit-SJ-Q216]]&gt; and use the code: hadoopsummit20 for 20% off your ticket price!

 We also invite you to take advantage of our library of Big Data and Digital Transformation resources, including:

 - Read the blog &gt; When It Comes to Big Data, Cloud and Agility Go Hand-in-Hand  &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/when-it-comes-to-big-data-cloud-and-agility-go-hand-in-hand]]&gt;
 - Read the case study &gt; Pivotal HDB Shows Simplicity of ODPi Interoperability  &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/case-studies/case-study-pivotal-hdb-shows-simplicity-of-odpi-interoperability]]&gt;
 - Read the report &gt; Pivotal and Hortonworks Expand Relationship with HDB SQL-on-Hadoop Reseller Deal  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/analyst-report/pivotal-and-hortonworks-expand-relationship-with-hdb-sql-on-hadoop-reseller-deal]]&gt;
 - Read the blog &gt; Fail Fast and Ask More Questions of Your Data with HDB 2.0  &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/products/fail-fast-and-ask-more-questions-of-your-data-with-hdb-2-0]]&gt;
 - Watch the video &gt; Pivotal’s Jacque Istok Talks About Breaking Down Barriers with Data on theCUBE  &lt;[[https://youtu.be/QarmzQYgzKY]]&gt;
 - Watch the webinar &gt; Analytics in the Cloud: Getting the Most Out Of Analytics Deployments  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/analytics-in-the-cloud]]&gt;
 - Read the paper &gt; Introducing the Newly Redesigned Apache HAWQ (incubating)  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/white-paper/introducing-the-newly-redesigned-apache-hawq]]&gt;
 - Read the eBook &gt; Shaping the Future of Data Warehousing through Open Source Software &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/shaping-the-future-of-data-warehousing-through-open-source-software]]&gt;

 Now is the time to take the reins of your Digital Transformation. Let’s build something meaningful. 

 Sincerely, 
 
 The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
