<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Postgres Vision 2016_Q416.Post-event</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Time for Digital Transformation is Now</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello,
 
 With Postgres Vision 2016 behind us, now is the time to put Postgres and Pivotal Greenplum to work to accelerate your digital transformation. It doesn’t matter what industry you’re in–your enterprise has the opportunity to use software, data and analytics to redefine its relationship with customers to develop completely new business models and drive new levels of profitability and efficiency. 

 We invite you to take advantage of our library of database, open source and digital transformation resources, including:


 - eBook: Shaping the Future of Data Warehousing Through Open Source Software  &lt;[[https://tdwi.org/research/2016/04/ebook-shaping-the-future-of-data-warehousing-through-open-source.aspx?tc=page0]]&gt;
 - White Paper: Toward Actionable Information - Transforming Business Results with Big Data and Analytics  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/transforming-business-results-with-big-data-and-analytics]]&gt;
 - White Paper: Introducing the Newly Redesigned Apache HAWQ  &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/big-data/white-paper/introducing-the-newly-redesigned-apache-hawq]]&gt;
 - On-Demand Webinar: Your Open Source Playbook  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/your-open-source-playbook-for-2016]]&gt;
 - Podcast: Database Portability Ups Developer Productivity &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-insights/features/episode-one-database-portability-ups-developer-productivity]]&gt;



Also, check out these other database-related open source projects we support: Greenplum Database &lt;[[http://greenplum.org/]]&gt;, Apache HAWQ (incubating) &lt;[[http://hawq.incubator.apache.org/]]&gt;, Apache Geode (incubating) &lt;[[http://geode.apache.org/]]&gt;, Apache MADlib (incubating) &lt;[[http://madlib.incubator.apache.org/]]&gt;. 

 Now is the time to take the reins of your digital transformation. To learn more about how Pivotal can help, visit pivotal.io &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/]]&gt; or contact us &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/contact]]&gt; to discuss how to put your digital transformation plans into action. Let’s build something meaningful. 

 Sincerely, 
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
