<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>EMEA_Event_Open House &amp; DTF_London_Q316.Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Invitation: Pivotal Digital Transformation Forum</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/digital-transformation-forum/london]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}}, 

 Do you understand how to gain or retain market leadership in the new era of digital disruption? How will you drive customer acquisition and retention with superior digital experiences? How can you accelerate the pace of business innovation to stay ahead of the competition? 

 If these are some of the challenges you face, join us to learn how digital disruption is affecting businesses in the UK, how digital disruptors are so successful, and what innovative technology capabilities you need to become a modern software company. 

Why you should attend this event?

 GE partnered with Pivotal to power innovative industrial internet apps central to the company’s historic, multi-billion dollar steps taken in 2015 to become the world’s premier digital industrial company. 

 Increasing demand for faster delivery of interactive mobile healthcare apps pointed Humana to a Silicon Valley state of mind, working alongside Pivotal to introduce a new culture encouraging development teams to work better together. 

“With Pivotal we have minimized our innovation cycles and can now respond to changing market demands faster than ever before, both of which allowed us to develop a profound software culture in our transformational journey into a digital company.” —Christoph Hartung, Head of Connected Cars, at Mercedes-Benz

DATE : 13 September 2016 
TIME : 9h00 to 16h45 
LOCATION: Pivotal, The Warehouse, 207 Old Street, London 

Full Agenda &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/digital-transformation-forum/london]]&gt;

Register now as space is limited. This is an exclusive event. 

REGISTER HERE &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/digital-transformation-forum/london]]&gt;

 We look forward to meeting you soon! 

 The Pivotal Team 

 Questions? Please visit our website &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
