<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>this is a clone from the 014 January 04 newsletter</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.015 January 18 2019 Newsl</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal 5-Point Friday</subject>
    <textOnly>January 18, 2019

Hello, my name is Mike Rhodes, a 13 year Dell EMC veteran. I joined Pivotal in May 2018 as a technical resource in the East, specifically focused on Dell Technologies alliances. Please enjoy this special National Retail Federation, (NRF), edition of 5-Point Friday.


 


 

 


 

1. Dell technologies at nrf

Almost 40,000 people attended the National Retail Federation “Big Show” in the Jacob Javits, NYC this week Jan 13-15.
 
VMware had a booth at the conference to show off retail technologies like VeloCloud and CloudWatch while Dell Technologies had a session at the show with our joint customer Home Depot. The standing room only session, titled, Modernize Retail IT to Deliver Exceptional Customer Experiences in the Intelligent Store went over the Dell Technologies “Better Together” story and how it helped Home Depot modernize their stores.



 


 

 


 


2. Dick&apos;s speaks at nrf executive dinner

Pivotal hosted an Executive Dinner after the National Retail Federation “Big Show” where David Lammers, VP of Store Technology at Dick’s Sporting Goods, shared his Pivotal success story with executives from Altria, Estee Lauder, HEB, American Eagle and other retailers. David talked about how Dick’s was spending millions of dollars on commercial software that was barely used and couldn’t get anything of their own into production. Pivotal, in less than a year of partnering with Dicks, has helped them cut costs, drive efficiencies and improve their time to market for new functionality. More people need to hear David’s inspiring story!


For more on Dick’s Sporting Goods, check out their interview from SpringOne Platform here &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oBwtX6FfW7c]]&gt;.

 


 

 


 


3. Greenplum: The Netezza replacement

As the Netezza DBMS faces a significant end-of-support milestone, leveraging an open source, infrastructure-agnostic replacement that has a similar architecture will help avoid a costly migration. Learn more at the upcoming Greenplum webinar on February 13th. Webinar hosts include Jacque Istok, Head of Data, Pivotal and Kelly Carrigan, Principal Consultant, EON Collective.

Register for the webinar here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/feb-13-ten-reasons-why-netezza-professionals-should-consider-greenplum-webinar]]&gt;.

 


 

 


 


4. Pivotal Container Service on Azure!
On Wednesday we announced the release of Pivotal Container Service (PKS) 1.3 &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/pks-azure-multi-cloud-kubernetes]]&gt; which means you can now deploy PKS on Azure. This brings the total supported clouds to four, (vSphere, GCP and AWS were previously supported). PKS on Azure will open up a plethora of opportunity for enterprise customers that are not happy with managed Kubernetes services or are looking for a multi and hybrid cloud Kubernetes deployment options.
 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/KQIBf2wqeMg]]&gt;
Watch this PKS on Azure video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/KQIBf2wqeMg]]&gt;
Pivotal Container Service 1.3 Documentation &lt;[[https://docs.pivotal.io/runtimes/pks/1-3/]]&gt;



 


 

 


 

5. Pivotal Days Customer Workshop 



Pivotal Days was so successful we are excited to announce an expansion of the program in FY20! Pivotal Days is a half day multi-customer workshop focused on running Pivotal Container Service (PKS) on Pivotal Ready Architecture (PRA).
 
We even hosted 2 Pivotal Days events in NYC this week with many customers from the National Retail Federation. The agenda for that workshop, and future Pivotal days can be found here &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Day-NYC.html]]&gt;.
 
In the first quarter of FY20, Pivotal Days will come to:






	- Conshohocken, PA - February 26
	- New York, NY - February 27 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-New-York-February-2019.html]]&gt;
	- Cambridge, MA - March 12 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Boston-March-2019.html]]&gt;
	- Fairfield, CT - March 26 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Fairfield-March-2019.html]]&gt;
	- Hartford, CT

	- Rochester, NY

	- Minneapolis, MN






	- Chicago, IL
	- Cleveland, IL

	- Atlanta, GA

	- Dallas, TX

	- Seattle, WA

	- Denver, CO







Please reach out &lt;[[mailto:AskDellTech@pivotal.io]]&gt; to pre-register your customer for these upcoming events.

- Mike


 






 
 
 


 


Upcoming Events


	- Pivotal Pulse Podcast: Pivotal Changed My Life! T.Mobile Customer Interview &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pivotal-changed-my-life-customer-interview-with-t-mobile/s-cSA1a]]&gt;



Digital Knowledge


	- Website: Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx]]&gt;, designed exclusively for Dell Tech

	- Now Available! Pivotal Pulse Exclusive &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/?ReturnUrl=%2fEnglish%2fGlobal%2fsales%2fdell-tech.aspx]]&gt;, confidential

	- Win of the Week: Germany Team lands $15M PAS, PKS Win at DATEV &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/dell-tech.aspx#wins]]&gt;

	- Customer Video: Kroger &amp; Pivotal in the News &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/customers/kroger]]&gt;
	- SpringOne Conference Videos: Security &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-security]]&gt;, Kubernetes &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-kubernetes]]&gt;



 


 

















Mike Rhodes
Advisory Platform Architect, Dell Tech Synergy East
AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io &lt;[[mailto:AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io]]&gt; 
 Forwarded this email? Sign up here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
