<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>New D&amp;I skills update</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.D&amp;I Upskill July 2017, No 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the D&amp;I Upskill Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>Today we&apos;re launching the first D&amp;I Upskill Newsletter, a new series dedicated to helping you access practical and snackable resources related to issues of diversity and inclusion. The series has been designed by Pivots for Pivots, based on your requests. We aim to send this email once a month, with each issue dedicated to a different topic. Each email should give you tools to better deal with issues you may face.
Based on overwhelming interest, our first topic is &quot;Having Difficult Conversations at Work&quot;. 
Happy learning,
The Upskill working group: Papa Akuffo, Amy Benoit, Natalie Bonifede, Eileen Markatos, Andrew McKenzie
Have feedback? We want to hear it! &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfiZc8_VMFvNDeNGh4N0npNF632Mrq4UnOYrva8q0TqpnBroA/viewform]]&gt;
To Read—If you do anything, do this!


 - Don&apos;t Shy Away From Discussing Difficult Topics of Race and Equity &lt;[[https://www.fastcompany.com/3062571/your-work-should-make-it-easy-to-discuss-difficult-topics-of-race-and-equity-at-the-office]]&gt; at Work.
 - You Just Had A Difficult Conversation at Work. Here&apos;s What To Do Next &lt;[[https://hbr.org/2017/05/you-just-had-a-difficult-conversation-at-work-heres-what-to-do-next]]&gt;.


To Do 


 - Like any other skill, getting comfortable with difficult conversations takes work. Use these role playing exercises &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/document/d/1xM0iP6RwQSmx6QqF6Jr0EXjVF3VsYcD0gYvbOnXqgxQ/edit]]&gt; to practice with real-world scenarios.


To Consider


 - Need a sounding board? Reach out to the People Team &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/departments/human-resources/meet-the-people-team]]&gt; for informal advice (tip: you don&apos;t need to have something &quot;formal&quot; to discuss!
 - Talk to a friend at another company who may bring a more neutral perspective.
 - Google it. Research best practices and how experts navigate these topics.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
