<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>This is the August version of the GET newsletter. Doc: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1GV5nvWtRu9RrBvIficp0bE7Xz2PHqrUsk8WBiTWLWcE/edit#</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_GET Partner Newsletter_2018.004 August 2018 GET Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Partner August Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>Our mission is to enable partners to build deep expertise and 
a thriving business practice with Pivotal.



 

 


 
 
 


 

.NET and The Return of Windows



 
 
 
 



In July, .NET was our main editorial focus. .NET workloads make up around 50% of enterprise applications, and the languages originally authored by Microsoft are in the midst of a renaissance with the maturation of .NET Core across OS’s.

 
 

We’ve organized a few of our most popular pieces of .NET content and made them available for you below. However, if you’d like to see all of the content we publish on the topic, the best place to look is in our content stream &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/net-and-the-return-of-windows]]&gt; -- and don’t forget that this stream is embeddable &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/partner-information.aspx#contentstream]]&gt; if you’d like always-fresh content for your site!




 

Blog






	- In addition to Java developer content, SpringOne Platform offers a ton of great content for .NET developers as well! See our guide to the conference for .NET developers &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/net-and-the-return-of-windows/the-net-developer-s-guide-to-springone-platform-2018]]&gt; to learn about which sessions can be most valuable.

	- Earlier this year, Pivotal’s Jared Ruckle and Shawn Neal (who brought Vagrant, Packer, and Chef to Windows) sat down to discuss &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/net-and-the-return-of-windows/the-net-renaissance-is-happening-now-here-s-why-it-s-a-new-era-for-net-developers]]&gt; the ongoing “.NET Renaissance”, and talk about some of the driving forces behind the uptick they’re seeing in .NET focus.






 

White paper







	- And of course if you’re interested in diving deep on the HOW-TO of modern .NET, we recently published an extensive white paper &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/net-and-the-return-of-windows/pivotal-cloud-native-dotnet-the-right-way]]&gt; sharing our experts’ opinions on the best way to write modern, .NET applications.







 


 

 


 




 


August Partner Webinar: In a few weeks we’ll be presenting a webinar on how to make the most of your Spring One Platform experience! This partner specific webinar will cover how to use the event to learn, make sales, connect with the Pivotal field teams, and more.
Register here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/webinars-events.aspx]]&gt;
Date: August 21st
Time: 1PM EDT


 




 












 

Enablement



 
 
 
 



With the speed of development in this industry, it can sometimes feel hard to stay abreast of the latest and greatest. We’d like to point out some of our best educational and enablement resources here.

 










 

Platform Acceleration Lab:







	- Aug 13-17: .NET Cloud-Native Developers

	- Aug 13-31: Cloud Native Architects

	- Sep 10-14: Java Cloud-Native Developers


For the most up-to-date schedule, check here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform-acceleration-lab]]&gt;, or talk to your Pivotal Alliances Manager.




 

Partner Portal:






	- Pivotal Partner Platform Architects have put together a collection of blueprint diagrams &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/presales/reference-arch.aspx]]&gt; of common use cases for Apps + Services +PCF Identity. 






 

Partner Platform Architect Spotlight:







	- PCF 2.2 was released in early July with many new features and improvements. Read about all the updates here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/how-pivotal-cloud-foundry-2-2-helps-you-improve-the-metrics-that-matter]]&gt;!

	- The Open Service Broker API (OSBAPI) continues to gain traction. Check out this whitepaper &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/white-papers/an-inside-look-at-the-open-service-broker-api]]&gt; on how the OSBAPI helps deliver services for both Cloud Foundry and Kubernetes.

	- You may have heard the recent announcements from Google about Knative. Read about how Pivotal will use Knative to build a portable Function-as-a-Service platform &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/knative-powerful-building-blocks-for-a-portable-function-platform]]&gt;.






 

Public Webinars:







	- August 8 - Pivotal’s Vince Russo and Peter Blum demonstrate spanning Spring and .NET workloads &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/aug-8-running-spring-net-and-ibm-watson-voice-on-pcf-2-0-webinar]]&gt; across Pivotal Cloud Foundry and Pivotal Container Service.

	- August 22 - Pivotal Data Engineer Alistair Turner talks about how to protect sensitive data &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/aug-22-how-to-meet-enhanced-data-security-requirements-with-pivotal-greenplum-webinar]]&gt; with Greenplum - both natively and via Pivotal Partner solutions.

	- August 23 - Best practices and data modeling techniques &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/aug-23-5-tips-for-getting-started-with-pivotal-gemfire-webinar]]&gt; to get the most out of GemFire.




View our previous and upcoming public webinars here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;.




 

Greenplum Partner Spotlight:







	- Read about the Pivotal Greenplum 5.10 release &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/pivotal-greenplum-5-10-introduces-greenplum-kafka-connector-for-real-time-data-loading]]&gt;, including Apache Kafka integration for real time data loading.

	- Zettaset Encryption &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/delivery/working-with-data.aspx#updates]]&gt; For Pivotal Greenplum And Pivotal GemFire now Available On Pivnet.

	- How to access instances &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/delivery/working-with-data.aspx#updates]]&gt; of Pivotal Greenplum for for demos, testing, and developing solutions.







 


 

 


 
 
 


 

Marketing



 
 
 
 



Last time, we talked about making the most of the Pivotal Editorial Themes Calendar &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/more/recordings.aspx]]&gt;.



 
 





 

Upcoming Events






	- Sept. 24-27: SpringOne Platform in Washington D.C. - SpringOne Platform is Pivotal’s premier customer event, which sold out both sponsorships and tickets last year. Download the sponsorship prospectus today &lt;[[https://d1ophd2rlqbanb.cloudfront.net/2018/sponsors/SpringOne-Platform-2018-Prospectus.pdf]]&gt;. Want to attend? Register here &lt;[[https://2018.event.springoneplatform.io/register]]&gt;.

	- Mar - Dec: SpringOne Tour - SpringOne Tour &lt;[[https://springonetour.io/]]&gt; is Pivotal’s multi-city roadshow running through the year. Sponsorships still available on a per-city basis! Learn how to sponsor a city that is critical to your practice &lt;[[https://springonetour.io/2018/sponsor]]&gt;.

	- Oct 10-11: Cloud Foundry Summit Europe in Switzerland - Do you have a presence in Europe? Don’t forget to look at the Cloud Foundry Foundation’s CF Summit Europe &lt;[[https://www.cloudfoundry.org/event/eusummit2018/]]&gt;.





 


MARKETING BEST PRACTICE OF THE MONTH: Pivotal Partner Site

Were you aware that every partner has a page available on Pivotal.io/Partners &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/partners]]&gt;?

The Account Profile Administrator from your company can update this content on the profile page of the Partner Portal &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/profile/account_profile.aspx]]&gt;. Keep this page up to date with an overview of your strategic partnership and description of your offerings. 
Reach out to your Pivotal Alliance Manager if you have any questions.

Over the coming months, we’ll be updating our branding on the partners site to emphasize our message of “We Partner Differently”. Keep an eye out for more!

 






 
 
 






 














 













Q&amp;A with Danny Zaidifard


This month we spoke with Danny Z, who leads our Global System Integrators.  


1. Danny, you recently moved from the Strategic Partner team to leading our Global SI’s. What are some of the most interesting things you’ve learned that you didn’t expect about our SI relationships?





As I mentioned in a recent partner webinar &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/more/recordings.aspx#webinars]]&gt;, I am regularly blown away by the breadth and depth of relationships our SI Partners have with their customers. Our SI partners often have a deep understanding of customers’ application portfolios, often times operating them soup to nuts! As such, our SI partners have had invaluable input as we work together to build transformation journeys for our joint customers. I am also encouraged by the level of executive sponsorship we have with our partners. Building a Cloud Native Practice is often times a CEO-level priority, so we have enjoyed both access, commitment, and time from Partner Leadership. Lastly, it has been great to see the level of joint activity we already have with partners across our customer base.




2. What are you most excited about in the SI ecosystem in the next 6-12 months?






I am humbled by the pace of growth around our SI ecosystem over the last 12 months. The market opportunity around Cloud Native App Transformation is increasingly evident, and our SI partners are making focused investments in this space. The next 12 months is really about Pivotal journeying with our SI partners as they transform their own capabilities and build out their Cloud Native businesses. It is a huge privilege and incredibly exciting to be a part of this! 

At Pivotal, we often talk about “partnering differently”... we want to be in the boat with our partners as they drive this change. Hopefully we can put to rest the myth of “Pivotal is competing with SI’s” -- we have been very vocal to customers, investors, and analysts to instead get the word out that SI partners are a key component to our scaling strategy.




3. What’s been keeping you busy on weekends? What do you do in your downtime?






I have 3 young sons, aged 9,7,5… need I say more? Weekends are usually busy with all their activities, but I love it. I personally cannot think of anything that is as energizing and exhausting as being a parent. As a family we love to cook, go on walks, and watch cooking shows on TV!

I must admit that I spend a ton of time refreshing myself on science, math, music, literature, etc in order to keep the myth alive that “Dad knows everything”... Unfortunately, I suspect the jig may be up quite soon!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
