<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_PAIR_Q217.London_Invite 4-24-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You&apos;re invited - Pivotal Analytics Innovation Roadshow</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[pivotal.io/event/pivotal-analytics-innovation-roadshow/london?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=PAIR-2017]]&gt;
Hello {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 
Every enterprise knows the importance of using data and analytics to accelerate innovation. With digital leaders disrupting just about every industry, it’s an absolute requirement. But knowing something and actually doing it are two different things.
 
Join us for the Pivotal Analytics Innovation Roadshow, where you’ll get practical advice from data scientists and data engineers on how to jumpstart your analytics practice and start putting data to work today.
 
Date:
Tuesday 16 May 2017

Time:

8.30am - 1.15pm Strategy Session
1.15pm - 5.15pm Data Science Workshop 
(Limited seating &amp; for practitioners only)

Location: 
Pivotal London Office
211 Old Street, London, EC1V 9NR (map &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps/place/211+Old+St,+London+EC1V+9NR,+UK/@51.5259343,-0.090919,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x48761ca61bf76b2d:0x89c21dcce87fd5a1!8m2!3d51.5259343!4d-0.0887303]]&gt;)

Register &lt;[[pivotal.io/event/pivotal-analytics-innovation-roadshow/london?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=PAIR-2017]]&gt;
 
Pivotal has a proven record for partnering with enterprises to enable digital transformation through technology, agile development, and analytics. Join us to learn how we can help you deliver innovation. We will cover:

 - The role of analytics in digital transformation.
 - How to move legacy production data warehouses to the cloud.
 - Steps to develop and implement your analytics strategy and roadmap.
 - How to apply agile methodologies for iterative data science practice.
 - Implementing the latest analytical models from machine learning to geospatial and graph.
 - Analytics use case scenarios in areas like risk and fraud management, security and IoT.
 - Advice for selecting the right technology to support your analytics practice.

We’ll end with a data science workshop geared toward practitioners to apply all that was learned.
 
Wondering if you’re the right person in your organization to attend the roadshow? The event is geared toward: 

 - Business leaders and marketers who leverage data to compete and win
 - Enterprise architects and IT, data warehousing, and business intelligence professionals
 - Data scientists, business analysts, statisticians, data engineers and hackers

If you have any questions, please email Phil Reay at preay@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:preay@pivotal.io]]&gt;.

Sincerely,
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
