<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Velocity_New York_Q316.Attended 9-29-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>With Pivotal, Transform How You Build Software</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}},

With Velocity New York 2016 behind us, now is the time to accelerate your digital transformation. It doesn’t matter what industry you’re in, your company has the opportunity to use open source software, cloud-native platforms, and data analytics to redefine the customer experience, develop completely new business models, and drive new levels of profitability and efficiency. 

 At the conference, we heard great talks on performance, security, modern architecture, collaboration, and the challenges that go along with each. We learn from the experiences of others, and Pivotal customers are demonstrating every day that it’s possible to completely transform the software development process by adopting great principles and platforms. Want to learn more? 

 We invite you to take advantage of our library of growing resources, including:

 - Allstate Podcast - Matt Curry from Allstate, one of the largest US insurers, describes the company’s journey to Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment, and Test-driven development with the goal to drive automation all the way through the application lifecycle. Listen  &lt;[[http://thenewstack.io/allstates-devops-honeymoon-pivotal-going-strong-one-year-later/]]&gt;
 - White Paper on NetflixOSS and microservices - This brand new white paper takes a look at microservices, how Netflix solved technical challenges, and how you can do the same using Spring Cloud. Download  &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/supercharging-your-microservices-with-netflixoss-and-spring-cloud]]&gt;
 - Microservices Architecture eBook - This eBook by Matt Stine &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/author/mstine]]&gt; helps developers learn how to architect and write cloud native applications, as well as understand how to deploy and manage them. It examines the cultural, organizational, and technical changes necessary to migrate traditional monolithic applications and service-oriented architectures to cloud native architectures. Download  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/platform/migrating-to-cloud-native-application-architectures-ebook]]&gt;
 - The Cloud Native Platform eBook - This digital eBook by Duncan Winn &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/author/dwinn]]&gt; explains the essential capabilities of a platform needed to support cloud applications and examines the changes enterprises need to make in process, organization, and culture if they are to take advantage of this approach. Download  &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-the-cloud-native-platform]]&gt;

Now is the time to take the reins of your digital transformation. Let’s build something meaningful. 

 Sincerely, 
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
