<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Email_Spring_Monthly_Newsletter (Pre-2018).August News (3) (2 webinars)</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>SpringOne 2GX - Group Discounts Available - Register Today</subject>
    <textOnly>AUGUST 2014
&lt;http://www.springone2gx.com&gt;
Tickets will run out for SpringOne2GX 2014 – Register now!
SpringOne2GX is where the cutting edge Java developers are. Join us at the conference to learn about Pivotal&apos;s vision for micro service architecture, Big Data, Cloud, and all things Spring, Groovy, Grails. Whether you&apos;re building and running mission-critical business applications, designing the next killer cloud or big data application, SpringOne 2GX will help you learn alongside the leaders of the enterprise Java community. Immersion training &lt;http://springone2gx.com/training&gt; for Hadoop and Cloud Foundry is being offered this year before the show at never before seen prices, and space is limited.
Register Now &lt;https://2014.event.springone2gx.com/register&gt;
Spring Boot&apos;s convenient: SpringApplicationBuilder
Java8 in STS: enable @NonNull checks
Java8 also introduced advanced type annotations. One of the most famous use cases for those annotations are the @NonNull annotations that help you to write code that doesn’t throw NullPointerExceptions anymore. Even though the Eclipse Java compiler supports the @NonNull analysis for quite some time already, these checks got combined with the new type annotations to allow @NonNull annotations and the corresponding checks in even more sophisticated positions (like the generic element type of collections). You can enable and configure these checks in the compiler errors/warnings preferences and you should definitely take a look at them. You find them in the “Null analysis” section:
Microservices with Spring Boot
Speaker: Josh Long

Microservices? A thing? Or hype? What does it mean in practice? The answer, like so many Facebook statuses, is complicated. In broad strokes, Microservices offer a refreshed approach to application architecture. Microservices are a new way to describe many of the patterns that have fallen out of large-scale applications in practice over the recent years. There is no doubt that the approach works.

The question is: how does one build a microservice architecture? Join Josh Long for this webinar introducing Spring&apos;s support for building microservice architectures.
Europe
Tuesday, September 16
 3:00PM GMT Summer Time
 (London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_MicroserviceswithSpringBoot-JoshLong7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, September 16
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_MicroserviceswithSpringBoot10AM_Register.html&gt;
Process Driven Spring Applications with Activiti
Speakers: Josh Long and Joram Barrez, Activiti

Today&apos;s applications are complex, distributed systems that - taken together - produce results. Tracking the flow of work through that system, however, becomes increasingly more painful as automated- and human-driven tasks are integrated into business processes. Business can&apos;t react to what it can&apos;t see. Business can&apos;t measure what it can&apos;t see. &quot;Workflow&quot; describes the sequence of processes through which a piece of work passes from initiation to completion. Workflow systems, like Activiti, describe and then execute these processes. Activiti is an open-source, Apache 2-licensed workflow engine that works with Spring and Spring Boot.

In this webinar, join Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long and Activiti-ninja Joram Barrez for a look at how to distill, describe and reuse complex business processes using Spring (and Spring Boot) and Activiti.

Upcoming Events:


9/16 12pm Hadoop Ask Me Anything &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Hadoop-Ask-Me-Anything/events/201746952/&gt; - Join our Apache Hadoop contributors Roman Shaposhnik and Suhas Gogate this month for a one-hour session, during which they answer your questions on Hadoop and related topics. This meetup has both office and dial-in options. 

9/17 12pm Cloud Foundry Ask Me Anything &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Cloud-Foundry-Ask-Me-Anything/events/201748202/&gt; - Meet Cloud Foundry Engineer, Jamie OMeara from Pivotal, to ask your Cloud Foundry questions until the hour is up! If you&apos;d like to ensure that your question is in the queue, please post your questions in the comments section before the start of Cloud Foundry Ask Me Anything.
Europe
Tuesday, September 23
 3:00PM GMT Summer Time
 (London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_ProcessDrivenSpringAppsActiviti7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, September 23
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_ProcessDrivenSpringAppsActiviti10AM_Register.html&gt;
Building a Shopping Cart in 24 Hours using Spring
Speakers: Casey Doolittle and Phil Dutson, ICON Health &amp; Fitness. Creating a transactional website that is secure, fast, and responsive is a challenge all on its own. Creating one in 24 hours borders madness, however with the resources that Spring brings to the table, this can be accomplished.
Watch Video &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QBfuTBJv3qE&gt;
Archived videos
 Pivotal Toronto Meetup Replay: Production Grade Applications with Spring Boot &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/25/pivotal-toronto-meetup-production-grade-applications-with-spring-boot&gt;
Using WebSocket to build an interactive web application
This guide walks you through the process of creating a &quot;hello world&quot; application that sends messages back and forth, between a browser and the server. WebSocket is a very thin, lightweight layer above TCP. It makes it very suitable to use &quot;subprotocols&quot; to embed messages. In this guide we’ll dive in and use STOMP messaging with Spring to create an interactive web application.
View Guide &lt;https://spring.io/guides/gs/messaging-stomp-websocket/&gt;
Whatever you’re building  -  these 15-30 minute guides are designed to get you productive as quickly as possible , using the latest Spring project releases and techniques as recommended by the Spring team.



http://spring.io/guides


 If you want to make contributions to an existing guide, there is a set of guidelines &lt;https://github.com/spring-guides/draft-gs-template/wiki&gt; you can read. They include instructions on installing Asciidoctor as well as rendering the content to check out your edits. Just sign our contributor’s agreement &lt;https://support.springsource.com/spring_committer_signup&gt; and submit a pull request.
Spring XD 1.0.0.RC1 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/18/spring-xd-1-0-0-rc1-released&gt;
 Spring Framework 4.1  &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/21/spring-framework-4-1-release-candidate-available&gt;
 Spring Data Dijkstra SR2 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/28/spring-data-dijkstra-sr2-released&gt;
 Spring Batch Admin 1.3.0.RELEASE &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/28/spring-batch-admin-1-3-0-release-is-available&gt;
 Spring XD 1.0 GA &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/30/spring-xd-1-0-ga-released&gt;
 Spring MVC Test HtmlUnit 1.0.0.M2 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/06/spring-mvc-test-htmlunit-1-0-0-m2-released&gt;
 Spring Boot 1.1.5 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/07/spring-boot-1-1-5-released&gt;
 First Release Candidate of Spring Data Release Train Evans &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/13/first-release-candidate-of-spring-data-release-train-evans-available&gt;
 Spring Framework 4.1 RC2 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/15/spring-framework-4-1-rc2-released&gt;
 CVE-2014-3527 Fixed in Spring Security 3.2.5 and 3.1.7 &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/15/cve-2014-3527-fixed-in-spring-security-3-2-5-and-3-1-7&gt;
Spring Framework 4.1 – handling static web resources &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/24/spring-framework-4-1-handling-static-web-resources&gt;
 
Using Spring Cloud programmatically &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/29/using-spring-cloud-programmatically&gt;
 Spring Framework 4.1 – Spring MVC Improvements &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/07/28/spring-framework-4-1-spring-mvc-improvements&gt;
 Extending Spring Cloud &lt;http://spring.io/blog/2014/08/05/extending-spring-cloud&gt;
 Pivotal CF Capabilities At A Glance: James Watters &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/wattersjames/pivotal-cf-in-2-slides&gt;
&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/training#spring&gt;
Spring Core &lt;http://mylearn.vmware.com/mgrreg/courses.cfm?ui=www_edu&amp;a=one&amp;id_subject=17750&gt;

Enterprise Integration &lt;http://mylearn.vmware.com/mgrreg/courses.cfm?ui=www_edu&amp;a=one&amp;id_subject=17833&gt;

Hibernate with Spring &lt;http://mylearn.vmware.com/mgrreg/courses.cfm?ui=www_edu&amp;a=one&amp;id_subject=18355&gt;

Rich Web Applications &lt;http://mylearn.vmware.com/mgrreg/courses.cfm?ui=www_edu&amp;a=one&amp;id_subject=17834&gt;

Groovy and Grails &lt;http://mylearn.vmware.com/mgrreg/courses.cfm?ui=www_edu&amp;a=one&amp;id_subject=41320&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
