<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.06-29-15 Enablement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Net New Enablement Team and Education Renewal</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

I’m very pleased to announce the following organizational changes and promotions, designed to continue our great progress in scaling and improving our field productivity and operational efficiency.

Chris Braney 
has been promoted to lead the Global Business Management Team that is responsible for sales forecast management, sales productivity and pipeline metrics, and the profitability of GEO sales teams. His team includes David Lo in APJ, Ian Bignell in EMEA, and Chris Want in the Americas.

Eric Landon will expand his role, leading a new group called Field Reporting, Analytics and Tools. This group will include the Deal Desk, where Eric will continue to have hands-on role managing it, with Ian Manter and Jessica Whitford. Jayme Kachadurian, Eddie Zuniga, and Sina Vaziri will form the Reporting and Analytics team, while Christine Lewicki, and Deb Weller remain focused on Field Tools, including Salesforce and Zuora. This combined group will use data-driven, innovative sales tools, such as the recently launched Customer Info App &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/document/d/1QF8uLKO9P_zrs0HZgszyM1ZdsZ-njFCu1URqL4vp-V8/edit?usp=sharing&gt;, to improve deal velocity and provide insights that will help guide sales strategy.

Kelli Robinson, currently leading the Toronto-based Sales Productivity team, will expand her team’s charter to standardize how customers interact with us, from proposals through 
customer visits, and includes our EBC efforts. Brian Wilson will report into Kelli and continue to lead our Federation EBC program in Palo Alto, as Kelli and her team ensure that our sales assets and messages are aligned concise, polished, and consistent.

These key organizational changes are designed to help us 
collaborate and support the Field by improving sales efficiency, velocity and productivity, and will take effect in Q3. The new groups will report into Greg Stroud, who runs our overall Sales Operations and who continues to report into me. 

Please take a moment to congratulate our colleagues in their new, expanded roles, and feel free to reach out to myself or Greg with any questions. 

Best,

Todd Paoletti
VP, Global Strategy &amp; Operations</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
