<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.August 24 2018 Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal 5-Point Friday</subject>
    <textOnly>August 24, 2018

Hello, I’m Michael. I seriously enjoy being a part of a world in the act of changing, which is why I find great satisfaction in working with our partner and customer, Dell. What makes Dell so unique is that they are simultaneously a financial institution, a retailer with a massive supply chain, and a tremendous go to market partner helping to drive the digital transformation message into our customer base. Dell/EMC was already a consumer of the Pivotal Cloud Foundry platform supporting IT, but roughly 2 years ago, we started a journey to help Dell change its software development culture, resulting in establishing a Pivotal Labs presence inside of Dell’s corporate headquarters in Round Rock. Over the course of the past year, stunning joint success has delivered value for both Dell and Dell’s customers.

 


 



 


 


1. Pivotal Steps into India to Train Partners, for the First Time


The Platform Acceleration Lab (PAL) is a dedicated facility in Boulder, CO where partner software developers are immersed in a three-week application replatforming course. The PAL curriculum was developed by Pivotal consultants and emphasizes “learning by doing.” Jointly with Dell, Pivotal has opened a PAL to train joint customers in India. Thanks to Nick Cayou and Mike Barinek&apos;s leadership in making it happen.

Also in India, a new Dell Pivotal Lab is about to launch. A seed APJ team is currently in Round Rock pairing with Pivotal Labs to get trained up to support Dell’s commerce efforts globally.

If your customers use .Net let them know about our classes: Pivotal.Io/Platform-Acceleration-Lab &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform-acceleration-lab]]&gt;

 


 



 


 


2. Dell.com’s Personalization Drives New Direction through Labs 

The Dell Personalization team (P13N) worked closely with Pivotal Labs to deliver new value to help customize customer product search on Dell.com. Replacing ‘waterfall’ with ‘agile’ methodology required a whole new work culture &lt;[[https://drive.google.com/file/d/12on9B0fe3nb3gS3QFoYTxMSjYNoGq_Ae/view]]&gt;. The team deeply learned user problems before building/testing on Dell.com and successfully launched the first MVP (minimum viable product) on a small % of traffic to test the solution for scalability. 
After 3 prototype iterations, a surge in positive feedback came from both users and business stakeholders, validating the new design. This process improves customer outcomes rapidly, enabling Dell.com to identify new revenue opportunities with significantly faster turnaround.


 


 



 


 

3. Dell.com Leaps Forward on Pivotal Cloud Foundry

Dell.com’s first tier 1, customer-facing, revenue generating application, the Configurator &lt;[[http://www.dell.com/content/topics/topic.aspx/us/segments/bsd/services/quickship-laptop-latitude-e5500?c=us&amp;l=en&amp;cs=04]]&gt; has launched via Pivotal Cloud Foundry (PCF) 
with astounding results! This feature first launched on Dell.com to UK traffic and was so successful, it will scale to the United States in the next wave of deployment.

Pivotal Labs agile method around balanced teams, cloud-native development, and microservices, enabled the Dell.com team to realize an increase in revenue per visit, improvements in speed and reliability, and a newfound ability to quickly iterate. Even Bask Iyer was quoted by Forbes &lt;[[https://www.forbes.com/sites/peterhigh/2018/08/06/simultaneously-the-cio-and-cdo-of-dell-and-vmware-bask-iyer-does-it-all/#1938a8bf6654]]&gt; saying “With the help of Pivotal, we created the Dell Digital Way. This is an incorporation of the best practices of agile, CI/CD, and pair programming.”

 


 



 


 


4. Dell has an Alexa skill … Voice Recognition for shoppers! 


Experiments are being conducted to build Dell Assisted Voice Interface (DAVI for short), a new voice assistant. The goal is to improve responsiveness to customer needs and product support. Working in a Labs-style balanced team, DAVI &lt;[[https://www.amazon.com/Dell-Technologies/dp/B07GJL7RZ7/ref=sr_1_1?s=digital-skills&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1534781920&amp;sr=1-1&amp;ketwords=dell]]&gt; launched into production in less than 14 weeks.


 


 



 


 


5. Executive Briefings Drive Opportunity 


One of the aspects I love about this role is the opportunity to support the EBC program, evangelizing digital transformation, and highlighting the successes we’ve discovered on the ground at Dell. Real opportunity has bubbled out of these efforts, with new revenue from accounts like the Secretary General of Canada and Sealed Air. To unlock the mystery, see the message I deliver and steal all the best ideas for your next customer presentation. For thoughts about the impact of digital transformation on humans, read my blog: Abitcloudy.Me &lt;[[https://abitcloudy.me]]&gt;.

 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/_0PVIEQnsaY]]&gt;





Michael Wood, Director of Alliances
Blog: Abitcloudy.Me &lt;[[https://abitcloudy.me]]&gt;

 


 






 
 
 


 


Upcoming Events

VMworld 2018 US &lt;[[https://www.vmworld.com/en/us/learning/tracks.html]]&gt; Aug 26-30 
Going to VMworld?  Here&apos;s your Complete Guide, Pivotal Style​ &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/going-to-vmworld-2018-heres-your-complete-guide-to-the-event-pivotal-style]]&gt; 
 SpringOne Platform &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/]]&gt; Sept 24-27 
20% Discount Code: S1P_SPON_DELLEMC20
Discount Code: S1P_SPON_VMWARE20 
VMware PKS Workshop Schedule &lt;[[http://pages.cloud.vmware.com/PKSWorkshop2018]]&gt; 
Seattle: Aug 7; Portland: Aug 9; NYC: Sept 6; Paris: Sept 11; Israel: Oct 9; Austin: Oct 11 
Pivotal PreSales 
Bootcamps 
Calgary &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01406279]]&gt;: Sept 11; Rome &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01404196]]&gt;: Sept 12; Milan &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01404198]]&gt; / Indianapolis &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01406908]]&gt;: Sept 13; Copenhagen &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01406957]]&gt;: Sept 18; Stockholm &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01404135]]&gt;: Sept 19; Brentford &lt;[[https://dell.sabacloud.com/Saba/Web_spf/PRODTNT091/common/leclassview/class-01406909]]&gt;: Oct 3

Digital Knowledge

Website: Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx]]&gt;, designed exclusively for Dell Tech
Webex: Pivotal Learning Series &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSc6Km9Ifg5-74OBRjRYjEVSN0fs9Mps-mE-g2h9bExFC32fYQ/viewform?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0RjM09XTTRNVFEyTnpGbCIsInQiOiJMXC9zcXBPSG1Zd1loRzcwZXF0YW5kN0JSTXpmaGZPV0hqVmdDdHVkMUVSMmpHV3VKWWNqV2t6Rm10NW84Zk44RURmUHVOU3UrSjl2K1Y2Y3ZLQ2lsVVE9PSJ9]]&gt;
Webex: Pivotal Power Hour featuring PRA &lt;[[https://emccorp.webex.com/emccorp/lsr.php?RCID=d74572be3f3e469ea1687dfc4fbfbe59]]&gt;
Blog: Pivotal Ready Architecture, The Easy Button for PCF &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/say-hello-to-pivotal-ready-architecture-from-dell-emc-the-easy-button-for-pivotal-cloud-foundry-in-your-data-center]]&gt;
Chad Sakac’s Blog: KNative + Riff + Google + Pivotal = PFS, 
What’s this about? &lt;[[http://virtualgeek.io/knative-riff-google-pivotal-pfs-whats-this-all-about/]]&gt;

 


 






 
 
 


 




Michael Wood, Director of 
Alliances


AskDellTEch@Pivotal.Io</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
