<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Advertising Lead Gen - Q117.Invite to Advertising Leads - 4/19/17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>ICYMI - We just released a Pivotal Cloud Foundry product update</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 
Did you know we just launched Pivotal Cloud Foundry 1.10? And it’s pretty amazing if we do say so ourselves. 
 
If you aren’t already familiar, Pivotal Cloud Foundry is a software platform that helps your teams focus on the activities that drive business value, by handling infrastructure, OS patching, and container orchestration for you. The platform’s built-in tools are perfect for scaling, metrics, microservice patterns, and modern stream processing. Like our customers, you too can use Pivotal Cloud Foundry to go from idea to production in hours, not months. 
 
If you would like to learn more about Pivotal Cloud Foundry or Pivotal, feel free to download one of our many complimentary eBooks &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/ebooks?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q1-2017-promo]]&gt;, like Embarking On The Cloud-Native Journey To More Agile IT &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/ebooks/embarking-on-the-cloud-native-journey-to-more-agile-it?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q1-2017-promo]]&gt;. 
 
If you wanted to get into the nitty-gritty of this technology stack immediately and deploy a sample application for yourself, please visit pivotal.io/platform &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q1-2017-promo]]&gt;.
 
To stay up-to-date with everything Pivotal, we recommend signing-up &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/newsletter-subscription?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=q1-2017-promo]]&gt; to receive our weekly newsletter. 
 
Thank you,
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
