<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ImaPivotNewsletter.2017-06-27</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Machine learning myths, test doubling, and remixing the design sprint</subject>
    <textOnly>From Tokyo to Atlanta, this month&apos;s newsletter features articles that explore different approaches to product design, explanations behind test doubling, myths about machine learning, the return of an award-winning game, and more.







1




Ten Myths About Machine Learning &lt;[[https://medium.com/@pedromdd/ten-myths-about-machine-learning-d888b48334a3]]&gt;
There are a lot of Machine Learning myths out there. Pedro Domingos dispels ten of them.



















2




Walking Through Design in Tokyo &lt;[[https://uxdesign.cc/walking-through-design-in-tokyo-d6f00a4639b7]]&gt;
Learn how applying UX principles to pedestrian navigation can improve rush hour.



















3




Five Factor Testing &lt;[[https://www.devmynd.com/blog/five-factor-testing/]]&gt;
Former Pivot Sarah Mei talks about the five practical reasons why we write tests.



















4




A Design Sprint for Good(r) &lt;[[https://builttoadapt.io/a-design-sprint-for-good-r-1e93563e18da]]&gt;
The Pivotal team in Atlanta decided to put a Pivotal spin on Google&apos;s Design Sprint exercise.



















5




Getting Started with Apple&apos;s Business Chat API &lt;[[https://developer.apple.com/library/content/documentation/General/Conceptual/MessagesIntegration/index.html]]&gt;
Many new features were announced at WWDC this year, but this one didn&apos;t make it in the keynote for time. It begins to open up iMessage as a platform, connecting businesses to their customers.





















6




The Test Double Rule of Thumb &lt;[[http://engineering.pivotal.io/post/the-test-double-rule-of-thumb/]]&gt;
&quot;Test Driven Development (TDD) is a practice that seems simple in concept, yet often proves challenging in practice. Perhaps you’ve recently started learning TDD, and you’re ready to move beyond the simple examples of testing a class with no collaborators. This post will introduce you to &apos;doubling&apos; – a practice you’ll find essential when testing your real world code.&quot;





















7




Designing for VR &lt;[[https://medium.com/@blakehudelson/designing-for-vr-a-beginners-guide-d2fe37902146]]&gt;
Get oriented with the processes, tools, and principles of creating VR experiences.





















8




Behind the scenes of Monument Valley 2 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/6gzygG3MTgk]]&gt;
The award winning mobile game is back. Watch this video about the ustwo team and how they came up with the story and developed ideas around story and visuals for this magnificent sequel.





















9




BuzzFeed&apos;s Design Roles &lt;[[https://medium.com/buzzfeed-design/product-design-roles-v3-c97a061a4b33]]&gt;
BuzzFeed cleared up the language and processes around the design practice. They cover the roles they have, how they handle promotion, and the common vocabulary they use. 





















10




Machine Learning Evolution (Infographic) &lt;[[http://usblogs.pwc.com/emerging-technology/machine-learning-evolution-infographic/]]&gt;
Check out PWC&apos;s infographic showing the evolution of machine learning.



















11




The Space Debris Apocalypse &lt;[[https://youtu.be/lQQk9XqTMAY]]&gt;
Hear how one young engineer used neural networks to help space stations avoid debris.
The Home Depot · Mobile Product Manager, Atlanta, GA &lt;[[https://careers.homedepot.com/job/6944525/manager-product-management-mobile-applications-atlanta-ga/]]&gt;
 
 Comcast · Principal Software Engineer, Philadelphia, PA &lt;[[https://jobs.comcast.com/job-162406-principal-software-engineer-in-philadelphia-pa-technology-software-engineering]]&gt;
 
 Vineti · Product Designer, San Francisco, CA &lt;[[https://jobs.lever.co/vineti/6a69d2e7-00fe-4730-a89d-70589ce926f8]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
