<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>External Newsletter.10-20-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>PCF on Google Cloud, Liberty Mutual&apos;s Journey, and Women in Leadership</subject>
    <textOnly>OCTOBER 20, 2016
&lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/7-ways-pivotal-and-google-simplify-cloud-native-for-the-enterprise]]&gt;
PCF Now Available on Google Cloud Platform
Pivotal Cloud Foundry is now generally available to run on Google Cloud Platform (GCP). Now enterprises can build, deploy, and run cloud-native apps on the same infrastructure that powers Google Search, Google Maps and YouTube. PCF deployments can be enhanced and extended with Google’s data products (like BigQuery and the Cloud Machine Learning platform).
Learn More &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/7-ways-pivotal-and-google-simplify-cloud-native-for-the-enterprise]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://pivotal.io/liberty-mutual]]&gt;
Developing the Technology to Keep Up with Evolving Risk Models
Learn more about Liberty Mutual&apos;s journey to disrupt the insurance industry from the company’s CIO James McGlennon.
Check It Out &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/liberty-mutual]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-insights/features/breaking-down-the-wall-between-developers-and-data-pros]]&gt;
Breaking Down the Wall Between Developers and Data Pros
In this Pivotal Insights episode, host Jeff Kelly talks with Pivotal’s Jacque Istok, who runs Pivotal’s data engineering and data science field organization, about how to break down the wall between application developers and data professionals. The two also discuss the concept of balanced teams to support data analytics projects.
Listen To The Episode &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-insights/features/breaking-down-the-wall-between-developers-and-data-pros]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SDIV8XV6Qrg]]&gt;
Women in Leadership
Janice Fraser sums up all the research about women’s career development in one handy diagram.
Watch Now &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SDIV8XV6Qrg]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/new-in-spring-cloud-services-1-2-multi-site-service-discovery]]&gt;
New in Spring Cloud Services 1.2: Multi-Site Service Discovery
With Spring Cloud Services 1.2, operators can configure peer replication of Service Registry service instances. Now, when an application registers with a Service Registry instance, that same application is available for lookup by consumers in a PCF installation in another data center, or across organizations within a single PCF installation.
Learn More &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/new-in-spring-cloud-services-1-2-multi-site-service-discovery]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xLxfVheByE]]&gt;
Establishing Technology as a Core Competency at Allstate
Opal Perry of Allstate explains more about how the insurance giant is building new applications that are evolutions of their core business, and modernizing decades of legacy investment. She also address best practices to organizational change management and real experiences in successful technical collaboration across the globe.
Watch Now &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xLxfVheByE]]&gt;
Upcoming Events
10/24 Molina Healthcare Drives Efficiency with Hadoop Native SQL Analytics, Online &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/drive-operational-it-efficiency-with-hadoop-native-sql-analytics]]&gt;


10/27 API Technology Forum, Dallas &lt;[[http://apigee.com/api-management/#/atf_eventdetail/125]]&gt;


10/27 Coud Native Road Show, Atlanta &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/event/pivotal-cloud-native-roadshow/atlanta]]&gt;


11/1 Digital Transformation Forum, Dubai &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/event/digital-transformation-forum/dubai]]&gt;


11/1 Future of Data Roadshow, Seoul &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/event/future-of-data/]]&gt;


11/2 Cloud Native Workshop, Kansas City &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/event/cloud-native-workshop/kansas-city]]&gt;


Check out Upcoming Pivotal Education Courses &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/academy]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
