<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_SpringOne_Platform_2019.S1P Apache Geode - 3/26/19</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Submit your Geode Summit 2019 session proposals, register to attend</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-geode-email-q119]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}}, 

It’s back! The fourth Geode Summit is coming your way this October. As with prior years, this year’s Geode Summit will be held in conjunction with SpringOne Platform &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-geode-email-q119]]&gt;, which takes place in Austin, TX from Oct 7–10, 2019.
Call for proposals is now open
Want to share your story? Submit your talk &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/2019/cfp?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-geode-email-q119]]&gt; by April 12, 2019 at 11:59pm (PDT)—just indicate Geode as the topic when you make your submission. This is a great opportunity to share your Geode knowledge, success stories, and best practices. Need a little inspiration? Check out the videos from past Geode Summits (2018 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL62pIycqXx-ShuJ1YpV2wlmNZodnqzY8T]]&gt;, 2017 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL62pIycqXx-QfmNrUmfKoTZXKU5K90JpK]]&gt;, and 2016 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL62pIycqXx-RCEP2APj4Mq9Oeyvskj_0K]]&gt;).
Register now and save
Join us for a half day of Geode-only sessions on the first day of the conference (Mon, Oct 7, 1–6pm), followed by a number of Geode sessions Tue–Thu. There are two ways to register:
1) A full conference registration entitles you to attend any of the Geode sessions, including the half-day Geode block on Monday, Oct 7. (The full conference pass prices do go up over time, so it&apos;s important to register early.) In addition to the early bird discount, you can use discount code S1P200_JMirani for an extra $200 off your pass. That’s a savings of $800 off the full conference pass if you register by April 24, 2019 at 11:59pm (PDT).
2) For those who only want to attend the Monday Geode sessions, select the reduced-price Monday-only option.
Register now and save. &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/register?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-geode-email-q119]]&gt;
I hope to see you in Austin this fall!
Regards,
Jag</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
