<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Email_Spring_Monthly_Newsletter.OSS_Email_Spring_Event_SpringOne2GX_8-6-13 D</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Hurry, SpringOne 2GX early bird pricing expires Aug 9, 2013</subject>
    <textOnly>SPRINGONE 2GX 2013 EARLY BIRD EXPIRES 8/9!
REGISTER TODAY http://www.gopivotal.com 

GET THE $200.00 EARLY BIRD DISCOUNT - expires 8/9/2013! http://springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/register

Pivotal http://www.gopivotal.com/, in conjunction with the No Fluff Just Stuff Symposium Series, is pleased to present SpringOne 2GX, the premier Java event of 2013. SpringOne 2GX is a collocated event covering the entire Spring ecosystem as well as Groovy, Grails, Big Data and the Cloud. The conference will be held in Santa Clara, CA, September 9-12, 2013 at the Santa Clara Convention Center. http://springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/home

NEW EVENT ADDED!
All registrants now have free access to Platform: The Cloud Foundry Event (Sep 8-9, 2013) http://www.platformcf.com. 

WIN A FREE PASS TO SPRINGONE 2GX!
 Show us how you champion Cloud Foundry http://www.bit.ly/cfchampathon to enter! If you win a SpringOne 2GX 2013 pass, you get into Platform for free, as long as you register in time.

 SESSION SPOTLIGHT:
 Zero Effort Spring
 Dave Syer &amp; Phil Webb
https://springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/session?id=29409

Register Now! &lt;http://springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/register&gt;
NEW SESSIONS ADDED!

CHECK OUR WEBSITE http://www.springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/springone/event_schedule for speaker and session updates. If you&apos;d like to get a feel for the type of content at the show, watch some of the 2012 conference sessions on YouTube! https://springone2gx.com/conference/washington/2012/10/video_list
 
 This is a one-of-a-kind conference for 
application developers, solution and data architects who develop business applications, create multi-device aware web applications, process vast quantities of enterprise data, design cloud architectures, and manage high performance infrastructure. The sessions are specifically tailored for developers using the open source Spring, Groovy/Grails, and Cloud Foundry technologies. Whether you&apos;re building and running mission-critical business applications, crunching huge piles of distributed data, or designing the next killer cloud application, SpringOne 2GX will keep you up to date with the latest enterprise technology.
 
 Featuring presentations delivered by development leads and published authors on the Spring, Groovy/Grails, Cloud and Big Data technology, it&apos;s the ideal place to obtain critical skills to help you design, build and run tomorrow&apos;s software solutions. Plus you&apos;ll meet and learn from open source leaders who drive innovation for these technologies.
 
 REGISTER TODAY FOR THE EARLY BIRD RATE!
http://springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/register

 Looking forward to a great conference.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
