<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>May Digest 2017.PCF Email send 5-3-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>May Webinars - Security Strategies, Cloud-Native, Reducing Production Risks and PostgreSQL</subject>
    <textOnly>May 3, 2017
&lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;


Strategies on How to Overcome Security Challenges Unique to Cloud-Native Apps
Zane Lackey, Signal Sciences and KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL
May 3, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Learn how Pivotal and Signal Sciences can improve your security posture in cloud-native environments, so you can deliver apps more quickly and safely. The webinar features Zane Lackey, CSO at Signal Sciences, a frequent speaker at top industry conferences, an author and lecturer.

Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/strategies-on-how-to-overcome-security-challenges-unique-to-cloud-native-apps?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=signalsciences-security-kd_q217]]&gt;

Journey to Cloud-Native: Making Sense of Your Service Interactions
KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL AND MIKE VILLIGER, DYNATRACE
may 16, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Join this session to learn how teams are overcoming the complexity in operational data that often makes root cause analysis challenging by applying automatic application-environment discovery, service and process flows integration and self healing platforms.

Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/journey-to-cloud-native-making-sense-of-your-service-interactions?utm_source=dynatrace-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-appdev-part3_q217]]&gt;

How to Configure PostgreSQL Consistent with Modern Security Best Practices
KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL AND jason o&apos;donnell, crunchy data
may 23, 2017  11:00am PDT / 2:00pm EDT

Join this session to learn how to configure PostgreSQL consistent with security best practices, get on-demand, self-service access to certified open source PostgreSQL, leverage built-in security and resilience of cloud-native environments to reduce risk. 

Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/how-to-configure-postgresql-consistent-with-modern-security-best-practices?utm_source=pivotal-digest&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=crunchy-postgresql-security_q217]]&gt;

Journey to Cloud-Native: Reducing Production Risks at Scale
KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL AND MIKE VILLIGER, DYNATRACE
june 7, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Join this session to learn how to auto-detect apps and services running on multiple clouds, automate problem detection and resolution, identify behavior patters, anticipate trends and respond quickly and learn why correlation is not causation.

Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/journey-to-cloud-native-reducing-production-risks-at-scale?utm_source=pivotal-digest&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-appdev-part4_q217]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
