<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Spring Days_Q217.1 Chicago Reminder</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See you tomorrow at Spring Days Chicago</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.springdays.io]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 
 We look forward to seeing you tomorrow at Spring Days Chicago. Please review the event details below and feel free to email the team at springdays@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:springdays@pivotal.io]]&gt; with any questions.
 
Spring Days - Chicago 
 
May 30th
7:45am: Doors Open
8:00am-8:45am: Breakfast/ Registration  
9:00am-1:00pm: Sessions
1:00pm-2:00pm: Lunch
2:00pm-5:00pm: Open Space 
5:00pm: Networking &amp; Social @ River Roast Restaurant &lt;[[http://riverroastchicago.com/]]&gt;
 
May 31st
7:45am: Doors Open
8:00am-8:45am: Breakfast/ Registration  
9:00am-1:00pm: Sessions
1:00pm-2:00pm: Lunch

2:00pm-5:00pm: Open Space 
5:00pm: Wrap-up
 
See the full Spring Days - Chicago Agenda here &lt;[[https://www.springdays.io/ehome/spring-days/chicago]]&gt;.
Location
1871 is located on the 12th floor of the Merchandise Mart. There is a large neon 1871 sign at the end of the hall.
 
Address: 
222 W. Merchandise Mart, Suite 1212
Chicago IL, 60654
 
Parking
Luxe Valet can meet you at The Merchandise Mart and valet park your car (they can even wash and fuel it!) and will return it whenever you are ready to leave. Download the Luxe App on iOS or Android. Enter promo code &quot;1871Guest&quot; under Payment for one free park ($15 credit) at The Merchandise Mart. 
 
SpotHero can help you secure and pay for a parking spot in advance, usually at a discounted cost. Download the SpotHero appon iOS or Android to get started.
 
Self-park at the 210 N. Wells lot and validate your ticket at 1871 for discounted rates.
$8.00 – Monday – Friday: enter between 3:00pm – 11:59pm, out by 8:00am
 
Garage Entrance:
Entrances are located on Wells Street and Post Place (between Franklin Street and Wells Street).
Enter 210 N. Wells Self-Park and pull a “timed” ticket to lift the gate and park your vehicle.
Take your parking ticket with you for validation at 1871 reception.
 
For any questions regarding parking at 210 N. Wells Self-Park, please contact info@210nwells.com or (312) 263 -1535.
 
We look forward to seeing you!
The Spring Days Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
