<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Webinar_Pivotal and Alpine Chorus_Q316.Invite 9-6-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Creating Smarter Applications: Pivotal Cloud Foundry + Chorus</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://alpinedata.com/cloud-foundry-and-chorus-webinar/]]&gt;

Hello {{lead.First Name:default=there}}, 

Join Richard Seroter of Pivotal and Lawrence Spracklen of Alpine Data on Wednesday, September 14, for a dynamic discussion and a live demo &lt;[[http://alpinedata.com/cloud-foundry-and-chorus-webinar/]]&gt; of how our new collaboration will help close the gap between data science insights and business value. 

 Pivotal Cloud Foundry and Chorus from Alpine make it easy to build machine learning projects and deploy them to a scalable platform. This partnership makes it possible for data science teams to work seamlessly with I.T. and line of business users as they design and iterate on intelligent scoring engines. Working on top of Pivotal’s Big Data Suite, the joint solution provides organizations with a toolkit for discovering deep insights into your data and turning it into action. 

 In this webinar &lt;[[http://alpinedata.com/cloud-foundry-and-chorus-webinar/]]&gt; you will learn:

 - How to deploy intelligent applications with Alpine Data Chorus and Pivotal Cloud Foundry  
 - How the joint solution between Chorus and Pivotal can expedite the process of building scoring engines around your models

 Speakers: 
Richard Seroter, Senior Director of Product, Pivotal 
Lawrence Spracklen, VP Engineering, Alpine Data 

 Event Details: 
September 14, 2016 10:00am PDT/1:00pm EDT
 
Register Here &lt;[[http://alpinedata.com/cloud-foundry-and-chorus-webinar/]]&gt;

We look forward to you joining us. 

 Kind regards, 
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
