<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.02-11-16 CDavis</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>A Message from The Diversity Council</subject>
    <textOnly>Wow! We’ve kicked off the year with tremendous energy around Diversity and Inclusion at Pivotal! While everybody agrees that diversity and inclusion is important, we’re hard pressed as an industry to show meaningful examples of this at work.

Following the presentation that Cornelia gave at WWKO, a huge number of you have asked or wondered, &quot;How can I help?&quot; It got many people very excited, but it also raised questions that prompted a discussion between the Diversity Council and the Pivotal leadership around the shared responsibility between leaders and individuals in becoming a more diverse and inclusive workplace.

What’s clear, and what our leadership supports, is that we as individuals can take grassroots action to get us closer to a shared vision—actions that can have a meaningful impact in the tech industry. With that, we&apos;d love to share some ideas and ways that you can get involved:


 - Grass roots diversity activities kicked off the week of January 25, with meetings in Asia Pacific, Europe and North America. Pivotal offices around the world are self-organizing teams of D&amp;I enthusiasts. They’re working on plans for activities to engage in and teams will share their ideas and plans with each other. We encourage you to seek out others in your office to form or join one of these grass roots diversity groups—the more diverse teams are, the better their results. Please reach out to Hamish Cook (hcook@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:hcook@pivotal.io]]&gt;) or Chelsea Troy (ctroy@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:ctroy@pivotal.io]]&gt;) for any guidance or support on where to start.
 - Join the #diversity &lt;[[https://pivotal.slack.com/messages/diversity/details/]]&gt; channel on slack. The channel is lively, with thought-provoking discussions and links posted every day. Share your ideas, and pick up new ones. For example, Jay Badenhope had an awesome idea of &quot;coding playdates.&quot;
 - Many of you asked how you can help with the Girls Who Code Summer Immersion program in Palo Alto. We’re in the early stages of planning, but know that we will absolutely need a large number of mentors, and help with other things. If you wish to get on our volunteer list, please, send an email to Zach Larson and Heather Ferguson—and discuss this with your manager first to secure the required time away from billable or project work. Specifically, we’ll need 10–20 female designers, developers, product managers, and executives. Each person will need to commit two to three hours of their time on one to two sessions over the seven week period, and should be excited and passionate about this project.
 - View the video on unconscious bias &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nLjFTHTgEVU]]&gt;, and think about ways of compensating for bias. The Platform Architecture team, for example, has already begun reviewing and updating their job descriptions. So awesome!



Look out for a CODE &lt;[[http://www.codedocumentary.com/]]&gt; screening in an office near you &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/departments/human-resources/diversity-inclusion/events]]&gt;.

The Diversity Council is here to help people get more involved. Engagement from and for our employees matters, and goes a long way in creating a more dynamic, productive and joyful workplace.

We’ve never been more excited about diversity and inclusion at Pivotal, and how together, we can do amazing things.

Warmest regards,

Abby, Cookie, Cornelia, David, Elisabeth, Guillermo, Heather, Janice, Joe, Lan, Magda, Maria &amp; Onsi</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
