<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>cloned from Nov 30 2018 newsletter</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.013 December 14 2018 News</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal 5-Point Friday</subject>
    <textOnly>December 14, 2018

Hey! I’m Melanie McElligott, a proud member of the Dell Tech tribe for (ahem) 19 years spending time in Dell, VMware, and now Pivotal as part of the new Dell Synergy Sales Team covering the Northeast and Mid Atlantic. I work with the joint SAB teams driving digital transformation opportunities with a focus on Pivotal Ready Architecture adoption for our joint customers.  Enjoy this special “Retail Edition” of 5 Point Friday.

 


 



 


 

1. PCF Customers Say “Happy Black Fri-YAY!”

While many retailers struggled with Black Friday/Cyber Monday e-commerce outages (J.Crew, Ulta, Lowe’s), Pivotal customers Home Depot, the GAP and Dick’s Sporting Goods were all smiles as PCF flexed its muscles and kept them up and running on one of the busiest shopping days of the year.

Industry experts reckon that these retailers could have avoided outages by &quot;having a layer of management software in the development pipeline so DevOps teams have more control and oversight into their systems. DevOps processes can be broken down into seven steps including build, test, deploy, run, monitor, manage and notify.&quot; says Samantha Ann Schwartz from CIO Dive &lt;[[https://www.ciodive.com/news/black-friday-traffic-brings-down-j-crew-ulta-sites-among-other-retailers/542926/]]&gt;. Hmmm..where have I heard that before? Oh yeah, that’s what Pivotal Cloud Foundry does!

Dick’s, a Black Friday winner, is leveraging PCF as part of their adoption of a product driven digital culture that’s delivering some amazing outcomes including scalability and stability. See their interview here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/videos/dick-s-sporting-goods-adopts-the-rituals-of-a-product-driven-digital-culture]]&gt;.


 


 



 


 


2. Better Software = Happy Customers (and employees) 


Did you know that Pivotal has worked with 8 of the largest retailers on their digital transformation? Forrester &lt;[[https://www.forrester.com/report/Building+The+Integrated+Retail+Commerce+Business+Case/-/E-RES91341?objectid=RES91341]]&gt; says the secret of success for retailers 
who survive the Amazon effect will be their ability to create an integrated, seamless experience for consumers - we agree.

Retailers need to “support new types of purchasing behaviors such as buy-online, pick-up-in-store, and a more self-service experience inside the store. When they do need help finding something, they want employees to be able to deliver those answers quickly and accurately” says Derrick Harris, Principal Product Marketing Manager at Pivotal in his latest blog post &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/how-pivotal-is-helping-retailers-improve-the-in-store-experience-through-better-software]]&gt;.

Harris highlights use cases demonstrating how Pivotal helped Kroger &lt;[[https://builttoadapt.io/data-in-aisle-3-b53e619e7939]]&gt;, Home Depot &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bl0oH0UdJPM#action=share]]&gt;, 
the Gap, Dick’s Sporting Goods and T-Mobile build well-designed applications that meet customer expectations again and again, make employees more efficient and keep better controls over inventory.

Learn more about Pivotal Digital Transformation solutions and use cases for Retail at Pivotal.Io/industries/retail &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/industries/retail]]&gt;

 


 



 


 


3. United [Store]Front at NRF’s BIG SHOW

The Dell Technologies, VMware, Pivotal and Boomi family is teaming up at the National Retail Federation’s Big Show, the largest retail trade show in the world, this January in NYC. Over 16,000 attendees representing over 7,500 retailers will be on hand to talk about the latest trends and technology driving their business. If you have a retail customer who will be there - make sure to:



	- Set up onsite exec meetings with retail experts from Pivotal, VMware, Boomi and Dell Technologies using the Jifflenow tool &lt;[[https://emc.jifflenow.com/portal?return_url=https%3A%2F%2Femc.jifflenow.com%2Fnrf2019%2F]]&gt;.

	- Invite them to an executive dinner with top Pivotal customers at one of NYC’s hottest restaurants Del Posto on Monday, January 14th. Contact Jamie De Martini &lt;[[mailto:jdemartini@pivotal.io]]&gt; for more information.

	- Visit VMware booth #1057 to see demos of Dell Tech solutions - VMware Promo Code 604 for 20% off full passes for customers.

	- Tell them about the Dell Tech Panel discussion “Modernize Retail IT to Deliver Exceptional Customer Experiences in the Intelligent Store” on Sunday, January 13th from 4:00PM to 4:30PM - Stage 6, EXPO Hall, Level 3 with Host Kyle Dufresne, President &amp; General Manager GCCS, Dell Technologies.




Contact Michelle Scobie &lt;[[mailto:Michelle.Scobie@dell.com]]&gt; at Dell for more information on the show.


 


 



 


 


4. $2.3M Win Announcement: AutoZone Hits the Gas to Deploy Apps Faster


Congratulations to our latest Pivotal customer AutoZone! Headquartered in Memphis, TN, Autozone is the leading retailer and distributor of automotive replacement parts and accessories. This was a $2.3M Pivotal software win for both PAS and PKS.

To capture commercial customers (ex: car dealership service centers) as part of their “Commercial Acceleration” strategy, Autozone partnered with Pivotal, changing their software Deployment and Ops process, to move faster and capitalize on this new market opportunity ahead of the competition. On their first “putt” with Pivotal they were able to deliver 5 new applications in 3 months - now that’s what I call putting your foot on the gas!

Listen to the Podcast with James Thibadeau, Pivotal Account Executive on the Autozone PKS Win &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pks-win-at-autozone-with-james-thibadeau-pivotal/s-hWXES]]&gt;.
Congratulations to the Pivotal team led by James Thibadeau on this great win.
 &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pks-win-at-autozone-with-james-thibadeau-pivotal/s-hWXES]]&gt;

 


 



 


 

5. The k8s Struggle is REAL… unless you’re a PKS customer!

On it’s first real vulnerability test, PKS proved that addressing critical updates quickly and effectively is where we really shine. Last week Google announced that the first major security hole or CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures) for Kubernetes (k8s) was discovered and fixing it requires users to upgrade to a new version of Kubernetes IMMEDIATELY. Fortunately for PKS customers, this is no big deal, thanks to BOSH and its ability to support zero downtime upgrades. In fact, PKS customers using PivNet had everything they needed to patch and upgrade their environment BEFORE the vulnerability was even announced! VMware PKS was the first to address and remediate following Google, the creator of Kubernetes.
 &lt;[[https://twitter.com/odedia/status/1072228525002903552]]&gt;

Customers are STILL asking why they need an enterprise-level Kubernetes management system? Show them these blog posts:


	- Happy Monday: How To Fix A Kubernetes CVE Before Bad Actors (And Your Boss) Discover It &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/happy-monday-how-to-fix-a-kubernetes-cve-before-your-boss-and-the-rest-of-the-world-reads-about-it]]&gt; by John Allright

	- PKS 1.2.3 release – and Kubernetes CVE-2018-1002105 &lt;[[https://virtualgeek.io/pks-1-2-3-release-and-kubernetes-cve-2018-1002105/]]&gt; by Chad Sakac
	- Pivotal&apos;s customer friendly site on PKS &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform/pivotal-container-service]]&gt;



- Melanie McElligott

 









 
 
 


 


Upcoming Events


	- National Retail Federation Big Show: &lt;[[https://nrfbigshow.nrf.com/?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIzLyjyoqW3wIVEF8NCh3X8gZUEAAYASAAEgImdvD_BwE]]&gt; New York, NY Jan 13-15 2019



Digital Knowledge


	- Pivotal Pulse Podcast: PKS Win at Autozone &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988]]&gt;
	- Webex: Pivotal 
Learning Series &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSc6Km9Ifg5-74OBRjRYjEVSN0fs9Mps-mE-g2h9bExFC32fYQ/viewform?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0RjM09XTTRNVFEyTnpGbCIsInQiOiJMXC9zcXBPSG1Zd1loRzcwZXF0YW5kN0JSTXpmaGZPV0hqVmdDdHVkMUVSMmpHV3VKWWNqV2t6Rm10NW84Zk44RURmUHVOU3UrSjl2K1Y2Y3ZLQ2lsVVE9PSJ9]]&gt;

	- Now Available! Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx]]&gt; Exclusive, CONFIDENTIAL assets for Dell Tech
	- Win of the Week: VPay buys PKS over Docker &amp; RedHat &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/dell-tech.aspx]]&gt;
	- SpringOne Playlist Now Available! Transformation &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-transformation]]&gt;, Architecture &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-architecture]]&gt;, 
Security &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-2018-security]]&gt;, Data &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-data]]&gt;, Cloud Foundry &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-cloud-foundry]]&gt;, Serverless / Microservices &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-serverless-microserivces]]&gt;, DevOps &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-devops]]&gt;, and Kubernetes &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/springone-platform-2018-kubernetes]]&gt;



 


 

















Melanie McElligott

Dell Technologies Synergy Director (Northeast and MidAtlantic)
AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io &lt;[[mailto:AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io]]&gt; 
 Forwarded this email? Sign up here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
