<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Bill Cook 12-31-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>A New Year Message From Bill—Thank You!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi Gang,

Looking back on the year, I’m humbled by your dedication, creativity, and grit. You’ve all taken Pivotal very far in 12 short months—thank you! Congratulations to each and everyone of you for a memorable and monumental 2015.

It was a year where we introduced and rallied around Cloud Native—a growing movement in how enterprises are creating and deploying applications. This meant becoming fluent, proficient, and productive in the new frontier it represented. It meant challenging each of you to train up, stretch your boundaries, and to deliver record-breaking growth around it.

I can&apos;t comment on how we did in Q4 or in 2015, but I can tell you that I’m looking forward to toasting you and the new year. Congratulations again to everyone across the Field for your contribution, and to the progress you’ve made!

Some of the 2015 highlights for me include:


 - Our undeniable progress in rotating to a subscription-based business, while increasing our footprint with the Pivotal Big Data Suite, and Pivotal Cloud Foundry across all geos.
 - The great energy and teamwork between Pivotal Labs and Sales—a combo that helped get our clients excited about their journey to rediscover software, and make it the heart of their business strategy.
 - The transformation best practices that we established internally are translating well to clients as they transform their organizations. We’ve made the organizational changes that I believe will help us continue the awesome momentum we have going into 2016.
 - Melissa Ries and the APJ team, which made good progress, winning key customers in each country. Melissa will continue to head APJ until we find the new geo lead, whereupon she will transition to her new role.
 - Alan Coad continues to ratchet up EMEA on a trajectory to becoming a $100 million-plus business for Pivotal. Josh Knowles and the Pivotal Labs team’s growth in the UK, Ireland, Germany—and coming soon in Paris, are creating the solid foundation for this important growth in 2016.
 - The Americas. We’re finally providing Andy O’Brien some relief by promoting Andrew Ettinger to carry some of the water for the Americas business. While Q4 in the US will stand out among the many accomplishments for the quarter, the team’s staggering performance throughout the year bodes well for Pivotal’s future.
 - The major effort to integrate key technical organizations—the Customer Success Organization, pre-sales, and Pivotal Labs—under Edward Hieatt. We’re seeing great progress and promise here. The teamwork between technical teams, and the major focus on making customers successful are giving our sales teams the confidence to build trusted business and personal relationships with their clients.
 - The leadership of James Watters, and the talent he has assembled to drive Pivotal Cloud Foundry. This has had a profound impact on the market, and in every region across the globe. We simply would not be in this position without them.
 - The best executive alignment we’ve had to date, with Rob as CEO, Scott leading our data teams (and countless others), and Paul still engaged, we couldn’t be more ready for 2016.
 - And finally, when you round out the leadership team with Leo, Joe, Robert, Andy, Richard, Jason, Julie, and the dedication and support they show us in the Field every day, this is one special place.



I couldn’t be more proud of what you’ve accomplished this year, and if it’s not already clear, I’m brimming with confidence in you, and what we can achieve as a company in 2016. I expect it to be another record breaking year.

We’ll once again meet new and unexpected challenges, and evolve and adapt. We’ll throw you curve balls, and challenge you every day to be better than you thought possible. That’s our job. But I’m also thrilled to be working alongside this team in 2016.

I’ll see you in a few weeks at the WWKO. In the meantime, here’s to closing a terrific 2015, to the journey and ride in front of us...and to a very Happy New Year!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
