<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Tracker Newsletter.PROD STACK SEP 19</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Webinar] Innovating in the Enterprise: How Product Managers Can Deliver Ideas Faster</subject>
    <textOnly>For the most part, releasing products at a small startup is a straightforward process because getting everyone on the same page is easy. But if you’re a product manager at a large company, releasing a new product is far more complex. Multiple stakeholders need to be involved at various stages, and achieving organizational alignment (i.e., executives, marketing, sales, legal, etc.) can be a tall order.

How do you navigate the challenges of shipping new features without getting stuck in the enterprise black hole? Join our panel discussion for answers, as Product Stack &lt;[[http://www.theproductstack.com]]&gt; welcomes Robin Calhoun, Sr. Product Manager at Jama Software; Jay Badenhope, Principal Product Manager at Pivotal Labs; and Jim Semick, Co-Founder at ProductPlan. 

Submit your question when you register, and we&apos;ll address as many as possible during the webinar. 

Here’s what you’ll learn if you join our webinar:

- How to make decisions and reach consensus with multiple stakeholders
- How to keep stakeholders informed about progress when priorities keep changing
- How to better embrace agile principles with a large team and ship products fast

RSVP today &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/8808116573214866178]]&gt; to take advantage of this free webinar.
RSVP &lt;[[https://pivotaltracker.com]]&gt;

Robin Calhoun is a Senior Product Manager with Jama Software. She uses her education in human behavior and economics to identify and understand patterns in the way people work, and patterns in product development data, to help people make better decisions. Robin’s goal is to enable people to understand, manage, and gain insights from the rich data we already have access to. Before joining Jama, Robin was a product manager at Tendril, defining data-driven Energy Service Management Products. She holds a degree from Columbia University in Neuroscience and Behavior, and Economics.Jay Badenhope is a Principal Product Manager at Pivotal Labs. He is based in their San Francisco office, where he has worked with enterprise and startup clients to build web and mobile applications for the past three years. Before Pivotal, Jay worked in product management and marketing at Intuit, web startup JustAnswer, and Wells Fargo. He has a strong professional interest in creating team cultures that build valuable products. Jay holds a BA in political science/international relations from the University of California at Los Angeles and an MBA from the University of California at Berkeley.Jim Semick is Co-Founder and Chief Strategist of ProductPlan. For over 15 years, he has helped establish pricing and launch new products now generating hundreds of millions in revenue. He was part of the founding team at AppFolio, a vertical SaaS company. Prior to AppFolio, Jim validated and helped launch GoToMyPC and GoToMeeting (acquired by Citrix). Jim is a frequent speaker on product management and the process of discovering successful revenue models.

Jay Badenhope is a Principal Product Manager at Pivotal Labs. He is based in their San Francisco office, where he has worked with enterprise and startup clients to build web and mobile applications for the past three years. Before Pivotal, Jay worked in product management and marketing at Intuit, web startup JustAnswer, and Wells Fargo. He has a strong professional interest in creating team cultures that build valuable products. Jay holds a BA in political science/international relations from the University of California at Los Angeles and an MBA from the University of California at Berkeley.

Jim Semick is Co-Founder and Chief Strategist of ProductPlan. For over 15 years, he has helped establish pricing and launch new products now generating hundreds of millions in revenue. He was part of the founding team at AppFolio, a vertical SaaS company. Prior to AppFolio, Jim validated and helped launch GoToMyPC and GoToMeeting (acquired by Citrix). Jim is a frequent speaker on product management and the process of discovering successful revenue models.

&lt;[[https://pivotaltracker.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
