<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.12-21-16 Holiday Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Inside Pivotal Newsletter—20 Dec 2016</subject>
    <textOnly>December 21, 2016
Vol. 4, No. 15
Letter from the Editor &lt;[[#letter-from-the-editor]]&gt; – Pivotal Indispensable
Platform in Review &lt;[[#culture-update]]&gt; – The Platform Breaks Out
Interestings &lt;[[#seen-update]]&gt; – Digital Odds &amp; Ends
Data in Review &lt;[[#data-update]]&gt; – The Great Goat Rodeo
pivotal indispensable




Steve Casale &lt;[[#author-socialcast-profile]]&gt;, Sr. Manager, Corporate Communications


In The Dispossessed &lt;[[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Dispossessed]]&gt;, Ursula K. Le Guin&apos;s sci-fi classic on time and freedom, Mitis, a senior physicist, serves as mentor to Shevek, a gifted adolescent destined for big things. Mitis&apos; intelligence, abundantly clear and sharply etched, required no enhancements of title. Le Guin writes how this distinction created a &quot;psychological clear space around Mitis, like the lack of crowds around the peak of a mountain&quot;. Her authority was inherent. Young Shevek, bristling with ideas, naturally seeks her guidance.

A few short years ago, Home Depot paired up with Pivotal and started doing new things with software in an agile way. Today, the levers of Home Depot&apos;s business—its payment systems, order management, supply chains, tool rentals—are being orchestrated by software at greater speeds and better quality, on top of Pivotal Cloud Foundry, in agile sprints, fed by analytics. That enterprise includes some 150 applications, between 800 to 900 services, and 1700 instances of PCF.

Pivotal is not Google or Amazon in the sense that their authority is inherent and tacitly understood in some way by almost anyone of any age. But maybe 2016 is the year Pivotal became understood as the indispensable partner across the enterprise—from developers and ops managers, to compliance and the C-suite.

In our year-end issue, two Pivotal talents give their views on 2016 for PCF and Data, each offering points on why we&apos;re important to companies that want to be good at software. Both allude to the Labs way that guides the daily coding conventions and stories behind all of our teams, and their ability to ship faster and better than ever before.

 
Hats off to the Pivotal folks who sweat the details and lead more enterprises to draw the conclusion that we are their indispensable partner in software transformation.
Close strong, and have a peaceful holidays. Here&apos;s to becoming &apos;inherently understood&apos; in 2017.
The PLatform Breaks out




Richard Seroter &lt;[[#author-socialcast-profile]]&gt;, Senior Director of Product, Cloud Foundry
As we close it out, 2016 was quite a year for Pivotal Cloud Foundry: explosive revenue growth, mission-critical customer apps running in production, and major product engineering feats.
 Among those product updates, we fulfilled the multi-cloud vision with Microsoft Azure and Google Cloud Platform, introduced PCF Metrics, added Route Services, revamped Autoscaling, built the Master Pipeline, and added a slew of new ISV partners. All of these technical feats were girded by a common aim—to bring more portability, automation, and ease, for the world&apos;s platform of continuous innovation.
But why exactly is PCF resonating so much with the market? Pivotal&apos;s Ian Andrews says there are three reasons:


 - 10–15 year old application middleware stacks from Oracle and IBM due for tech refresh. Enterprises are refreshing their legacy tech stacks, and wondering why they’re overpaying for inflexible app servers and stacks that don’t support automation. PCF is a refreshing change.
 - The move to cloud (both public and on-prem) causing a shift in application architecture. New software paradigms deliver unheard of app resilience and flexibility. This requires a new type of platform that supports continuous delivery and horizontal scale.
 - Large enterprises coming to grips with the reality of digital disruption and “software is eating the world.” To be good at business, you have to be good at software. That’s what Forrester’s John Rymer said on our webcast this month, and the market has proven that right.



For those reasons, and more, Pivotal is at the forefront of the software revolution for any enterprise. Customers like Home Depot—which now release more software &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-conversations/features/045-cloud-native-at-home-depot-with-tony-mcculley]]&gt; on a monthly basis than than ever before—represents the primacy of software in the enterprise today. The tremendous growth PCF experienced in 2016 is proof of our position as arbiters of this software revolution.

To build on our 2016 momentum, we’re going to spend lots of time talking about cloud-native architectures, secure operations at scale, and optimizing delivery. We&apos;ll keep you posted, and here’s to another successful year!
Interestings









 - Podcast pick: Trust, guardrails, and 1700 instances: Home Depot on going cloud native &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-conversations/features/045-cloud-native-at-home-depot-with-tony-mcculley]]&gt;
 - A happy video: Michael Dell wraps Dell Technologies&apos; big year and says Happy Holidays &lt;[[https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B8GCVlqTdMB-SUJ6V05kemUzS2s]]&gt;
 - For Devs: Gemfire &amp; PCF get tight with PCF GemFire 2.0 service broker beta &lt;[[https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1932813-williammartin1]]&gt; (internal to Pivots)
 - Stand-up select: Storyboarding in virtual reality &lt;[[https://virtualrealitypop.com/storyboarding-in-virtual-reality-67d3438a2fb1#.hrojja6s9]]&gt; (thanks, Tokyo)
 - Learn: Cloud Foundry R&amp;D Town Hall &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/cloud-foundry/tech-talks]]&gt; is its usual informative self
the great goat rodeo




Elisabeth Hendrickson &lt;[[#author-socialcast-profile]]&gt;, Vice President, Data R&amp;D


One of my all time favorite albums is The Goat Rodeo Sessions with Yo-Yo Ma, Stuart Duncan, Edgar Meyer and Chris Thile &lt;[[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Goat_Rodeo_Sessions]]&gt;. Four incredibly talented musicians, each with distinct styles, came together and made magic. The name Goat Rodeo—explained in the liner notes &lt;[[http://aln3.albumlinernotes.com/Goat_Rodeo_Sessions.html]]&gt;—is slang for “the most polite term used by aviation people (and others in higher risk situations) to describe a scenario that requires about 100 things to go right at once if you intend to walk away from it.”

Pivotal is, in the best possible sense of the term, a Goat Rodeo. One hundred things have to go right. Paul Maritz kicked off this company by noting three software &quot;secrets&quot; behind disruptors like Uber and AirBnB:


 - First, they found ways to store very large amounts of data, reason over it, and do so in a very cost-effective way.
 - Second, these organizations have a culture of rapid application development, being able to introduce new experiences to their customers very rapidly.
 - Third, these consumer internet giants have found ways to operate at scale through automation.



Paul was making the case that these elements would soon matter to any business. In those phrases we find the founding pillars of Pivotal: Data, Labs, PCF. We may still be figuring out how all the pieces—especially Data—form a cohesive whole, but we are closer than ever. In 2016, more than any other year in our short history, we’re enabling our customers—industry leaders in retail, banking, insurance, and other segments not traditionally associated with technology—to leverage our offerings and truly transform the way they build software.
PCF is the platform and key structure for our customers and our offerings. By the end of this year we will have doubled our year-on-year platform business—and that is great for all of us. The &apos;smart&apos; part of application development will continue to have a whole lot to do with data. Further, the data services opportunity with PCF is growing, and we&apos;re seeing more opportunity with “alignment customers”—those who purchase both the platform and the data and analytics.
So as we move into 2017, we are likely to see more of our PCF customers asking about data offerings.
And we’ll be ready...
In 2016 we showed how an outstanding data team works in the typical Pivotal way. This includes the Greenplum Database team that put out 10—yes 10—releases this year! The GemFire team just shipped 9.0 (with 9.0.1 just around the corner). The rebooted PCF GemFire 2.0 on-demand service broker was just made available to internal stakeholders, while the GemFire-Greenplum PCF connector &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/products/big-data-meets-fast-data-to-fight-fraud-and-more]]&gt; will bridge to our analytics offers, and our open source communities are humming with activity. There’s more to come in 2017.
A customer commented to me a few months back, “I love Pivotal. You have all these different parts, and I never know what you guys are going to do next. It’s so much fun to watch as you grow and evolve! ”
It is indeed. A successful Goat Rodeo—just like the album—is exhilarating.
Onward!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
