<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>June Digest 2017.June Cloud-Native Invite 6-7-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reduce Production Risks at Scale, Fastest Way to Redis, Caching for Microservices II</subject>
    <textOnly>june 7, 2017
&lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;
Journey to Cloud-Native: Reducing Production Risks at Scale
Kamala Dasika, Pivotal and Mike Villiger, Dynatrace
june 7, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT 

Join this session to learn how app and service detection, problem identification and resolution, anticipating behavior trends, and other activities that previously required human intervention are getting baked into intelligent platforms that transform Operations teams into champions of delivering business value.

Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/journey-to-cloud-native-reducing-production-risks-at-scale?utm_source=pivotal-digest-pcf&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-appdev-part4_q217]]&gt;

The Fastest Way to Redis on Pivotal Cloud Foundry
greg chase and craig olrich, pivotal
june 28, 2017  8:00am PDT / 11:00am EDT 

What your developers want is Redis and when they want it is now! Learn about on-demand Redis for Pivotal Cloud Foundry and different ways to use Redis in cloud-native applications including:

 - Use cases and requirements for developers

 - Alternative ways to access and manage Redis in the cloud

 - Features and roadmap of Redis for Pivotal Cloud Foundry  

- Demo

Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jun-28-the-fastest-way-to-redis-in-pivotal-cloud-foundry-webinar?utm_source=pivotal-digest-pcf&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=redis-in-pcf_q217]]&gt;

Caching for Microservices Architectures: Session II - Caching Patterns
jagdish mirani, pivotal
june 29, 2017  11:00am PDT / 2:00pm EDT 

In this webinar, we&apos;ll explore various caching patterns and how they relate to microservices architectures. Beyond the simplest of use cases, caching can be tricky business. Understanding data access patterns, covered in this webinar, will help you make the right decisions for each use case. This is the second webinar in a two part series on Caching for Microservices Architectures - here&apos;s a recording of the first webinar &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/using-caching-in-microservices-architectures]]&gt;.

Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/caching-for-microservices-architectures-session-ii-caching-patterns?utm_source=pivotal-digest-pcf&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=data-caching-2_q217]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
