<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>External Newsletter.5-26-16</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Debugging the Gender Gap, Data Science 101, and Geode Summit Takeaways</subject>
    <textOnly>May 26, 2016
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sc8jNBwFtDI]]&gt;
Diversity and Debugging the Gender Gap with Cornelia Davis
Watch Cornelia Davis, Senior Director of Technology at Pivotal, discuss how we can close the gender gap by introducing girls to careers in Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM). This video aims to open an inclusive dialogue and shows how diversity is not only a good business practice but also good for business.
Debug the Gap &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sc8jNBwFtDI]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/data-science-101-using-election-tweets-to-understand-text-analytics]]&gt;
Data Science 101: Using Election Tweets to Understand Text Analytics
To illustrate the power of text analytics in terms everyone can understand, the Pivotal Data Science team recently collected Twitter data from the New York Democratic and Republican primaries and used them as a backdrop to illustrate three common scenarios where Natural Language Processing (NLP) can help businesses, including a basic understanding of word embeddings, sentiment analysis, and topic analysis.
Learn about text analytics &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/data-science-101-using-election-tweets-to-understand-text-analytics]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/geode-summit-takeaways-user-stories-new-architecture-and-futures]]&gt;
Geode Summit Takeaways: User Stories, New Architecture, and Futures
Earlier this year, a highly pedigreed group of big and fast data professionals gathered at the Apache Geode Summit. With all of the session videos and slides now online, we wanted to highlight three major themes from the conference and point out the related videos and slides.
Check Out Our Recap &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/geode-summit-takeaways-user-stories-new-architecture-and-futures]]&gt;
Upcoming Events
6/01 Pivotal Cloud Native Roadshow, Minneapolis &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/pivotal-cloud-native-roadshow/minneapolis]]&gt;


6/01 Bootiful Data Integration with Josh Long, Kansas City &lt;[[http://www.meetup.com/kc-spring/events/230115070/]]&gt;


6/02 Deciphering the Buzzword Bingo, Online &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/platform/webinar/deciphering-the-buzzword-bingo]]&gt;


6/03 Pivotal Cloud Native Roadshow, Atlanta &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/pivotal-cloud-native-roadshow/atlanta]]&gt;


6/07 Pivotal Cloud Native Roadshow, Chicago &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/pivotal-cloud-native-roadshow/chicago]]&gt;


6/09 She&apos;s Pivotal: Transforming Who’s Building The World’s Software, St. Louis &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/shes-pivotal]]&gt;

6/09 Pivotal Cloud Native Roadshow, Washington D.C. &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/event/pivotal-cloud-native-roadshow/arlington]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
