<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>March Emails 2019.Migrate Apps 3-5-19</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>3/20/19 Webinar - Migrating Your Apps to the Cloud: How to do it and What to Avoid</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 

Please join us for the webinar Migrating Your Apps to the Cloud: How to do it and What to Avoid &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/mar-20-migrating-your-apps-to-the-cloud-how-to-do-it-and-what-to-avoid-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=migrate-apps-pcf&amp;utm_term=q122]]&gt;, on March 20, 2019. 

Migrating your applications to the cloud can be a harrowing journey, one fraught with complexity and uncertainty. What’s required to succeed, above and beyond the right platform, are the right set of people, equipped with modern practices, to build and run cloud-native applications with confidence. 

Join Allison and Tom, from Pivotal&apos;s Application Transformation (AppTx) team, as they discuss what common problems arise when teams try to get their apps on the platform and the AppTx team approach to solving them. 

Whether you have purchased PCF (Pivotal Cloud Foundry) or are of a mind to move your legacy applications to the cloud this webinar will help you understand: 


	- 
Why it’s imperative to have a small team dedicated to the application portfolio 

	- 
When to replatform, modernize or rewrite an application

	- 
Strategies to address the most common issues we see



Presenter: 
Allison Willams, Senior Solutions Architect, Pivotal
Tom Collings, Advisory 
Solutions Architect, Pivotal

Date: Wednesday, March 20, 2019
Time: 10:00am PDT / 1:00pm EDT


Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/mar-20-migrating-your-apps-to-the-cloud-how-to-do-it-and-what-to-avoid-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=migrate-apps-pcf&amp;utm_term=q122]]&gt;

We thank you in advance for joining us.
The Pivotal Team

  © 2019 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g]]&gt;, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103.
Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/c000200I0NAU0rCJC001O00]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/TDAIO000r0000U220N00CJ0]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
