<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Content Syndication_Gartner_DataMgtSolutionsforAnalytics_AR_Q117.Confirma</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank you for downloading Gartner’s Critical Capabilities for Data Management Solutions for Analytics report</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for downloading Gartner’s Critical Capabilities for Data Management Solutions for Analytics report. At Pivotal we are very excited about the implications of data on modern architectures and hope this reports helps you with your modernization efforts.  

 Regardless of where you are in your journey, we think you might find these resources of interest as well:  


	- eBook: Shaping the Future of Data Warehousing through Open Source Software &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/ebooks/shaping-the-future-of-data-warehousing-through-open-source-software]]&gt;
	- Webinar: Cloud-Native Data: What Data Questions to Ask When Building Cloud-Native Apps &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/mar-15-cloud-native-data-what-data-questions-to-ask-when-building-cloud-native-apps-webinar]]&gt;
	- Case Study: Aridhia - Creating a Platform to Power the Next Generation of Clinical and Translational Informatics &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/aridhia]]&gt;
	- Case Study: O’Reilly Media - Enabling Rapid Analysis of Huge Quantities of Data &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/oreilly]]&gt;
	- Video: Data Microservices in the Cloud &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H-T-0WdZ3Sk&amp;list=PLAdzTan_eSPQ1fuLSBhyB4eEZF7JQM0Mx&amp;index=175]]&gt;
	- Analyst Report: Spring Cloud Data Flow for Continuous Data Processing &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/analyst-reports/spring-cloud-data-flow-for-continuous-data-processing]]&gt; 
	- White Paper: The Data Warehouse in the Age of Digital Transformation &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/white-papers/the-data-warehouse-in-the-age-of-digital-transformation-white-paper]]&gt;  &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/ebooks/shaping-the-future-of-data-warehousing-through-open-source-software]]&gt;



If you would like more information, or have any questions about how Pivotal can assist your organization on its digital transformation journey, don’t hesitate to reach out by contacting us here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/contact]]&gt;. 
Sincerely,
The Pivotal Team
For more on everything from Spring to cloud-native to accelerating your application development and more, please join us at SpringOne Platform &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-confirmation-discount-2018]]&gt;, taking place this September 24-27th in Washington, D.C.
Use code S1P_Discount_100 &lt;[[https://2018.event.springoneplatform.io/register?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=s1p-confirmation-discount-2018]]&gt; and save $100 off the price of admission.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
