<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Webinar_JK_DS-Cybersecurity_Q117.TYFA 1-26-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank you for attending Data Science for Cybersecurity Webinar</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/using-data-science-for-cybersecurity]]&gt;
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},

 Thank you for attending our webinar Data Science for Cybersecurity: Detecting Anomalous User Behavior within a Large Enterprise. We hope you found it enjoyable and informative as you explore your data science and analytics options. 

Let us know what you thought of the Cybersecurity session and what you&apos;d like to see in future webinars here &lt;[[http://bit.ly/PivotalWebinarSurvey]]&gt;. As mentioned during the webinar, you can view the recording and download the slide deck at the links below:

 - Watch the webinar recording  &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/using-data-science-for-cybersecurity]]&gt;
 - Download the webinar presentation &lt;[[http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/using-data-science-for-cybersecurity]]&gt;

Additional data science and analytics resources:

 - Download: Greenplum Database &lt;[[http://greenplum.org/]]&gt; and Apache MADlib (incubating)  &lt;[[http://madlib.incubator.apache.org/]]&gt;
 - Data Sheet: Pivotal&apos;s Approach to Threat Detection: Cybersecurity Analytics at Scale  &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/securityanalytics]]&gt;
 - Blog: Sequential Pattern Mining Approach for Watering Hole Attack Detection  &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies/sequential-pattern-mining-approach-for-watering-hole-attack-detection-2]]&gt;
 - Podcast: Don’t Let Your Data Science Models Die A Lonely PowerPoint Death &lt;[[https://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-insights/features/09-dont-let-your-data-science-models-die-a-lonely-powerpoint-death]]&gt;

And don’t miss future data science, big data and analytics webinars and other events from Pivotal. Check Pivotal’s upcoming webinars here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/resources/1/webinars]]&gt;. 

 If you would like more information or have any questions about data science and analytics, submit your question and contact information at pivotal.io/contact &lt;[[http://pivotal.io/contact]]&gt;. 

 Sincerely, 
The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
