<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.June 15 Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Pulse 5-Point Friday Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>June 15, 2018

Hello friends, 

 Exciting momentum is building at Pivotal and it’s been a while since we&apos;ve sent a newsletter. I’m happy to say, we’re back and dedicated more than ever to supporting our Dell Tech counterparts. Joint product updates went GA last week including PRA 1.1, VMware and Pivotal have a high-powered GTM model for PKS, and opportunities momentum is building. It’s a GREAT time to be in the Dell Tech ecosystem SAB’s. 

 I’d like to welcome you to our first bi-weekly dose of 5-Point Friday, a newsletter with ONLY 5 bullets designed to showcase sales strategies, customer stories, talk tracks and valuable data points to uplevel our joint customer conversations, help them understand how to operate at start-up speeds, and help us all land more business. 

Looking forward to great sales success with each of you this year.

 


 



 


 


1. Your Inside Access to Pivotal
 
 There are many former Dell EMC folks here at Pivotal, myself included. We have walked in your shoes. One of our primary goals is to open Pivotal doors and make it easier to work with our teams in the field. Today, we are incredibly excited to announce a giant step in that direction. The Pivotal Opportunity Registration &lt;[[http://www.surveygizmo.com/s3/4243153/d5679a47c95anewsletter]]&gt; link has officially launched. This tool enables you to submit a qualified customer opportunity which will get assigned to a Pivotal rep and empower us to successfully work together. Meeting the scale of Dell EMC, and VMware is not easy, but we’ve made significant investments to drive joint customer engagements to the next level.

 


 



 


 


2. Pivotal Ready Architecture
 
 If you not yet prospecting customers for PRA, now is the time. On June 4th, PRA 1.1 went GA which you can read about here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/say-hello-to-pivotal-ready-architecture-from-dell-emc-the-easy-button-for-pivotal-cloud-foundry-in-your-data-center?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_campaign=dell-newsletter&amp;utm_term=q218]]&gt;. We have 50 PRA opportunities in the pipeline for Q2, with an additional 100 + prospects to follow. For more details, Dell EMC &lt;[[https://www.dellemc.com/en-us/solutions/cloud/pivotal-ready-architecture.htm]]&gt; and Pivotal &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/pivotal-ready-architecture]]&gt; recently launched website to showcase this joint offering.

 


 



 


 


3. Dell Tech World &amp; SpringOne
 
 We are grateful to have been included at Dell Tech World a few weeks ago. One theme was consistent across the board, and that is, how we work together via Pivotal Ready Architecture. Here are a couple recorded sessions from the show: Chad Sakac and Chad Dunn cover infrastructure stacks &lt;[[https://www.thecube.net/dell-tech-world-2018/content/Videos/t8cNDdjGK8DX3TBL7]]&gt; and a quick talk with me and the Dell Tech TV folks, covering a high level overview on the partnership &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ozlX13af5W4]]&gt;, including PRA. Pivotal’s version of Dell Tech World is SpringOne Platform &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/]]&gt; @S1P in Washington DC, Sept 24-27. It’s a great opportunity to engage customers in application and development focused conversations. Our conference is unique because the majority of speakers are in fact Pivotal customers with tremendous stories of how they leverage our combined technologies to become modern software development organizations in their own right. Please help us get the word out!

 


 



 


 


4. The Pivotal Team Dedicated to Dell Tech
 
 As many of you know we at Pivotal are fortunate to have Chad Sakac join as the new SVP leading our group. Chad has been on the road talking to customers and driving important initiatives including Pivotal Container Services (PKS). You can listen to the Pivotal Insights Podcast, Beware of Superheroes and Resume-Driven Development &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/podcasts/beware-of-superheroes-and-resume-driven-development-ep-71]]&gt; covering Chad’s lessons from the road to learn more. Additional members of the Dell Tech team at Pivotal include Jag Brar, Business Analytics, Courtney McShane, Program Management, David Krant, Business Development, Michael Wood, Transformation Specialist, and Angus MacDonald, VMware lead. We are all here to serve at the pleasure of our partners field sales organization and happy to help with whatever you need.

 


 



 


 


5. Fast (not Big) Companies Thrive in the Cloud Era
 
 This is why it is critical to quickly meet the demands of today’s consumer expectations. Pivotal conducted a Built to Adapt Benchmark &lt;[[https://benchmark.builttoadapt.io/banking]]&gt; study that gauges how well an organization builds and operates software. Partnering with Longitude Research and Ovum, 1,600 of the world’s top organizations in six countries and across five industries were interviewed. Our colleague and eStaff leader @Pivotal, Edward Hieatt, SVP Customer Success Organization digs into the details of the study in his blog post The Built to Adapt Benchmark Will Help Companies Set a New Course &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/the-built-to-adapt-benchmark-will-help-companies-to-set-a-new-course]]&gt;. See how your customer measures up. 

 Catch you on the next addition of Five Point Friday! 
Yours in the battle, 
 Craig Steel

 


 






 
 
 


 


Upcoming Events

VMworld 2018 US &lt;[[https://www.vmworld.com/en/us/learning/tracks.html]]&gt; Aug 26-30 
 SpringOne Platform &lt;[[https://springoneplatform.io/]]&gt; Sept 24-27


Digital Knowledge

Pivotal Learning Series &lt;[[https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1j1pEC99jbscZJQTNKKskMxRiyI-8I3K7dfLEezuHNR4/viewform]]&gt;

 


 






 
 
 


 


Craig Steel
 GM, Pivotal Software, Inc
Dell Tech Strategy &amp; Operations</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
