<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>April Digest 2017.Email send 4-5-17</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Monthly Webinar Digest - Spring Boot, RabbitMQ, Cloud-Native, Microservices, Analytics and more</subject>
    <textOnly>April 5, 2017
&lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;


Spring Boot Under the Hood
Nicolas Fränkel, Hybris Software
April 13, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Going beyond the automatic settings? Join veteran speaker Nicholas Frankel as he teaches you Spring Boot internals and shows you how to wield Spring Boot like a boss.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/spring-boot-under-the-hood?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=spring-boot-under-hood_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Orchestration Patterns for Microservices with Messaging by RabbitMQ
Dan Baskette, pivotal and Greg Chase, pivotal
April 18, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Adding a message queue like RabbitMQ to microservices architectures helps them communicate in sophisticated ways. Learn about different messaging patterns that utilize RabbitMQ in microservices-based applications.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/orchestration-patterns-for-microservices-with-messaging-by-rabbitmq?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=orch-patterns-microservices-rabbitmq_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Journey to Cloud-Native: Continuous Delivery with Artificial Intelligence (AI)
Kamala Dasika, Pivotal and Mike Villiger, Dynatrace
April 19, 2017   9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT 

This webinar will cover how you can contain post-deployment risk with rapid rollback of poorly performing releases within blue/green deployments by using AI-based anomaly detection.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/journey-to-cloud-native-continuous-delivery-with-artificial-intelligence?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-appdev-part2-q217]]&gt;




 

 
New! Pivotal Cloud Foundry: Run Native Windows at Scale, Distributed Tracing, Network Isolation, and Much More
Jared ruckle, pivotal and pieter humphrey, PIVOTAL 
April 25, 2017  10:00am PDT / 1:00pm EDT

Ship software early and often with Pivotal Cloud Foundry 1.10, now generally available. Join us for a deeper look with live demos and expert Q&amp;A about many of the new capabilities, and learn all about the latest updates to the leading multi-cloud platform in this online event.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/pivotal-cloud-foundry-run-native-windows-at-scale-network-isolation-and-more?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pcf-1.10-ruckle-humphrey_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Using Caching in Microservices Architectures
jagdish mirani, PIVOTAL 
April 26, 2017  11:00am PDT / 2:00pm EDT

Caching can boost performance and scalability of your microservices architecture without introducing huge costs, complexity, and rigidity. Find out how the new Pivotal Cloud Cache service for Pivotal Cloud Foundry can satisfy these requirements. This is the first in a series of webinars on caching for microservices architectures.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/using-caching-in-microservices-architectures?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=caching-microservices-arch-jag_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Strategies on how to Overcome Security Challenges Unique to Cloud-Native Apps
Zane Lackey, Signal Sciences and KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL
May 3, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Join our webinar to learn how Pivotal and Signal Sciences work together to make app deployments faster *and* safer in cloud-native environments.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/strategies-on-how-to-overcome-security-challenges-unique-to-cloud-native-apps?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=signalsciences-security-kd_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Journey to Cloud-Native: Making Sense of Your Service Interactions
KAMALA DASIKA, PIVOTAL AND MIKE VILLIGER, DYNATRACE
may 16, 2017  9:00am PDT / 12:00pm EDT

Join this session to learn how teams are overcoming the complexity in operational data that often makes root cause analysis challenging by applying automatic application-environment discovery, service and process flows integration and self healing platforms.



Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/journey-to-cloud-native-making-sense-of-your-service-interactions?utm_source=dynatrace-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=dynatrace-appdev-part3_q217]]&gt;




 

 
Capitalizing on Customer Desire with Social Media Analytics
Scott Hajek, Pivotal
may 31, 2017  11:00am PDT / 2:00pm EDT

Determining customer desire or intent from social media data provides companies the opportunity to deliver targeted, more 	effective messaging and convert more sales. This webinar will describe the data science techniques, tools, and infrastructure required to capitalize on this potentially lucrative opportunity. Save My Seat &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/capitalizing-on-customer-desire-with-social-media-analytics?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=digest-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=social-media-analytics-jk_q217]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
