<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Cloned from 017 February 15 2019 Newsletter A For Friday, March 01 send</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Dell Sales Newsletter_5 Point Friday_2018.018 March 01 2019 Newslet</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You’re missing out on sales… get the Hottest product in Dell Tech in your next quote. - Pivotal 5 Point Friday</subject>
    <textOnly>March 01, 2019

Hello, I’m Courtney McShane. As Program Director for the Dell Tech Synergy team at Pivotal, I’m dedicated to accelerating sales growth among the Dell Tech family, with special focus on VMware and Dell EMC. If I could make one small ask it would be - check out the Pivotal Pulse Podcasts, all episodes are listed under ‘Digital Knowledge’ below. Thanks for reading!


 


 

 


 

1. Work with Pivotal… in 60 seconds


Here is what you need to know for 2019, tools you can leverage, important customer opportunities, and work being done by the Dell Tech Synergy team. It&apos;s actually more like 160 seconds...but who&apos;s counting.
Everything in this video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cFXhOeAmeAY&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt; is public (so it can be shared) but rest assured there is a LOT of internal momentum taking place as well. For sales wins, confidential battle cards, and other exclusive materials built for the field, visit Pivotal Pulse Exclusive &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/?ReturnUrl=%2fEnglish%2fGlobal%2fsales%2fdell-tech.aspx]]&gt; portal under ’Sales’ → ‘Dell Technologies’
 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cFXhOeAmeAY&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;

 


 

 


 


2. Great things come in small...


Drumroll please! This beautiful one-page customer facing slick &lt;[[http://home.mv.treehousei.com/MVImages/Pivotal/DellTech/pra_slick_final.pdf]]&gt; is a wonderful intro to Pivotal Ready Architecture. Whipped up by my colleague Raj, and by whipped I mean iterated on a couple dozen times. Share, re-share, add to your email signature - this is the hottest product in Dell Technologies, because it’s multiple products. It brings the best of Dell Technologies together and beats out competition every. single. time.

 &lt;[[http://home.mv.treehousei.com/MVImages/Pivotal/DellTech/pra_slick_final.pdf]]&gt;


 


 

 


 


3. Customer First Innovation at T.Mobile


T. Mobile is using Pivotal Cloud Foundry to maximize performance and productivity - and focusing on innovation that puts customers first &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/customers/t-mobile]]&gt;. While competing wireless carriers faulted under the surge of traffic, T.Mobile soared through iPhone launches with zero downtime.

At Dell Tech World, T.Mobile’s Platform Architect Seffi Yaran will be on stage discussing The Evolution of IT at T. Mobile from IaaS to PaaS to CaaS to FaaS &lt;[[https://delltechnologiesworldonline.com/2019/connect/search.ww#loadSearch-searchPhrase=mobile&amp;searchType=session&amp;tc=0&amp;sortBy=&amp;p=]]&gt;.

If you haven’t already, listen to Seffi&apos;s Pivotal Pulse Podcast &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pivotal-changed-my-life-customer-interview-with-t-mobile/s-cSA1a]]&gt;.


 


 

 


 


4. Featured Win of 2018 - Duke Energy

There were a lot of big wins as we wrapped up FY19 and stepped into Q1. Duke Energy is a great example. 



	- It showcases the power of the Global Transformation Office bringing together Dell EMC, VMware and Pivotal for a ‘Better Together’ win.
	- Duke benefitted from Pivotal Ready Architecture, for deploying PCF on-prem.


Duke struggled to meet expected business requirements and software development deadlines so Dell EMC brought in Pivotal to help. Duke bought PAS and PKS which landed on PRA resulting in $16M Dell Technologies revenue. Congratulations to the whole team! 

Dell EMC: Scott Mulwee, Tom Santuccio and Dale Pickford​. 
Pivotal: Michael Krumpe and Abhinav Rau. 
(Fun fact: VMware products account for $32% of PRA)

 


 

 


 

5. Custom-Built Infra for Containers?
 
You may hear our competition touting their infra built-for containers. Here’s the thing, we’ve had this on lock down for a LONG time, with a full agile engineering dev/test team behind it actively validating the entire solution-level config for each new release of PCF and VMware. It offers Containers and VMs on any cloud - Google Cloud, Azure, vSphere, AWS, OpenStack. Nutanix can’t do this. Red Hat can’t do this. No. One. Else. Can. Do. This.
When customers ask about this week’s PKS Announcement (Meet the PKS Family: Kubernetes Done Your Way &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/meet-the-pks-family-flexibility-for-your-kubernetes-architectures?utm_campaign=content-social&amp;utm_content=1551146638&amp;utm_medium=social-sprout&amp;utm_source=twitter]]&gt;) combining Heptio’s expertise with VMware and Pivotal, let them know Pivotal Ready Architecture is not only custom-built for containers, but the easy button for deploying PKS on-prem. 
Nothing like a Real Advantage
- McShane

 






 
 
 


 

Upcoming Events
Pivotal Days Customer Workshop:




Chicago, IL - March 5 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Chicago.html]]&gt;
 Cambridge, MA - Mar 12 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Boston-March-2019.html]]&gt;
 Seattle, WA- Mar 15 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Seattle.html]]&gt;
Denver, CO - Mar 19 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Denver-2019]]&gt;
Fairfield, CT - Mar 26 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Fairfield-March-2019.html]]&gt;
 Cleveland, OH - Apr 2 &lt;[[https://connect.pivotal.io/Pivotal-Days-Cleveland.html]]&gt;





PKS Roadshow Cities &lt;[[https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__vmware.cvent.com_events_multicloud-2Dkubernetes-2Dseminar_event-2Dsummary-2Defe4f4942fba4c3bb11c6298f5e0b2bb.aspx&amp;d=DwMGaQ&amp;c=lnl9vOaLMzsy2niBC8-h_K-7QJuNJEsFrzdndhuJ3Sw&amp;r=z2OUpB4hmCNKIsEQKqBgxJGZJotrI9RgX88d4-wviUs&amp;m=79tRyTmOEJiNX7aupi6XUHY_gB2o6B63I1BjVb5HgnQ&amp;s=BYrb6VEIUybHp9L7WdPHpL2NErulgZjh2imrmBVCujs&amp;e=]]&gt;:




Toronto, Canada - Mar 19
San Jose, CA - Mar 12
Vancouver, Canada - Apr 2






Dell Tech World &lt;[[http://www.delltechnologiesworld.com/]]&gt;:




April 28- May 2 , work with your Pivotal rep to set up a Customer Meeting with a Pivotal Executive




Digital Knowledge
Pivotal Pulse Podcasts:



	- New release! CPO at Merrill brings Innovation to M&amp;A Industry, Customer Interview &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/cpo-at-merrill-brings-innovation-to-ma-industry-customer-interview]]&gt;

	- The Operations behind Daimler’s Self-Parking App, Customer Interview &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/the-operations-behind-daimlers-self-parking-app-customer-interview/s-5CtDb]]&gt;
	- &quot;Pivotal Changed My Life&quot; T.Mobile Customer Interview &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pivotal-changed-my-life-customer-interview-with-t-mobile/s-cSA1a]]&gt;
	- $2.3M Win: AutoZone Hits the Gas to Deploy Apps Faster &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pks-win-at-autozone-with-james-thibadeau-pivotal/s-hWXES]]&gt;
	- Winning Mental Strategy for $30M PRA &amp; PKS Win at Telecom Italia &lt;[[https://soundcloud.com/user-606338988/pra-pks-win-at-telecom-italia/s-TTCUE]]&gt;




	- Website: Pivotal Pulse &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx]]&gt;, designed exclusively for Dell Tech

	- Internal: Pivotal Pulse Exclusive &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/?ReturnUrl=%2fEnglish%2fGlobal%2fsales%2fdell-tech.aspx]]&gt;, confidential sales tools &amp; content

	- Win of the Week: Cisco, Nutanix, and OpenShift outed w/ PRA at Prime &lt;[[http://home.mv.treehousei.com/MVImages/Pivotal/DellTech/Prime-Therapeutics_North-America-Commercial-Win-of-the-Week.pdf]]&gt;
	- Chad Sakac Blog: Kubernetes and PKS - 5 Pieces of News &lt;[[https://virtualgeek.io/kubernetes-and-pks-5-pieces-of-news/]]&gt;



 


 

















Courtney McShane
Program Director, Dell Tech Synergy, Pivotal
AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io &lt;[[mailto:AskDellTech@Pivotal.Io]]&gt; 
 Forwarded this email? Sign up here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/General_DT_Info.aspx#newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
