<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.Jenn Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Field Video Series:  “Success in the Second Half of 2015”</subject>
    <textOnly>We recently sat down with some of our best Product and Field people and asked them to share their insights for driving successful sales plays for the balance of the year.  The result was the creation of a new video series: “Success in the Second Half of 2015.” To kick this off, we’ve got two great videos that will give you an edge in understanding and articulating the value we deliver.
 
Please set aside time over the next week to watch each of these informative videos. You’ll need to be logged into the Field Enablement &lt;https://pivotal.biglms.com/field_enablement&gt; site to view them.


 - Use the links below to access the videos, and select “Register for Course”. 
 - If you’re not already signed-in, select “Sign In”, or select “Register” if it’s your first time on the site.  Both options are in the upper right corner of the page.



SELLING PIVOTAL CLOUD FOUNDRY – “CLOUD 1, 2, 3” &lt;https://pivotalfield.biglms.com/courses/PFS/SELL101/VWZ/about&gt; (18:26)
 Featuring Andrew Ettinger, Ian Andrews, and James Watters
 &lt;https://pivotalfield.biglms.com/courses/PFS/SELL101/VWZ/courseware/5ae6580e6063451cb4e872a51b8b64c9/98952254195140aba2b650e500871475/&gt;
 
 Learn more about the “Cloud 1, 2, 3” approach and how that’s differentiating Pivotal and creating value for our customers.  Specifically, you’ll get insights into:


 - Cloud 1, 2, 3 approach
 - Momentum and adoption around Cloud Native
 - Best positioning points to use with your customer to diffuse pricing and competitive objections



SELLING PIVOTAL LABS &amp; PIVOTAL CF TOGETHER &lt;https://pivotalfield.biglms.com/courses/PFS/SELL100/VWZ/about&gt; (21:25)
 Featuring Edward Hieatt, Arni Raghvender and Alex Luttschyn
 &lt;https://pivotalfield.biglms.com/courses/PFS/SELL100/VWZ/courseware/5ae6580e6063451cb4e872a51b8b64c9/98952254195140aba2b650e500871475/&gt;
 
 Learn more about the “better together” sales proposition and story that occurs when we’re aligning Labs with PCF.  Specifically, you’ll get insights into:


 - How this joint selling motion differentiates us by addressing the needs of both the Apps team and the Ops team
 - The significant pipeline traction that’s been made to-date for Labs and Pivotal Cloud Foundry
 - How this joint selling motion helps us lead our customers to the Cloud Native world
 - Steps you can take to run a joint Labs and PCF play



If you have any access issues, please contact Jennifer O’Neill
 
Good Selling!



Jennifer O&apos;Neill 
Sr Mgr, Global Sales Training and Development
M: 646-734-0227 &lt;tel:646-734-0227&gt; | joneill@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:joneill@pivotal.io&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
