<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>cloned from 009 November 2018 GET newsletter (partner spotlight)</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_GET Partner Newsletter_2018.015 January 2019 GET Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Is Kubernetes the right place to run that? The Pivotal Partner Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>Our mission is to enable partners to build deep expertise and 
thriving business practices with Pivotal.



 

 


 
 
 


 

What to Run Where



 
 
 
 



In December, our editorial focus was on Accelerating Development &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/accelerating-development]]&gt;. This month we look at choosing the ideal runtime for your application, container, or function. 

 
 

From applications to containers to functions, choosing the correct runtime environment for your workloads is critical to success. Here are 3 great examples of how partners and customers are making sure their workloads land on the appropriate platform:





 

Videos






	- Learn why West Corp. has embraced Pivotal Container Service &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/videos/enabling-global-transformation-at-west-corp-thomas-squeo-cto-west-corp]]&gt; in this chat from SpringOne Platform 2018.
	- T-Mobile discusses how it decides which workloads to run &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/videos/making-multi-cloud-a-reality-at-t-mobile-brendan-aye-james-webb]]&gt; on Pivotal Application Service and which on PKS.






 

Blog







	- Learn how VMware’s new PKS Competency &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/vmware-pks-competency-kubernetes-abstraction-going-mainstream]]&gt; helps partners develop new Kubernetes-based solutions and revenue streams.




There is more great content in the Choosing the Best Runtime for Your Workloads content stream &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/choosing-the-best-runtime-for-your-workloads]]&gt; on Pivotal.io. That content stream is also embeddable on your own site using the embed code found here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/partner-information.aspx#contentstream]]&gt;.





 


 

 


 




 

Upcoming Webinar - Building Your Brand: Co-Marketing with Pivotal


Join Pivotal’s Kamala Dasika and Jeff Kelly to learn about the best ways to market your relationship with Pivotal and joint customer successes to increase market awareness, increase mindshare of the Pivotal field, and drive more joint customer engagements.


In this webinar, you will get/learn:



	- An overview of Pivotal&apos;s &quot;We Partner Different&quot; approach to partner marketing

	- Pivotal&apos;s key marketing and messaging themes for 2019 

	- Best practices for effectively marketing your relationship with Pivotal, both to the external market and to internal stakeholders.



Register here &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/webinars-events.aspx]]&gt;
Date: January 23, 2018
Time: 2PM ET


 




 












 

Enablement



 
 
 
 



The following resources are designed maximize the development of your cloud native knowledge. 

 










 

Platform Acceleration Lab:





Start the year off empowered to build new and migrate existing applications. Here are the upcoming opportunities for Cloud Native training:



	- March 11, 2019 - Boulder and Japan

	- April 15, 2019 - Boulder, London, and Shanghai


For the most up-to-date schedule, check here &lt;[[https://pivotal.io/platform-acceleration-lab]]&gt;, or talk with your Pivotal Alliances Manager.




 

Partner Portal:






	- Want to learn more about your partnership with Pivotal? Check out your customized Partner information page &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/sales/partner-information.aspx]]&gt; to see your primary contact, capabilities, specialty, and geographic focus.
	- The December Global Ecosystem webinar recording on PCF 2.3 and 2.4 &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/more/recordings.aspx]]&gt; is live, complete with accompanying slide deck.






 

Partner Platform Architect Spotlight:







	- PCF 2.4 became GA mid-December, and you can see a recap of new features in this extensive blog post &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/pcf-is-known-for-the-best-app-deployment-experience-now-its-even-better-with-zero-downtime-updates-for-pretty-much-everything]]&gt;. There’s too much awesomeness to list here, but the new Compliance Scanner and app blue-green deploy with cf push are some highlights.

	- Check out the specifics of the new Dynamic Egress Policy capability here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/blog/beyond-application-security-groups-avoid-app-restarts-with-dynamic-egress-policies-in-pcf-2-4]]&gt;!

	- If you haven’t seen Pivotal’s James Watters lightboard video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3PLq2vTIjVE]]&gt; reviewing questions to ask customers about running Kubernetes, take the 9 minutes to do so now!






 

Public Webinars:







	- Jan 23: Four Steps Toward a Safer Continuous Delivery Practice &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jan-23-four-steps-toward-a-safer-continuous-delivery-practice-hint-add-monitoring-webinar]]&gt; (Hint: Add Monitoring)

	- Jan 29: Securing Microservices &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jan-29-securing-microservices-spring-and-pivotal-cloud-foundry-webinar]]&gt; Spring and Pivotal Cloud Foundry 

	- Jan 31: Habits of Highly Effective Platform Teams &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jan-31-habits-of-highly-effective-platform-teams-the-key-to-unlocking-the-value-of-pivotal-cloud-foundry-webinar]]&gt;: Unlocking the Value of PCF


View our previous and upcoming public webinars here &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars]]&gt;.




 

Greenplum Partner Spotlight:







	- Join us at Greenplum Summit @ PostgresConf 2019 &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/pivotal-greenplum/greenplum-summit-2019-scale-matters]]&gt;, March 18 to 22 in New York City! 

	- Learn about the Greenplum for Kubernetes operator &lt;[[http://engineering.pivotal.io/post/greenplum-for-kubernetes-operator/]]&gt; for declarative deployment of Greenplum in Kubernetes. Also learn how you can test Greenplum for Kubernetes using Minikube &lt;[[http://engineering.pivotal.io/post/rapid-development-using-minikube/]]&gt;.

	- Pivotal Greenplum is now available on the Google Cloud Platform (GCP) Marketplace &lt;[[https://console.cloud.google.com/marketplace/partners/pivotal-public]]&gt;! You can also find Greenplum in the Azure Marketplace &lt;[[https://azuremarketplace.microsoft.com/en-us/marketplace/apps/pivotal.pivotal-greenplum-azure-hourly]]&gt; and AWS Marketplace &lt;[[https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace/pp/B073V7NWQD?qid=1546466830475&amp;sr=0-2&amp;ref_=srh_res_product_title]]&gt;.



The Partner Portal Data Page &lt;[[https://partners.pivotal.io/English/Global/delivery/working-with-data.aspx]]&gt; has the latest Greenplum release details, demonstration ideas, and information from a few of our data partners.





 


 

 


 
 
 


 

Marketing



 
 
 
 



Last month, we talked about telling compelling customer stories. This month, we highlight thought leadership content.

 
 





 

Upcoming Events






	- April 2-4, 2019: Cloud Foundry Summit North America &lt;[[https://www.cloudfoundry.org/event/nasummit2019/]]&gt; is coming to Philadelphia

	- Oct 7-10, 2019: Start planning now for SpringOne Platform 2019 in Austin, TX! Please contact us at sponsorS1P@pivotal.io &lt;[[mailto:sponsorS1P@pivotal.io]]&gt; about 2019 sponsorship





 


BEST PRACTICE OF THE MONTH: 
Thought Leadership Content


We’re in the midst of a once-in-a-generation transformation in enterprise computing, leaving companies large and small with no shortage of questions. What does digital transformation mean for my industry? How do we decide which technologies and approaches to bet our future on?

The good news is that you, Pivotal’s ISV and SI partners, are in prime position to help our joint customers and prospects answer these and other questions. By providing impactful thought leadership content, you not only help enterprises make hard decisions, but you also solidify yourselves as trusted partners and strategic advisors.

What’s the best way to get started? 



	- First, identify the topics and trends that are most important to our joint customers. Take a look at Pivotal’s editorial theme calendar &lt;[[http://home.mv.treehousei.com/MVImages/Pivotal/editorial-themes-1-pager.pdf]]&gt; for ideas. 

	- Second, seek out subject matter experts in your company that have great insights on these topics to share. 

	- Third, work with your Pivotal alliances rep and our partner marketing team to develop and promote joint content to customers and prospects. 




Contact your alliances rep and start creating great thought leadership content today!




 








 
 





 














Partner Spotlight

 

System Integrator // North America // Pivotal Cloud Foundry

Magenic and Pivotal Cloud Foundry get your business to the cloud faster. Our partnership with Pivotal helps clients design and develop .NET and Java applications quickly and effectively using the Pivotal Cloud Foundry platform. Magenic and Pivotal share a commitment to helping our clients build better and more innovative digital products. It’s a partnership that runs so deep that Pivotal named Magenic “Breakthrough Partner of the Year” in 2018.

Getting the Joint Story Out:



	- Listen to Magenic’s Rocky Lhotka in this Pivotal podcast discuss Modernizing .NET Apps &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/podcasts/modernizing-net-apps-with-magenics-rocky-lhotka-ep-74]]&gt;

	- Learning more about effectively digital transformation and .NET apps with a path to Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;[[https://magenic.com/media/2790/modernizing-your-net-apps-wp.pdf]]&gt;




Find more content from Magenic about working with Pivotal here: content.pivotal.io/magenic &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/magenic]]&gt;
“Magenic’s partnership with Pivotal enables our joint clients to modernize and move their .NET applications to the cloud with greater speed and lower cost so they can accelerate innovation.” - Greg Frankenfield, CEO, Magenic</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
