<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Tracker Newsletter.PROD STACK OCT 25</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Webinar] The Essential Skills All Product Managers Must Master</subject>
    <textOnly>What does it take to be a product manager? Is there a cookie-cutter template, a perfect mold that all PMs should seek to fit into? Are the skills finite and easily definable? In the next Product Stack webinar, we’re going to find out together if there is a such a thing as a paragon of product managementhood—and if you’re on track to be that kind of PM.

Join our panel discussion for answers, as Product Stack &lt;[[http://www.theproductstack.com]]&gt; welcomes Kevin Steigerwald, VP of Products and UX at Jama Software; Isabelle Berner, Senior Product Manager at Pivotal Labs; and Annie Dunham, Director of Product at ProductPlan. 

Here’s what you’ll learn if you join our webinar &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/167314178058813955?source=pivotal]]&gt;:

	- Let’s be truthful: what is and is not a product manager function?
	- What are the soft skills that product managers should cultivate?
	- What are the hard skills product managers should know?

RSVP &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/167314178058813955?source=pivotal]]&gt;

THE PANEL

Annie Dunham is the Director of Product Management at ProductPlan. Annie has worked with product and engineering teams for the last 15 years to bring technology products to market. Prior to ProductPlan, she worked with teams at Elite Meetings, LogicMonitor, BlueCasa Communications, and Microsoft.

Isabelle Berner is a product manager for Pivotal Labs, a software development consultancy specialized in lean and agile. She has worked as a product manager for over 10 years, primarily for fintech startups such as Current, Betterment, and TagPay.

Kevin Steigerwald is the VP of Products and UX at Jama Software. He&apos;s a full-stack product designer with over 10 years of experience designing, researching, marketing, planning, and building products.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
