<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>January Emails 2019.Concourse/Dynatrace 1-8-19</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>1/23/19 Webinar - Four Steps Toward a Safer Continuous Delivery Practice (Hint: Add Monitoring)</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 

Please join us for the webinar Four Steps Toward a Safer Continuous Delivery Practice (Hint: Add 
Monitoring) &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jan-23-four-steps-toward-a-safer-continuous-delivery-practice-hint-add-monitoring-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=four-steps-concourse&amp;utm_term=q119]]&gt;, on January 23, 2019. 

The demands of fast incremental code development require a stable, safe, and continuous delivery pipeline that can get your code into the hands of your customers without delay. Put your continuous delivery pipeline on autopilot by automating and simplifying the workflow—continuous integration to production readiness—and by using an automated monitoring solution to prevent bad builds from impacting production. This webinar will cover the steps to building an automated, monitored pipeline: 


	- 
Modeling and visualizing your build and delivery process as a pipeline (defined as a single, declarative config file) 
using Concourse CI.

	- 
Leveraging integrations to trigger actions and share data, supporting functions like testing, collaboration, and 
monitoring.

	- 
Enhancing your end-to-end continuous delivery pipeline with contextual deployment event feeds to Dynatrace.

	- 
Adding automated, metrics-based quality gates between pre-production stages and an automatic post-production approval 
step, all with specifications defined in source control.



Presenters: 
James Ma, Senior Product Manager, Pivotal
Michael Villiger, Sr. Technical Partner Manager, Dynatrace

Date: Wednesday, January 23, 2019
Time: 10:00am PST / 1:00pm EST


Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/jan-23-four-steps-toward-a-safer-continuous-delivery-practice-hint-add-monitoring-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=four-steps-concourse&amp;utm_term=q119]]&gt;

We thank you in advance for joining us.
The Pivotal Team

  © 2019 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g]]&gt;, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103.
Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/c000200I0NAU0rCJC001O00]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/TDAIO000r0000U220N00CJ0]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
