<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Dell Tech celebration invite</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.09-12-16 BCook</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Mark Your Calendars – Dell Technologies Celebration</subject>
    <textOnly>All,

As you have likely heard, Dell Technologies has an ambitious celebration planned to mark its debut. Michael Dell will host a high-production event from Dell, EMC and VMware broadcast hubs across the globe, this Wednesday, September 14th.

Any Pivotal employee interested in watching this live celebration broadcast can stream it online at their workstations/laptops. Additionally, five Pivotal offices—Denver, London, New York, San Francisco, and Toronto—will stream the broadcast in their event spaces.

When and How to Watch it


- Celebration is on Wednesday, September 14th, from 10:30 AM – 1:00 PM (Central Time)—or 8:30 AM in San Francisco, and 4:30 PM in London. Pre-event programming starts at 10:30 AM and the live show kicks off at 11:00 AM.
- You can find the celebration event link and information on Inside Pivotal Dell Day 1 site &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/dell-day-1]]&gt;. NOTE: The live link will be posted shortly before the start of the show.



We encourage those of you who can make time for it to watch the live broadcast. We&apos;ll also post the celebration replay link on Inside Pivotal following the event. This is a good chance to hear from the Dell Technologies leadership, watch videos, and catch the global social chatter.

And if you haven&apos;t yet done so, support Dell Technologies&apos; Million Tree Challenge by casting your vote &lt;[[https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/dell-day-1/the-million-tree-challenge]]&gt; now for the region in which you&apos;d like to trees planted on behalf of Pivotal employees.

Enjoy the show.

Bill</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
