<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>October Emails 2018.GraphQL 10-9-18</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>10/17 Webinar - Simplify Access to Data from Pivotal GemFire Using the GraphQL (G2QL) Extension</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 

Please join us for the webinar Simplify Access to Data from Pivotal GemFire Using the GraphQL (G2QL) Extension &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/oct-17-simplify-access-to-data-from-pivotal-gemfire-using-the-graphql-g2ql-extension-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=graphql&amp;utm_term=q418]]&gt;, on 
October 17, 2018. 

GemFire GraphQL (G2QL) is an extension that adds a new query language for your Apache Geode™ or Pivotal GemFire clusters allowing developers to build web and mobile applications 
using any standard GraphQL libraries. G2QL provides an out-of-the-box experience by defining GraphQL schema through introspection. It can be deployed to any GemFire cluster and serves a GraphQL endpoint from an embedded jetty server, just like GemFire’s REST endpoint. 

We will be demoing G2QL using a sample application that can read and write data to GemFire and share data between applications built using GemFire client APIs, showing you: 


	- 
How to use GraphQL to query and mutate data in GemFire

	- 
How to use open-source GraphQL library to build web and mobile applications using GemFire

	- 
How to use GraphQL to deal with object graphs

	- 
How G2QL can simplify their overall architecture



Presenters: 
Sai Boorlagadda, Staff Software Engineer, Pivotal
Jagdish Mirani, Pivotal

Date: Wednesday, October 17, 2018
Time: 10:00am PDT / 1:00pm 
EDT


Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/oct-17-simplify-access-to-data-from-pivotal-gemfire-using-the-graphql-g2ql-extension-webinar?utm_source=promo&amp;utm_medium=webinar&amp;utm_campaign=graphql&amp;utm_term=q418]]&gt;

We thank you in advance for joining us.
The Pivotal Team

  © 2018 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g]]&gt;, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103.
Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/c000200I0NAU0rCJC001O00]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/TDAIO000r0000U220N00CJ0]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
