<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>April Emails 2018.PCF-CN/CI Dormain 4-3-18</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>5/17/18 Webinar: Cloud-Native Fundamentals: Accelerating Development with Continuous Integration</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
 

Please join us for the webinar, Cloud-Native Fundamentals: Accelerating Development with Continuous Integration &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/may-17-cloud-native-fundamentals-accelerating-development-with-continuous-integration-webinar?utm_source=digest&amp;utm_medium=webinars&amp;utm_campaign=cn-ci&amp;utm_term=q218]]&gt;, on 
May 17, 2018. 

DevOps. Microservices. Containers. These terms have a lot of buzz for their role in cloud-native application development and operations. But, if you haven&apos;t automated your tests and builds with continuous integration (CI), none of them matter. 

Continuous integration is the automation of building and testing new code. Development teams that use CI can catch bugs early and often; resulting in code that is always production ready. Compared to manual testing, CI eliminates a lot of toil and improves code quality. At the end of the day, it&apos;s those code defects that slip into production that slow down teams and cause apps to fall over. 

The journey to continuous integration maturity has some requirements. Join Pivotal&apos;s James Ma, product manager for Concourse, and Dormain Drewitz, product marketing to learn about:


	- 
How test-driven development (TDD) feeds the CI process

	- 
What is different about CI in a cloud-native context

	- 
How to measure progress and success in adopting CI



Presenters: 
Dormain Drewitz, Pivotal
James Ma, Pivotal

Date: Thursday, May 17, 2018
Time: 10:00am PDT / 1:00pm EDT


Attend &lt;[[https://content.pivotal.io/webinars/may-17-cloud-native-fundamentals-accelerating-development-with-continuous-integration-webinar?utm_source=digest&amp;utm_medium=webinars&amp;utm_campaign=cn-ci&amp;utm_term=q218]]&gt;

We thank you in advance for joining us.
The Pivotal Team

  © 2018 Pivotal Software, Inc. 875 Howard Street &lt;[[https://www.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g]]&gt;, Fifth Floor, San Francisco, CA 94103.
Published in the USA. Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/c000200I0NAU0rCJC001O00]]&gt;. Manage your subscription preferences &lt;[[http://info.pivotal.io/TDAIO000r0000U220N00CJ0]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
