<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.12-15-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of December 15, 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of December 15, 2014
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/moments-in-container-history-infographic&gt;
MOMENTS IN CONTAINER HISTORY INFOGRAPHIC
Container-based technology has experienced a recent revival, and is becoming adopted at an explosive rate. For those that are new to the conversation, containers offer a way to virtualize an operating system. This virtualization isolates processes, providing limited visibility and resource utilization to each, such that the processes appear to be running on separate machines. In short, allowing more applications to run on a single machine. Here is a brief timeline &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/moments-in-container-history-infographic&gt; of key moments in container history.
READ MORE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/moments-in-container-history-infographic&gt;
EPISODE #10: WEDNESDAY, JANUARY 7TH
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt; this week for &apos;Using Pivotal CF for Blue/Green Deployment&apos;, Episode #9 of our ongoing podcast series.

Getting new features into the hands of your customers sounds great, but it can be a little trickier than it looks. How do you ensure that a change does not “break” the system? How do you roll-back if something bad happens? How do you deploy a change so that no traffic is lost, packets are dropped or transactions missed?

Fortunately Pivotal CF provides built-in capability to handle this complexity for you. In this episode, we will dive more deeply into the concept of Blue/Green deployments, and the mechanism used by Pivotal CF to deploy changes into production with zero downtime and no packets dropped!
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
HOW TO SCALE NATIVE (C/C++) APPLICATIONS ON PIVOTAL&apos;S MPP PLATFORM: EDGE DETECTION EXAMPLE, PART 1
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/products/scaling-native-applications-on-pivotals-mpp-platform-part-1&gt;
One of the challenges organizations face while adopting big data platforms is seamlessly integrating legacy applications. Fear of having to redesign and reengineer existing applications built over years leads to resistance towards adopting big data platforms such as MPP databases and Hadoop within some organizations. In this two-part blog post, we’ll demonstrate how a sample native application can be seamlessly integrated and scaled up for data parallel problems on HAWQ, Pivotal&apos;s SQL-on-Hadoop solution.
 
 READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/products/scaling-native-applications-on-pivotals-mpp-platform-part-1&gt;
BIG DATA IN EDUCATION: ANALYZING STUDENT CLUSTERS TO INFLUENCE SUCCESS AND RETENTION
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/big-data-in-education-analyzing-student-clusters-to-influence-success-and-retention&gt;
Learn how one university is using data science to understand students and identify the factors leading to student success and retention by analyzing structured and unstructured data. In this post, one of Pivotal&apos;s Senior Data Scientists explains the background, approach, solution, models, and outcomes of a recent project.
 
 READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/big-data-in-education-analyzing-student-clusters-to-influence-success-and-retention&gt;
- In Big Data, Shepherding Comes First &lt;http://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/15/technology/in-big-data-shepherding-comes-first-.html?ref=technology&amp;_r=0&gt;
 - Two Programmers Are Better than One for Your Data Science Team &lt;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/two-programmers-are-better-than-one-for-your-data-science-team/&gt;
 - The Enterprise’s Multi-Cloud Conundrum &lt;http://www.itbusinessedge.com/blogs/infrastructure/the-enterprises-multi-cloud-conundrum.html&gt;
 - Sony Pictures Tries to Disrupt Downloads of Its Stolen Files &lt;http://recode.net/2014/12/10/sony-pictures-tries-to-disrupt-downloads-of-its-stolen-files/&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
