<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.July 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Build a shopping cart in 24 hours using Spring - Why do I recommend Spring - Conquering Content-enabled apps with Spring and Groovy</subject>
    <textOnly>Building a Shopping Cart in 24 Hours using Spring
Speakers: Casey Doolittle and Phil Dutson
 
 Creating a transactional website that is secure, fast, and responsive is a challenge all on its own. Creating one in 24 hours borders madness, however with the resources that Spring brings to the table, this can be accomplished. Casey Doolittle and Phil Dutson were issued the task of creating a charity-benefit website two days before the sale started. In time for the opening sale, they had a simple website that was open during a set time of day, and offered users the ability to complete a purchase regardless of the device they were using.

During this talk Casey and Phil will discuss how they accomplished the feat and the techniques and tactics that were used.
Europe
Tuesday, July 15, 2014
3:00pm BST Time
(London, UTC+01:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_BuildingaShoppingCartin24HoursusingSpring7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, July 15, 2014
10:00am PDT
(San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_BuildingaShoppingCartin24HoursusingSpring10AM_Register.html&gt;
Why Do I recommend Spring?
Speaker: Michael Plöd 
 
 Is Spring the new legacy as quite a few people tell you on their blogs? I disagree on many levels. Throughout this session I will holistically detail without any polemics why I do recommend using the Spring Framework and its ecosystem. Aspects that will be covered include: operational impacts, ecosystem, coding and road maps. This presentations aim at IT managers, Architects and Developers alike.
Europe
Tuesday, July 22, 2014
3:00pm BST Time
(London, UTC+01:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_WhydoIrecommendSpring7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, July 22, 2014
10:00am PDT
(San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_WhydoIrecommendSpring10AM_Register.html&gt;
Conquering Content-enabled Web and Mobile Applications with Spring and Groovy
Speaker: Russ Danner
 
 Rich media and digital content are an integral part of nearly all Web and mobile applications today, but the growing number of platforms, changing business demands and time to market are a major concern.

Join this session to learn modern practices for building content-enabled Web and mobile apps. We will uncover common challenges faced by content and application teams, explain how these problems are solved by simple, powerful tools and the right architecture. We&apos;ll also demonstrate how leading organizations such as AT&amp;T, Marriott, and Harvard Business Publishing have succeeded by leveraging Spring Framework, Groovy and other leading Java development technologies along with content management frameworks to build and manage content rich applications.
Europe
Tuesday, July 29, 2014
3:00pm BST Time
(London, UTC+01:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_ConqueringContentwithSpringandGroovy7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, July 29, 2014
10:00am PDT
(San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_ConqueringContentwithSpringandGroovy10AM_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
