<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.PM - Org Announcement 10-7</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Leadership Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Colleagues,

We launched Pivotal to address the opportunity to enable businesses to generate new value through developing new applications and uses of data in the cloud era. We have developed three capabilities to enable this: our cloud independent PaaS platform based on Cloud Foundry, our Big Data Suite, and our Pivotal Labs agile development services. These three capabilities are resonating strongly with customers. At the same time we are seeing the environment change rapidly with open source technologies and competitors gaining traction. 

To respond to the opportunity to be the leading 3rd generation platform company, and to the address the challenges, we must now focus and move faster to:


 - Have our three capabilities reinforce each other.
 - Align with the open source forces operating in our industry.
 - Get to “one Pivotal” with a shared culture and approach to development, based on the best practices that we share with our customers.



Cloud Foundry has now matured to the point where we can make it the foundation of our platform. We recommend Pivotal Labs as the way of building great apps and technology, and have seen this approach successfully applied to Cloud Foundry. The Data and Application Fabrics are vital to Pivotal’s success and our Big Data Suite concept has been well received. There is now the need to align these Data and App Fabric efforts more strongly with Cloud Foundry, with a common development culture and with open source, to accelerate development of our unique capabilities and get more leverage.

For these reasons, we have decided now is the time to 
unify our technology teams under one leader, Rob Mee. Rob is ready and excited to take on this challenge.

Hugh Williams is moving into a new role outside of the Product organization. He will be our first Entrepreneur-in-Residence (EIR), and will be exploring new strategy and business directions with the leadership team. All of Hugh’s organization will report to Rob, effective immediately. I would like to thank Hugh for all his contributions to date. 

I look forward to this next chapter in Pivotal’s evolution and to sharing more of our 2015 plans as we work through the details in next month or so.

Thanks to all of you for all you are doing,</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
