<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.JM-8-25-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the Pivotal Pulse Survey: Five Minutes That Matter</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi Team,

As Paul wrote on August 25th, we place a premium on honest feedback as we continue to make improvements at Pivotal. Starting in September we’ll ask for 5-10 minutes of your time to participate in a survey which will go a long way in helping us make Pivotal a great place to work. 

 Surveys are one of the tools we have to understanding how you view Pivotal and your work experience, and we now have a great process to make this a global survey effort that covers our entire employee base.

 We want our approach to be simple and frequent ‘pulse’ checks that give everyone a chance to provide feedback. We’re launching this new Pivotal Pulse survey this month and here is what you need to know:

 



 - 
This survey is short and simple. It should only take around 5-10 minutes to complete.


 - 
It&apos;s confidential. In order to encourage open and honest feedback, survey participation will remain strictly anonymous. An experienced third party, Sirota Consulting &lt;http://www.sirota.com&gt;, will administer the survey to help ensure this level of confidentiality.


 - 
Within the next week Sirota will send the online survey to a random sample that covers approximately 25% of our employee base. Thereafter, a different random sample of employees will be invited to take the survey each quarter. Within 12 months time everyone will have had the opportunity to participate.

 - We&apos;ll share a summary of the survey results, and use the data to guide us on initiatives and policies that will have the greatest impact on your success. 


The 5 to 10 minutes we’re asking of you each year will ensure that your voice is heard and give us the basis against which we can help make Pivotal and you successful. Please look out for the survey invitation, and make time to complete it. Your viewpoint matters.

Please refer to our FAQs &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/document/d/1dTm5GR2Z-Ktc2AxRBytwLfJcOOMjsCfojPV033lsRiY/edit&gt; for more information.

 Thank you in advance for your time! 

 Joe
VP People</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
