<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.February 2015 Webinar Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Spring XD-A Platform for data at scale and developer productivity &amp; Introducing Spring Session</subject>
    <textOnly>Spring XD: A Platform for data at scale and developer productivity
Speaker: Sabby Anandan, Mark Fisher &amp; Mark Pollack

Worried about Big Data and the challenges inherent in making a real application? You don’t have to worry anymore! Spring XD provides a one-stop shop solution that spans traditional enterprise to Big Data use cases - both batch and streaming. It&apos;s important to choose the right tool for each use-case, which is why Spring XD integrates with technologies such as Spark, Reactor and RxJava to demonstrate the flexibility and the unified programming model to support complex data computation use-cases.

In this webinar, we&apos;ll show you how to develop data-driven use cases much faster than other big data solutions on the out of the box XD runtime.
Europe
Tuesday, February 17, 2015
 3:00PM GMT Time
 (London, GMT)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMSpringXDAPlatformfordataatscaleanddeveloperproductivity_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, February 17, 2015
 10:00AM PST
 (San Francisco, GMT-08:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMSpringXDAPlatformfordataatscaleanddeveloperproductivity_Register.html&gt;
Introducing Spring Session
Speaker: Josh Long

Back in the era of the application server, HTTP Session replication was a common way to scale out user session data, as well as make it fault tolerant. In today&apos;s world of lightweight containers, PaaS, and virtualization, Spring Session offers a 100% server and/or container portable HTTP Session.

See how Spring Session easily plugs in implementations like Redis, scales out across a cluster, handles multiple users&apos; browser sessions, works with WebSocket, and allows header based authentication within REST apps. It&apos;s a perfect fit for working with user data, particularly in a highly distributed environment like the cloud, or on a Platform like Cloud Foundry.
Europe
Tuesday, February 24, 2015
 3:00PM GMT Time
 (London, GMT)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMIntroducingSpringSession_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, February 24, 2015
 10:00AM PST
 (San Francisco, GMT-08:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMIntroducingSpringSession_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
