<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Labs 8-14 Announcement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Labs Branding Update</subject>
    <textOnly>EVENT NAME
Tagline
All,

In recent months, Labs has collaborated closely with Marketing to develop a more unified story around the 
relationship between the Labs business and Pivotal overall. As you know, Labs is a key part of the company and we think that a closer alignment of the brands will be very positive for Pivotal’s success. We have spent considerable time making sure that we end up with solutions that represent Labs’ history and emphasize the critical role of Labs at Pivotal. Starting August 18th, we will roll out a variety of changes:
 
 Pivotal Labs Logo
One of the important items we have worked on is the development of a visual brand identity that associates Labs more closely with Pivotal but that preserves the equity of the Labs brand. We feel we have arrived at a solution that speaks to our heritage but aligns us more closely to the Pivotal brand. (This is being done also for the Pivotal Cloud Foundry and Big Data Suite logos.) I am very pleased to announce the unveiling of the new Labs logo, shown below along with Pivotal’s company logo.
 

 
 The new Labs logo reflects the following important considerations:


 - Retain the heritage and equity of the Labs brand by keeping its most recognizable asset: the fan blades.
 - Adopt Pivotal brand colors and typography to immediately create a visual relationship between both brands.



The new Labs logo assets along with usage guidelines will be ready for download on Inside Pivotal &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/corporate-marketing/brand-assets&gt; on August 18th.

 


Pivotal Labs presence on pivotal.io &lt;pivotal.io&gt;
We think that an important part of aligning with the Pivotal brand is to retire the pivotallabs.com &lt;pivotallabs.com&gt; site and instead have a strong Labs presence at pivotal.io &lt;pivotal.io&gt;. We have put a lot of work into creating new content and making the new site stronger than the old pivotallabs.com &lt;pivotallabs.com&gt; site, which was in need of renovation anyway. On August 18th, we will launch a new Labs section at pivotal.io &lt;pivotal.io&gt;, with plans to continuously improve on the content and redirect traffic from pivotallabs.com &lt;pivotallabs.com&gt; to it. Key functionality, like the connect page, will operate in the same way on the .io site as it did on the .com site.

 Pivotal Labs Blog
The Pivotal Labs blog has been migrated to the pivotal.io &lt;pivotal.io&gt; blogging platform. Current Labs contributors will find their accounts set up on the pivotal.io &lt;pivotal.io&gt; blog with their same login information. A blogging guideline for working on the blog can be found here &lt;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1jBLcNOSFMfcSNI4SyvwtKd9Kh9VrhVvzvgy1XWz6KYE/edit&gt;. If you experience any problems accessing your blog account or publishing a post, please email: askmarketing@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:askmarketing@pivotal.io&gt;
 
 Pivotal Labs Business Cards
 We will also create new Pivotal Labs business cards. Instructions on how to order new cards will be posted next week.

I’m excited by these changes: I think they will help tell a clearer story about how Labs fits into Pivotal and clear up any remaining confusion outside the company. Thanks for being part of Labs at this exciting time. As always, feel free to reach out to me or your local management team if you have any questions.


Edward</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
