<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Labs_Newsletter_Q314_August.Monthly Newsletter - August 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Labs News - August 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Pivotal Labs News - August 2014



Luxr Joins Labs &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/agile-team-grows-stronger/&gt;

Pivotal Labs has a mission to change the way the world builds software, and we&apos;re pleased to announce that Luxr&apos;s team of Lean Startup specialists has joined Pivotal to become an important part of continuing to execute on our vision. 

Since 2010, Luxr has led the development of Lean Startup methodologies, helping innovators bring new products to market with less risk and greater impact. Throughout that time, Pivotal and Luxr have been close partners, developing new methods, consulting together, and driving innovation through Lean and Agile methods for many mutual clients, at both the startup and enterprise level.
 
Click here to learn more about LUXR and how they will continue to drive Lean expertise at Pivotal Labs in this blog post by Janice Fraser, Founder and CEO of Luxr &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/agile-team-grows-stronger/&gt;.


Announcing Pivotal Labs at gSchool &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/galvanize-launches-exclusive-apprenticeship-program-pivotal-labs/&gt;

In this apprenticeship program, Pivotal Labs at gSchool provides rigorous, real-world software development experience to students attending gSchool’s 6-month developer training programs in San Francisco.
 
Click here to learn more &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/galvanize-launches-exclusive-apprenticeship-program-pivotal-labs/&gt;.


Partnership with Startup Grind &lt;http://startupgrind.com/&gt;

Startups have been a part of the Pivotal Labs DNA for over two decades. As part of our ongoing commitment to the startup community, we&apos;re happy to be partnering with Startup Grind, a global startup community designed to educate, inspire, and connect entrepreneurs by providing space for their awesome monthly meetups in four of our offices: Silicon Valley &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Grind/&gt;, San Francisco &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Grind-SF/&gt;, New York &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Grind-NYC/&gt;, and Toronto &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Grind-Toronto/&gt;. Be sure to check out their calendar of events here.


Visit Us in the Windy City!

We&apos;ve recently opened an office in Chicago&apos;s historic Merchandise Mart Plaza, where we look forward to forging more partnerships with this booming city&apos;s leading brands. You can already see some of our work in the app stores: we recently designed, developed and launched the Android &lt;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cellit.flexilist.leye&gt; and iOS &lt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/lettuceeats/id351174022?mt=8&gt; apps for Lettuce Entertain You &lt;http://www.leye.com/&gt;.


Our Recent Top Blogs

A Review of Google I/O &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/review-google-io/&gt;

A few Pivots attended the annual Google I/O conference, which aims to educate developers on what&apos;s new with the wide variety of technologies that Google supports. With over 100 different one hour sessions available and only 10 slots to cover them all, each of us had a different and unique experience.
 
Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/review-google-io/&gt;.


When Your Client Wants Over-the-Top Features &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/client-wants-crazy-features/&gt;

Sometimes our stakeholders ask for features that are counter to generally good UX and design practice. So what do we do about that? It’s a tough situation because they feel so strongly about it.
 
Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/client-wants-crazy-features/&gt;.


Why Executives Need to Embrace Experimentation &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/embracing-experimentation/&gt;

There is no question that the game has changed, and is going to keep changing faster. Fortunately, making software (and recently hardware too) is easier than ever before.
 
Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/embracing-experimentation/&gt;.


Where to Find Us in the Near Future


Startup Grind Silicon Valley Hosts Manu Kumar (K9 Ventures) &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Startup-Grind&gt; \ (August 19 - 6:00pm @ 3495 Deer Creek Rd) \ Join us in our Palo Alto office to hear Manu Kumar, founder and Chief Firestarter at K9 Ventures, participate in a fireside chat with Derek Andersen, Founder and CEO of Startup Grind.
 
Getting Started with Redis &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Toronto-Pivotal-User-Group/events/179792932/&gt; \ (August 20 - 7:00pm @ 1 Toronto St, Suite 1100) \ Come to our Toronto office to learn about Redis, an advanced key-value store or a data structure server. Faisal Akber, who has been working in IT for over 17 years, will be presenting.
 
Madison+ Ruby &lt;http://madisonpl.us/ruby/&gt; \ (August 21 - 23 in Madison, WI) \ Mike Dalessio, who recently joined our Cloud Foundry team, is attending this conference designed for people who are either Ruby-curious or already practitioners. Mike will be representing various open-source projects that he maintain, so feel free to reach out &lt;mailto:mdalessio@pivotal.io&gt; if you&apos;d like to meet him in person.
 
WindyCityRails &lt;http://www.windycityrails.org/&gt; \ (September 4-5 in Chicago) \ We are speaking at Chicago&apos;s single-track Ruby on Rails conference, so come out to listen to great speakers, grow your skill set, and meet new people.
 
Disrupt SF &lt;http://techcrunch.com/events/disrupt-sf-2014/event-home/&gt; \ (September 8 - 10 in San Francisco) \ Come out to meet us at TechCrunch Disrupt, one of the most anticipated technology conferences of the year.
 
Digital Media Wire: Future of Television &lt;http://www.dmwvideo.com/&gt; \ (September 10 in New York) \ We&apos;re attending Future of Television, which brings together 300+ content creators, broadcasters, cable execs, digital and mobile service providers, advertisers and ad-tech execs to focus on strategies to engage, empower, connect and monetize video audiences across platforms.
 
Denver Startup Week &lt;http://www.denverstartupweek.org/&gt; \ (September 15 - 20 in Denver) \ We&apos;re sponsoring this event, so come say hello at this week of learning, discussion, networking, and more.
 
FITC Web Unleashed &lt;http://fitc.ca/event/webu14/&gt; \ (September 17 - 18 in Toronto) \ We&apos;ll be moderating a panel and speaking at FITC, which produces design and technology events worldwide that inspire, educate and challenge attendees.
 
GoGaRuCo &lt;http://gogaruco.com/&gt; \ (September 19 - 20 in San Francisco) \ Swing by our booth at GoGaRuCo, which offers in-depth technical explorations of the most interesting parts of the Ruby landscape, presented by some of the top talents in the Ruby development community.
 
Finovate Fall &lt;http://www.finovate.com/fall2014/&gt; \ (September 23 - 24 in New York) \ Come out to meet us at this showcase of the latest and greatest financial and banking technology innovations from leading established companies and hot young startups.
 
Rocky Mountain Ruby &lt;http://rockymtnruby.com/&gt; \ (September 24 - 26 in Boulder) \ Developer Arjun Sharma will be speaking on the topic of &quot;What it means to have good test coverage, and why it matters,&quot; at this conference that gravitates around the Ruby programming language.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
