<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Bill Cook 8-19 Org Memo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Pivotal Organization and Leadership</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,
 
 What a big day and what a way to celebrate a pivotal moment! We had record attendances both live and online for Tuesday’s Town Hall. Please find the Town Hall replay, other videos, org announcements, customer FAQs and media coverage on our Town Hall landing 
page.

 I speak for the company when I say that Paul has led and inspired by example. As the new Executive Chair of the Pivotal Board, we’re excited Paul remains actively engaged as our biggest supporter. We also congratulate our new CEO Rob Mee. No one has a deeper understanding of who we are and what we can achieve than Rob, and he has our full support.

 We’re focused on making customers successful with Pivotal, and making this an outstanding year for the company. With a record quarter closed and huge customer momentum, we have a tremendous opportunity to capture a disproportionate fair share of the market. This requires organizing ourselves to better anticipate customer needs and market opportunities, and to out execute the competition.  

 Effective immediately, in order to move faster with greater focus, we’re announcing the following 
organizational changes:
 
Edward Hieatt will expand his role at Pivotal, leading a re-defined and rethought Customer Success Organization that unifies our customer-facing technical teams as follows:


 - An important new team of technical partners for our sales reps, aligned to accounts and focused on customer success in order to drive our subscription model (leader to be announced, led by Edward directly initially)
 - Data Engineering pre- and post sales team, led by Jacque Istok
 - Pivotal Labs, now operated by Drew McManus
 - Pivotal Transformation, led by Siobhan McFeeney
 - Global Support Services, led by Johnny Scarborough
 - The Alliances Engineering and the new Pivotal Enablement team, led by Michael Wood


Unifying these services and support groups as one group under Edward’s leadership will strengthen the collaboration between 
product and sales teams, drive the rapid adoption of our subscription services, better support our sales reps, and ensure long-term customer success.
 
Further, the Pivotal 
Tracker and the Pivotal IT teams will now report into Edward, and continue to be led by Dan Podsedly and Drew Kramer, respectively.

 Second, to strengthen alignment between our Pivotal Cloud Foundry (PCF) product and field teams, we’re bringing PCF services and field engineering teams into James Watters’ Cloud Platform Group. Effective immediately:


 - Dino Cicciarelli’s PCF Services team will partner closely with the Field Engineering team that is now led by Arni Raghvender (and focused primarily on pre-sales). This collaborative new team will be called the PCF Solutions team, reporting into James
 - In addition, the PCF Technical Marketing and PCF Business Development teams that currently report to James will now be led by Ian Andrews


We need to stay nimble to win greater mind- and market-share in a cloud native space that moves at breakneck speed. We’re very confident that this will help our product and field engineering teams align better on our technical capabilities and roadmap, accelerate successful PCF sales and rollouts, and speed the wide adoption of our platform.  

Third, we’re tying together related business development efforts in an expanded Corporate Development and Strategy team, led by Leo 
Spiegel. Pivotal channel partner teams such as EMC, VMware, system integrators, VARs and OEMS, as well as our technology alliance teams will now roll into Leo. Nick Cayou will lead this consolidated channel and alliances effort, reporting to Leo. Leo, Nick and team will work closely with PCF, Data and Pivotal Labs teams to set priorities and align with our field organization. 

We’ve done so much in a short time, but markets don’t wait.  

To ensure that we turn a record quarter into a record year, these organizational adjustments will get us to 
market faster, and help customers on their transformational journey from good companies to great software companies. We have an extraordinary culture on which to do this, and I believe deeply what Rob stated—that showing our customers a new way to innovate and remain relevant in a world driven by software, is a transformational movement that unites us all.  

We’ll move ahead with the same passion and dedication that brought us to this moment. Please help me congratulate Paul, Rob, and our Pivotal leaders, and let’s transform how the world builds software!

Bill</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
