<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Bill Cook federation Note</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Federation Go-To-Market Update</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

Last quarter EMC announced a new cross-Federation strategy led by Jeff Casale to help our largest and most strategic global accounts harness the full power of the Federation to transform their business IT. Key customers are keen for a simplified cross-Federation approach, and we believe they’re ready to increase their overall spend with us as we simplify our collective go-to-market.

This new Federation GTM team is now operational. Jeff Casale has been working closely with me and our Pivotal and Federation leadership, and I’m pleased to share with you the following actions and steps we’ll take in Q3 FY15 on this coordinated, go-to-market effort:


 - To lead efforts at the strategic account level, we’ll appoint Federation client directors to a small set of highly-qualified accounts. These individuals will serve as the lead point-of-contact for the customer, managing C-level sales and services engagements across the Federation.
 - We’re creating a Federation Pursuit Team under Jeff’s leadership to help our account teams qualify and pursue large, strategic opportunities.
 - Recognizing how rapidly business and technologies change, we’ll create a Federation Scale team - a set of highly-specialized resources expert in our collective Federation assets to assist you in selling and qualifying the Federation value.
 - Lastly, we’re creating a Federation Shared Services Desk to help Federation account teams harmonize commercial terms across the Federation. (pricing, legal, etc.)



Learn more

Please read the Federation FAQs &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0B8GCVlqTdMB-RWJlYUtVbVhycE0/view?usp=sharing&gt; to learn the details on these new engagement rules, and how they may apply to you and your customers. You can also watch this short video &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0B8GCVlqTdMB-R1NpS3kzcU4zSGc/view?usp=sharing&gt; of Jeff Casale talking through the changes.

I also encourage all of you to join the live Federation Go-To-Market Virtual Q&amp;A session on Monday, July 27 at 12:30 P.M. EDT (9:30 A.M. PDT).  To watch: 



 - For those in Pivotal offices or remote, go to www.Livestream.com/emctvlivestream &lt;http://www.livestream.com/emctvlivestream%3Chttp:/www.Livestream.com/emctvlivestream&gt; and enter the following password: saleschat (link will not be live until Monday)
 - For those in an EMC II office location, directly connected to the EMC II network, you can use the following Multicast link &lt;http://dmpweb.corp.emc.com/Federation_go2.asp&gt;



A seamless, coordinated EMC Federation is our unique opportunity to become a strategic partner on some of the most visible and important IT and business transformations today. We are beginning to see the mutual value in this partnership in our recent big wins. I expect all of us to give Jeff and his team our full support as we increase our collaboration across the Federation, to deliver the best integrated solutions and value for our customers. 

Please reach out to me, Nick Cayou, or your Geo Leader with any questions. Great selling!


Best,</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
