<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Hugh Announcement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Organization Announcement</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

As we kick-off 2014, I am very pleased to announce that Hugh E. Williams has joined Pivotal as our new SVP of Research and Development, reporting to me. Hugh is responsible for leading Engineering, QA, Product Management, Tech Operations, and University/Technical Community Relations for the Application and Data teams.
Having someone with Hugh&apos;s experience, leadership and technical background join our team is a strong validation of Pivotal&apos;s vision and opportunity. Hugh has been actively recruited by the highest profile companies in the Valley, and ultimately chose to join us at Pivotal. Adding the horsepower of an executive of Hugh&apos;s stature will be invaluable as we head into 2014.
Hugh has spent nearly twenty-five years researching and developing search engines, web services, and big data technologies. From 2009 to 2013, Hugh was with eBay. He led a large cross-disciplinary team that turned around the Marketplaces business. His teams conceived, designed, and built eBay’s user experiences, search engine, big data technologies, and platforms. Prior to eBay, he spent 4+ years managing a R&amp;D team at Microsoft’s Bing, 10+ years researching and developing search technologies, and 5 years running his own startup and consultancy. He has published over 100 works, mostly in the field of Information Retrieval, and two books for O’Reilly Media Inc. He holds nineteen US patents and has many more pending. He has a PhD from RMIT University in Australia.
Please join me in welcoming Hugh to Pivotal! The mission is big and I am looking forward to our work together.
- Scott
More about Hugh in his own words:
Hi All,
I’m excited to be joining Pivotal. I’ve been working on large data problems continuously since 1993, when I started work on the challenge of searching large genomic data sets to help geneticists discover information about DNA and proteins. Since then, I’ve spent my career working on large-scale distributed data problems, including using map-reduce infrastructures in domains such as web search, image search, commerce search, and trend prediction. I’ve seen how data transforms the businesses I’ve worked in, and the technologies, teams, and investments that companies need to be successful. It’s awesome now to have the chance to help build those technologies for everyone to use, and to be part of the first real enterprise-grade company that will transform the way business happens. I’m excited to be working with you all – and looking forward to getting to know you all better.
On a personal note, I’m married, and have two beautiful daughters. We live in Los Gatos. We’re all originally from Australia, and we’ve lived in the US since 2005. Outside of work, I enjoy spending time with the family, exercising, playing the drums, writing, and collecting strange and not-so-strange things.

Cheers, Hugh












Follow Us: Twitter &lt;http://www.twitter.com/gopivotal&gt; | LinkedIn &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/gopivotal&gt; | Facebook &lt;http://www.facebook.com/gopivotal&gt; | Google+ &lt;https://plus.google.com/105320112436428794490&gt;




© Pivotal - FOR INTERNAL USE ONLY - DO NOT DISTRIBUTE.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
