<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.6-29-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>25% Off Registration at OSCON</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of June 29, 2015
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/pivotal-at-oscon-microservices-iot-spring-cloud-graph-analysis-more?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;
Pivotal at OSCON: Microservices, IoT, Spring Cloud, Graph Analysis &amp; More
Come join us at OSCON to see some of the world’s best and brightest in open source. Visit us at booth #306 or come see talks by Pivotal on Microservices, Spring Cloud, Graph Analysis, In-Memory Databases, Internet of Things (IoT), Spring XD, Docker, Cloud Foundry, Lattice, Apache Giraph, and Spark GraphX.

Use the promo code Pivotal25 for 25% off registration.
REGISTER NOW &lt;https://en.oreilly.com/open-source-2015/public/register?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;
Cloud Foundry Summit - Some Selections
July 1, 2015
The Cloud Foundry Summit took place in Santa Clara back in May and brought together a large group of passionate people to discuss all things Cloud Foundry. In this episode, Simon highlights some interesting sessions that were his &quot;pick of the bunch&quot;.
 
Listen Now &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/features/cloud-foundry-summit-some-selections?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;
EMC IT: Using Pivotal Cloud Foundry to Streamline Product Licensing
June 29, 2015
EMC faced a challenge within their license management group, which covers a very large product portfolio. It needed to be able to support a global operation at a much faster pace to support the business. After the team became familiar with Pivotal Cloud Foundry, it was able to see how it would help provide a cloud-native platform for full application lifecycle management as well as a runtime for microservices. Since deploying, deployment times have been drastically reduced. Some apps that took months to deploy now take minutes.


Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/case-studies-2/emc-it-using-pivotal-cloud-foundry-to-streamline-product-licensing?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;
This Month in Data Science: June 2015
July 1, 2015
Data science’s critical role within a wide range of industries and areas of research was evident during the month of June, as Spotify announced a new data analytics team, free-to-play games received increased scrutiny, and much more. Here’s our roundup of the biggest data science news of the month, both from Pivotal and beyond.


Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/this-month-in-data-science-june-2015?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-6-29-15&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
