<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.SA-Ian Gray Announcement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Welcome Iain Gray, Vice President of Customer Success</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

I am delighted to welcome Iain Gray to Pivotal as our new Vice President of Customer Success, reporting to me. Our Customer Success group brings together several different parts of the business, with the goal of building a world-class customer experience. With his leadership experience in software development, consultant delivery, training, enablement, and technical support services, Iain will bring the perspective required to help us build a strong culture of customer success. More broadly, Iain will also be responsible for field education and enablement, and Global Support.
 
Iain most recently served as Vice President of Global Services at Red Hat, Inc., where he led professional services, customer training, and partner enablement activities on a global level. He also had key roles at Sun Microsystems Inc., SCO UK Limited, and Logica plc, a breadth of experience that will serve him well at Pivotal.
 
Iain holds a BS degree in Chemistry from Herit Watt University in Edinburgh, Scotland and a Master’s degree in Computer Science from University College in London, England. He enjoys running, and playing tennis and golf in his free time and sits on the Board for Artspace, a visual arts center, which conducts exhibitions, education programming, and allows artists to work in open studios. http://www.godowntownraleigh.com/go/artspace &lt;http://www.godowntownraleigh.com/go/artspace&gt;
 
Please join me in welcoming Iain to the team, and feel free to reach out to him: igray@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:igray@gopivotal.com&gt;.
 
Make it Happen!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
