<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.11-24-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of November 24, 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of November 24, 2014
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/5-tips-for-building-engaging-data-driven-mobile-apps-infographic?utm_source=Twitter&amp;utm_medium=tweet&amp;utm_campaign=core-5-tips-mobile-infographic-q42014&gt;
5 TIPS FOR BUILDING ENGAGING, DATA-DRIVEN MOBILE APPS
Whether you&apos;re building a native mobile app or a mobile-friendly website, users demand an engaging, high-performance experience.

Check out our infographic, 5 Tips for Building Engaging, Data-Driven Mobile Apps &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/5-tips-for-building-engaging-data-driven-mobile-apps-infographic?utm_source=Twitter&amp;utm_medium=tweet&amp;utm_campaign=core-5-tips-mobile-infographic-q42014&gt;, for a short list of considerations as you embark on your own mobile odyssey.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/5-tips-for-building-engaging-data-driven-mobile-apps-infographic?utm_source=Twitter&amp;utm_medium=tweet&amp;utm_campaign=core-5-tips-mobile-infographic-q42014&gt;
EPISODE #8: A Chat About Microservices with Matt Stine, Wednesday, NOVEMBER 26TH
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt; this week for &apos;A Chat About Microservices with Matt Stine&apos;, Episode #8 of our ongoing podcast series.

We will focus on continuous delivery and Microservices, which is very much a topic du jour in software architecture and design circles.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
FROM SEA TO TREES, PIVOTAL DATA SCIENCE LOOKS AT CLIMATE CHANGE IN ACADIA NATIONAL PARK: DAY 1 FIELD REPORT
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/from-sea-to-trees-pivotal-data-science-looks-at-climate-change-in-acadia-national-park-day-1-field-report&gt;
Data science is being used to transform the way we measure the world around us, particularly in the area of climate change. In the first post of this series, Pivotal’s Senior Data Scientist, Srivatsan Ramanujam, shares a journal of his trip to Acadia National Park to work with a cross functional team from Pivotal, EMC, Earthwatch, and Schoodic Research Institute, improving the way they collect and analyze data within the context of a data lake.

READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/from-sea-to-trees-pivotal-data-science-looks-at-climate-change-in-acadia-national-park-day-1-field-report&gt;
CASE STUDY: 300% INCREASE IN APP PERFORMANCE WITH INDIA RAIL ON PIVOTAL GEMFIRE
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/case-studies-2/case-study-300-increase-in-app-performance-with-india-rail-on-pivotal-gemfire&gt;
With India’s massive online population growth, the e-ticketing systems supporting India Rail faced a major challenge with scale. At a recent forum in India, the team responsible for the applications explained how they overcame the scale and other issues with Pivotal GemFire, tripling application throughput.

READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/case-studies-2/case-study-300-increase-in-app-performance-with-india-rail-on-pivotal-gemfire&gt;
- Cloud Computing Continues Accelerating in the Enterprise &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/louiscolumbus/2014/11/22/cloud-computing-adoption-continues-accelerating-in-the-enterprise/&gt;
 - How Data Scientists are Changing the Face of Business Intelligence &lt;http://thenextweb.com/dd/2014/11/23/data-scientists-changing-face-business-intelligence/&gt;
 - How Big Data Analytics Creates Order Out Of Chaos &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/teradata/2014/11/25/how-big-data-analytics-creates-order-out-of-chaos/&gt;
 - 5 Ways To Apply &apos;Agile&apos; To Customer Relationships &lt;http://www.informationweek.com/strategic-cio/enterprise-agility/5-ways-to-apply-agile-to-customer-relationships/a/d-id/1317699&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
