<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pivotal IT Comm.4-16 Announcement CC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>An Important Message from Pivotal IT</subject>
    <textOnly>To all Pivotal:
Our Pivotal IT team has been working hard for you as always, and we have a few important updates to share.  To use your time more effectively, we’ve consolidated these announcements into a single communication.  Please take the time to read below to benefit from these changes.
EMC Employee Calendar Free-Busy Sharing in Google
Do you get frustrated when you try to schedule a meeting with your EMC colleagues because you can’t see their free-busy details and you have to call them, or go back-and-forth multiple times to find a day and time that works?   Yeah, me too!  
 Good news, we’ve worked closely with EMC IT to enable sharing of free-busy calendar details from EMC.  Now, when you enter an EMC email address into your Google Calendar meeting requests, you can use the “Suggested Times” function, or view the calendar for all attendees, including EMC employees, to select a suitable meeting time.  What will you do with all the extra hours in your day now?!  
It doesn’t yet work the other way, where EMC employees can see our free-busy details, but we are working on it.
Pivotal Wi-Fi at EMC Offices
We’ve also been working closely with EMC IT to provide a “Pivotal-like” cloud experience for our users that work from EMC offices, either full-time or when visiting.  You may have recently noticed that a “Pivotal” SSID has appeared in EMC offices and you are probably asking yourself, “That sounds awesome!  How do I get on that?”  Well, it is now ready to go so we’ve created some instructions on how to connect to it.  Please access the instructions here &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/pivotal-it/emc-systems/pivotal-wifi&gt;.  Enjoy full access to your Pivotal cloud applications from EMC offices without the need to configure a proxy or install additional software!
Socialcast Changes Coming
Last, Pivotal will be expanding our deployment of Socialcast this week.  As part of the effort to expand our use of this powerful communication tool, and to prepare for single sign-on with Okta (fewer passwords!), we will be enrolling the remainder of all employees who have not yet signed up for the service.  If you are a new user, when your account is set up, you will receive an email inviting you to the Pivotal Socialcast community.  Please take a moment to click the signup link in this email and complete your registration.  If you&apos;re already a Socialcast user, no action is required (but feel free to welcome your colleagues into the service as they join!) 
 
Thanks for reading all the way to the bottom of this email!  As always, if you have any questions – please direct them to askIT@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:askIT@gopivotal.com&gt;
 
Regards,

Chris Curtis
Vice President IT</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
