<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.5-20-2015 Customer Info App</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Customer Info App is here!</subject>
    <textOnly>Colleagues,

After much anticipation, and development that involved Pivotal Labs, Pivotal IT and Pivotal Global Operations, the Customer Info App is available to the Pivotal Field, for both iOS and Android devices, via Pivotal Lab’s AppTime store &lt;https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fapps.pivotallabs.com%2F&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNFqQiPeLnDQ1D3N_q4BZVCuXrOZig&gt; (you can log in through Okta).

As demoed at the Sales Kickoff in February &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0B1rVqn9ifV69ekZkUmpnUHF4Wm8/view&gt;, and developed by Pivotal Labs, the Customer Info App provides field teams with a 360 degree view of customer account activity, including forecast opportunities, and history 
of product installations and customer support activity.

Leveraging The Pivotal Big Data Suite, Pivotal Cloud Foundry and our Mobile Services, this is a great new tool for the field, and one to show current and prospective customers how the Pivotal portfolio helps drive 
great apps that drive the business!

To get the app and use its demo mode for customers, please do the following:


 - Follow these instructions &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/document/d/1QF8uLKO9P_zrs0HZgszyM1ZdsZ-njFCu1URqL4vp-V8/edit?usp=sharing&gt; to install the app via AppTime.
 - Once installed, review your account information, and familiarize yourself with the ‘Demo Mode’ version of the app to show off its features to customers.

 - Our user guides and documentation &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/document/d/1p5USTs5Dj3qwzHJApQnlf5bVRGIrYdzzmp2bBx8ZUgo/edit?usp=sharing&gt; provide details on the app, and if you have any questions, please post them to the Customer Info App &lt;https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fgopivotal-com.socialcast.com%2Fgroups%2F121820-customerinfoapp&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNELFHlUuYsHoAl29z-no0mkD9BY9w&gt; page on Socialcast.



The Customer Info App is one example of Pivotal investing in our best resources to help you succeed in the field. The tool is being jointly supported by Field Ops and Pivotal IT. Please feel free to contact the team with any questions at AskIT@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:AskIT@pivotal.io&gt;.

Good selling in closing Q2 and beyond, and BE BOLD!

Todd Paoletti</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
