<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>APJ_SG_Insurance Demand Generation_Q414.01 Invite Email Revised</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Capitalize on Big Data and Analytics Solutions for the Insurance Industry</subject>
    <textOnly>Capitalize on Big Data &amp; Analytics Solutions for the Insurance Industry
 
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Sir/ Madam}},
The insurance industry is experiencing significant pressure and change: insurers are adapting to slower demand in mature markets while reacting to growth challenges in emerging markets. Customers are increasingly more sophisticated in their knowledge of insurance products and are expecting simpler yet more personalized products. Social media and multi-channel interactions make it increasingly challenging to acquire and manage customers.
Introduce Business Data Lake and Big Data Suite
 
 The Principles of Business Data Lake &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/sites/default/files/The_Principles_of_the_Business_Data_Lake_2013-12-02_V07_WEB.pdf&gt;
 
 Pivotal Big Data Suite Datasheet &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/datasheet/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt;
This presents tremendous opportunities for insurance players to create new approaches to containing costs, accelerating time-to-market, and improving both product design and customer services. To achieve this, deep insight into customers and operations must be combined with business agility and innovation.



Pivotal’s real-time and predictive analytics platform has helped many world’s leading financial services and insurance companies achieved the ultimate goal of better understanding, attracting and retaining valuable customers.



Please check out our Big Data Analytics solutions by downloading these whitepapers.

• The Principles of Business Data Lake &lt;http://info.pivotal.io/I060QI00N00rAC20090UJ00&gt;

• Pivotal Big Data Suite Datasheet &lt;http://info.pivotal.io/tCJ02009I00Ns00AU00006R&gt;



If you’d like more information, please contact us. &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/contact&gt;
Sincerely,

Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
