<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.PM 1-21 V2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Executive Leadership Org Changes and Additions *****UPDATE -  Please find updated Org Chart Link Below*****</subject>
    <textOnly>*****UPDATE - Please find updated Org Chart Link Below*****  

 &lt;https://www.pivotalinitiative.com&gt;Dear Colleagues, 
As a follow up to the “Agenda for 2014 &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/document_repository/FINAL_Mission_2014_Final_to_proof_010814af.pdf?attredirects=0&amp;d=1&gt;” document that I recently sent out, I wanted to share some changes and additions we are making at the Executive Leadership level. I am a strong believer that great teams are lead by great teams – that is, teams of leaders whose capabilities, styles, and areas of focus complement each other and who, through mutual respect, empower each other. As noted in my agenda document, we need to get the best out of each other, and the changes below are designed to do this.

With a focus on the day-to-day running of the company, I have asked Bill Cook and Scott Yara to perform as co-Presidents of Pivotal.


 - Bill Cook’s title will be President and COO. He will focus on and own the responsibilities of Field Operations, Finance, HR, Corporate Development, Legal, and Facilities/Real Estate.




 - Scott Yara’s title will be President and Head of Products. He will focus on and own responsibility for R&amp;D, Product Marketing, Marketing, IT and our new Pivotal Data Labs group. Additionally, for those who were not aware, Scott is also a member of the Pivotal Board of Directors.


Rob Mee, SVP, will continue to focus on and own leading Pivotal Labs and Cloud Foundry.
The above three folks formally report to me.

In addition, I would like to recognize three members of our executive staff who each have extraordinary duties in their respective business roles, reporting to Bill Cook:


 - Scott Aronson, SVP, Worldwide Field Operations
 - Leo Spiegel, SVP, Corporate Development
 - Robert O’Donovan, CFO


I would also like to welcome Hugh Williams &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/press-center/01152014-hugh-williams&gt;, our new SVP of R&amp;D, reporting to Scott Yara. As you have already heard, Hugh joins us by way of eBay, Microsoft and RMIT University. He is a remarkable talent and will have great impact on our future.
The org chart of the entire executive team can be seen here &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDo1YmRkZjBlMzE4ZmU1MjEy&gt;.
So what does this leave me to do? This will enable me to focus my time on overall strategy for the company, evangelism with partners and customers, and to providing support and advice to the above persons, and all the other great people who comprise Pivotal.
I would also like to take this opportunity to identify Julie Mercurio as the overall leader of our great group of Executive and Administrative Assistants.
Thanks,














Follow Us: Twitter &lt;http://www.twitter.com/gopivotal&gt; | LinkedIn &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/gopivotal&gt; | Facebook &lt;http://www.facebook.com/gopivotal&gt; | Google+ &lt;https://plus.google.com/105320112436428794490&gt;




© Pivotal - FOR INTERNAL USE ONLY - DO NOT DISTRIBUTE.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
