<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_EMC World_2015.EMC World Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank You for Joining Pivotal at EMC World</subject>
    <textOnly>EVENT NAME
Tagline
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=There}},

Thanks for visiting Pivotal at EMC World &lt;http://pivotal.io/emc-world&gt; in Las Vegas. We hope you enjoyed learning how enterprises are using Digital Transformation to drive modern, software experiences for their customers. 

In case you missed anything, here’s a quick recap:


 



 - Keynote Recording – Pivotal CEO, Paul Maritz joined Joe Tucci and Pat Gelsinger to present a session &lt;http://www.emcworld.com/emctv.htm?id=4232088673001&gt; about Enterprise Hybrid Cloud, PaaS, Big Data and Digital 
Transformation.

 - Key Interviews – Bill Cook &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VdwiBBzVPOA&gt; spoke with EMCTV about how Pivotal is helping customers on their transformational journeys.  Additionally, Michael Cucchi &lt;https://youtu.be/MpH_F5ze-Dc?list=PLenh213llmcbskhko-e7sAeEKZYETuJGE&gt; and Craig Steel &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eWgH_I02Y4c&gt; were 
interviewed on theCUBE.

 - Announcements – There was big news for Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;https://pivotal.io/big-data/press-release/pivotal-big-data-suite-accelerates-digital-transformation&gt;, with major performance and feature improvements, as well as 
Open Data Platform integration.

 - Posts – Read blogs about the latest updates to Pivotal HAWQ &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/p-o-v/pivotal-hawq-lands-in-the-hortonworks-sandbox&gt; and upgrades to Pivotal Greenplum Database &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/products/greenplum-database-adds-the-pivotal-query-optimizer&gt;.



Want more? 


 


 - Turbocharge data science &lt;https://www.brighttalk.com/webcast/9573/155785?utm_partnersource=Pivotal&gt; with Pivotal HAWQ and the Hortonworks Data Platform.

 - Come see Pivotal in action at a Pivotal Big Data Roadshow &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/data-roadshow&gt; or Pivotal Cloud Platform Roadshow &lt;http://pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/cloud-platform-roadshow&gt; near you.
 - Visit Pivotal Training &lt;http://pivotal.io/training/emc-world&gt; to learn about our education and certification programs.



By unifying big 
data, cloud &lt;https://pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/pivotal-cloud-foundry&gt; and agile product 
development, Pivotal is providing the platform for  Digital Transformation and shaping the future for modern enterprises.

We look forward to seeing you at the next Pivotal 
event &lt;https://pivotal.io/news-events&gt;! 

The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
