<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.9-2-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Pivotal on Your Cloud Native Journey</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of August 31, 2015
&lt;http://pivotal.io/cloud-native?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;
Join Pivotal on Your Cloud Native Journey
On Monday during the VMworld keynote, we announced intent to deliver Pivotal Cloud Foundry with the VMware Photon Platform as an integrated solution for Cloud Native Applications &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/next-gen-cloud-native-platform-vmware-photon-pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt; - an IaaS built for Cloud Native workloads embedded with Pivotal Cloud Foundry. This is an exciting moment for us—it signals an important milestone in the evolution of cloud technology. With this solution, companies will fundamentally transform how they deliver and run custom enterprise software for the next decade.



We also launched a new online destination to begin your cloud native journey. Visit the Cloud Native microsite &lt;http://pivotal.io/cloud-native?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt; to learn why it matters, what it looks like and how to become cloud native.
VIEW NOW &lt;http://pivotal.io/cloud-native?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;
Pivotal Cloud Foundry
Next-Gen Cloud Native Platform: VMware Photon + Pivotal Cloud Foundry
August 31, 2015
Pivotal and VMware are announcing our intent to deliver Pivotal Cloud Foundry with the VMware Photon Platform as an integrated solution for Cloud Native Applications. The joint solution will represent a complete, turn-key Cloud Native platform for our customers. This post explains what the Photon Platform is, the significant value it adds and why it marks an important milestone in the evolution of cloud technology.
 

Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/products/next-gen-cloud-native-platform-vmware-photon-pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;
All About Concourse For Continuous Integration
September 02, 2015
This week we take a look at Continuous Integration tooling, with a particular focus on the Concourse open source project. We will review the key design principals behind this software that makes it so attractive to developers, including specifically to our Pivotal Cloud Foundry developers around the globe.

 
Subscribe &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-perspectives/features/all-about-concourse-for-continuous-integration?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;
Data Science
This Month in Data Science: August 2015
August 31, 2015
In the month of August, as students prepare to return to school, big data’s increasing impact upon the college admissions process came to light. Data science’s role in transforming the economies of developing nations was considered, and Twitter’s Sid Patil revealed how his probabilistic approach to Blackjack influenced his data science practice.



Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/this-month-in-data-science-august-2015?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-9-2-15&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
