<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.4-22-15 CF Summit Member Competition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Help us Win the Cloud Foundry Summit Member Competition</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

As a Platinum sponsor and the company that launched the event, Pivotal will be at the Cloud Foundry Summit &lt;http://www.cfsummit.com/&gt; in force, hosted for the first time by the Cloud Foundry 
Foundation. We have ten Pivotal Cloud Foundry customers &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/ten-pivotal-customers-to-speak-at-cloud-foundry-summit&gt; - including Allstate, Comcast, Verizon, GE, Corelogic, Lockheed Martin, Humana, and 
others, in addition to many Pivotal experts, who will showcase the value of Pivotal Cloud Foundry to your prospects.

Share this registration link with your prospects, customers, and partners, and encourage them to attend the Summit: bit.ly/cfsummitreg &lt;bit.ly/cfsummitreg&gt;

And here’s more incentive. The Cloud Foundry Foundation is offering prizes to the member company that helps sell the most Summit tickets through referrals. They will give 5 iPad Minis to a team from the winning Member company.

We need you to help Pivotal come out on top, and here’s how it works:


 - Cloud Foundry Foundation has allocated 250 tickets to the Summit for this competition.
 - Have your prospects register for the Summit and select the “Referred By” field on the reg form.
 - Once all 250 tickets are allocated and the winning company is determined, we’ll map registrants back to you, and the 5 sales reps with the most customers will be the winning team.
 - All referral registrations must be completed by midnight PT on May 10. Here’s the link again bit.ly/cfsummitreg &lt;bit.ly/cfsummitreg&gt;



Finally, help spread the word and use your social channels. Go to Inside Pivotal Cloud Foundry Summit &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/events/cloud-foundry-summit-2015&gt; page to find out how.

I look forward to seeing our customers at the 
Summit.

Be bold!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
