<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.James Watters 8-27-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Cloud Platform Strategy and Org Update</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

Last fall, to extend our mission to change how customers create and run cloud native applications, we brought together our Cloud Foundry product team and the Spring team. 

Since then, Pivotal Cloud Foundry has set sales records for a new open source product, and the Spring team has managed the explosive adoption of our new cloud-focused Java 
development technologies, Spring Boot and Spring Cloud. Together these  technologies have been at the heart of our customers’ exciting cloud native journey &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/features/mapping-the-cloud-native-journey&gt;. 

While Spring has always been popular with enterprise developers, newer patterns of continuous delivery and microservices have opened the door for a new player in the market—not one that offers a less expensive solution than IBM and Oracle, but one that represents a true generational shift forward. With the growth of the cloud-friendly Spring Boot and Spring Cloud running on PCF, more and more top enterprises see Pivotal as the leader in cloud native java technologies, and are making their strategic investment with us. The opportunities for PCF and Spring Boot/Cloud together have become enormous.  

With so many customers turning to Pivotal as their cloud native partner, we’re bringing more great talent into our Cloud Platform organization. As detailed in Bill Cook’s organization announcement &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/corporate-marketing/corporate-communications/news-archive/bcookorgnote&gt;, 
Ian Andrews, Dino Ciccarelli, and Raghvender Arni have joined our team, working for me directly. 

Our strategy in the second half is simple: to make our hyper-growth, cloud native java on stack on PCF the number one choice for enterprises around the world to create, deliver and manage cloud 
native applications. 

To support this mission, we’ll see significant growth in our technology evangelism teams and capabilities in order to double down on delivering inspiring technical workshops for our top 
prospects and customers. As our team has been ‘oversold’ on delivering workshops, I’ve asked Andrew Shafer to focus full-time on growing this world-class team, who will work along with field engineering to inspire our technical champions with hands-on 
sessions, speaking engagements and events. 

The success of these workshops has created incredible demand for field engineering and consulting talent to help customers migrate to a true cloud native enterprise applications and technology stack. Working together, Arni and Dino will grow our Cloud Platform field engineering and consulting organizations. To help Dino’s team rapidly expand their bench, I’ve asked Ryan Morgan and his Spring organization to help them hire a team of cloud native application architects who will work onsite with customers migrate to our stack. This team will also be working closely with Pivotal Labs CTO Michael Barinek to ensure consistency across Labs and the Cloud Platform team. 

For our business to achieve its lofty financial goals, we must improve the productivity of our field sales organization. I can’t think of a better bridge than Ian Andrews to help our sales organization grow our business through the right messaging, plays, and pricing tactics. In addition to leading Cloud Foundry Product Marketing, I’ve asked Ian to oversee technology partnerships and business development. There is no surer way to drive a partner strategy than through sales and customer channels. To that end Nima Badiey will join Ian’s team and continue his work on technology partnerships and our GTM meeting cadence. Josh McKenty will also move into the product organization and continue to report to Ian. Josh will be joined in his strategic customer work by Dekel Tankel and Farhan Thawar on Ian’s team. 

Cornelia Davis continues to lead our Platform Engineering team, technically advancing our top partners/customers, helping with field engineering enablement and continue reporting to me. Her team recently helped Tibco create a PCF version of their integration suite software, as they realize they need to transform to cloud native lifecycle management and operations in their products in order to compete. 

James Bayer remains in charge of all PCF product management. James will be growing his team in the second half to expand our already world-leading functionality, and our reach with enterprise customers. Between the imminent delivery of .NET support, built-in APM, PWS-E expansion, and a now fully integrated set of Spring Cloud services, our product story continues to go from strength to strength. 

Pivotal is on a mission to transform how the world builds software. We will win by making our customers successful in this industry-changing transition to cloud native platforms and applications. I look forward to working with all of you to make the second half of 2015 a great one for Pivotal!

James</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
