<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.GS - Monthly Announcement - March 2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Field Operations: January Sales News Flash</subject>
    <textOnly>PIVOTAL FIELD OPERATIONS
A Message from Greg Stroud
MARCH 2015 SALES NEWS FLASH
Global Field Operations Team,

Now that we are nearing end-of-quarter, please take the time to read this communication carefully; as there are a number of federation engagement, process, and product updates that you should be aware of. 

2015 Rules of Engagement Update

EMC reps will now receive commission on Pivotal software sold on VMware paper. It must be a registered deal and pivotal has to agree that the EMC rep helped advance the deal in order for that rep to be compensated. EMC will be implementing a registration process for commission only eligible products, effective from Q2’15 forward. For more information on rules of engagement, please read through the complete deck, here &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/presentation/d/1VK7wZ0Rxw4BrE3Qw0zElOX9P23wbJQfa6sug6FVyLX0/edit#slide=id.g77b7345f3_2_89&gt;. 

Compensation Tool Updates

GAFs will continue to rollout through the end of March. Please note that you will only receive access to Callidus once your GAFs are available to review and approve. On a technical note, Callidus is integrated with SFDC and is single-sign on. If you ever see a screen asking you for a username &amp; password, you have most likely been timed-out of the tool. Please re-click on the Callidus tab within SFDC to refresh your page.

SFDC – Named Accounts, Changes &amp; New Responsibilities

This quarter, Sales is moving to a named account strategy where Accounts will be categorized (named or focused) and assigned an owner. The program will be supported by the GEO Business Managers and tracked in Salesforce.  These new account attributes will enable us to report on our success, Lead through Opportunity, for these identified accounts. You can read the complete list of enhancements to SFDC here &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/document/d/1zMrAOEijOZ9yxAHQ3iEjjA5cV8atOlPAy8tw7XNGYAk/edit#heading=h.n6wr07pub2sf&gt;.

Immediate 
Benefits. All SFDC Users may now:


 - Run a list of your accounts
 - See current Sales Rep Coverage of an account
 - View all event attendees, regardless of their status as either a Lead or a Contact
 - Have a real-time list of named accounts!!!



Reference Edge Update – Labs Sales

We will soon be rolling out Reference Edge to the Labs Sales Field. This is a new system within Salesforce we&apos;re using to track which clients can be used as references for other clients. The system also allows you to accumulate points that you can redeem for prizes. The 2014 prizewinner was Joe Hold, who received a Rolex watch at SKO for his participation in the customer reference program.

Megan Wheeler will be following up with Labs reps for customers we&apos;d like to have as references within the tool. Sophia Tseng is managing the program for Core reps.

Here are some helpful links with more information on the system and how to accumulate points:


 - Session presentation &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0B5ObkKTwRMwEUzFERXp0aGNuNnc/view?usp=sharing&gt;
 - Customer stories repository &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/assets/external-slides&gt;
 - More training &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/references/reference-system&gt;



CF Mobile Services Sizing 

Please note that the Mobile Services team will be hosting a webinar on Thursday, April 9 to 
provide an overview of their product offerings. There is a new Mobile Services Sizing Tool &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/spreadsheets/d/16_KIiKINvqK8eTRciC7AOcckVEGkDJnTN2ONEHxaHCo/edit&gt; that can be used to assess the number of instances needed based on customer requirements. For any questions on sizing and pricing deals please email cfms-pm@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:cfms-pm@pivotal.io&gt;.

Customer Success Update – What’s 
New

Customer Success offers two account-focused complementary offerings (TAMs &amp; DSEs) that are committed to the ongoing health and success of Pivotal’s strategic customers.  A combination of both resources ensures the highest level of success; 
however, the appropriate balance of offerings are customer and opportunity dependent.



 - Technical Account Managers (TAM) - Proactive account-level technical resource focused on Pivotal technology enablement and adoption, deriving maximum business value from Pivotal technology, and ongoing account assessment to ensure success. Emphasis is on early lifecycle planning, customer enablement, and access to Pivotal resources to guarantee the most optimal and impactful deployment of Pivotal technology.
 - Designated Support Engineers (DSE) - Technical resource, which compliments Pivotal premium support by providing highly personalized technical expertise. DSE&apos;s provide operational best practices, regular account feedback, and account continuity that customers rely upon to operate business or mission critical applications at scale.



Additional program details and contact information can be found on Inside Pivotal, here: Customer Service 
Offerings.

Be Bold!
Greg</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
