<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Paul Priorities 11-20-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Our Priorities and Our People</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Colleagues,

At our last company update meeting in October, we laid out how we are responding to the opportunities and challenges before us. We said that our priorities needed to be:


 - Get all parts of Pivotal working towards enabling our customers to drive new business value from new uses of apps and data in the Cloud era,
 - To focus on our areas of strength and advantage,
 - To either lead or align with well-functioning open source ecosystems,
 - To build out Cloud Foundry and associated services into a true platform,
 - To move to a common “Labs-inspired” development culture and team,
 - To build towards a valuable, “IPO-worthy” business.



As we do this refocusing we unfortunately have team members who no longer fit into the above mission, and this week we are informing the affected people. As I have said before, how we do things is as important as what we do. So it is important that we show fairness and respect to these folk and thank them for their contributions to date. We have active work under way with our Federation and other key partners to offer new positions to as many individuals as possible.

Also in keeping with the above priorities, as we indicated in October, you will see us in the near future:


 - More strongly align our Big Data Suite with open source. We believe that this will help unlock the value we have in such components as HAWQ and GemFire, as well as enable us to become more aggressive in general.
 - “Double down” on Cloud Foundry, where we have tremendous potential.
 - Obtain further leverage from Labs engagements to pull through the above capabilities.



I thank you all for your effort and contributions to date, and ask for your help and understanding as we take these steps.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
