<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.4-20-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of April 20, 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of April 20, 2015
&lt;http://projectgeode.org/&gt;
PIVOTAL ANNOUNCES PROJECT GEODE
Last week, at ApacheCon in Austin, Pivotal announced &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/press-release/pivotal-releases-geode&gt; the creation of “Geode”, the new in-memory distributed database that forms the open source core of Pivotal GemFire &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-gemfire&gt;. As part of this announcement, Pivotal has  submitted a proposal to The Apache Software Foundation &lt;https://wiki.apache.org/incubator/GeodeProposal&gt; (ASF) to establish and incubate Project Geode.

Pivotal will contribute to, support and help build the Project Geode community while simultaneously producing its commercial distribution of Pivotal GemFire. 

Pivotal GemFire started as a high speed caching tool for a new generation of super fast financial services electronic trading systems and customers include many no-longer independent investment banks &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/case-study/sbi-securities-achieving-significant-roi-with-improved-performance-and-scalability&gt;, large scale travel reservation systems &lt;http://pivotal.io/customers/indianrailways&gt;, and airlines &lt;http://pivotal.io/customers/southwest&gt;.


 - Want to contribute and find out more about Geode? Check out ProjectGeode.com &lt;http://projectgeode.org/&gt;.
 - Ready to engage with Pivotal to scale your applications now? Go to Pivotal GemFire &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-gemfire&gt;.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://www.projectgeodge.org&gt;
TUESDAY, APRIL 21ST, &quot;CHIP CHILDERS AND THE CLOUD FOUNDRY FOUNDATION&quot;
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us this week for our latest episode of our All Things Pivotal Podcast Series, &quot;Chip Childers and the Cloud Foundry Foundation&quot;.

Michael Coté talks to Chip Childers of the Cloud Foundry Foundation about his career in IT from SunGard to CloudStack, what he does at the Cloud Foundry Foundation, and what the Foundation does.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/podcasts-pivotal&gt;
TEN PIVOTAL CUSTOMERS TO SPEAK AT CLOUD FOUNDRY SUMMIT MAY 11-12
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/ten-pivotal-customers-to-speak-at-cloud-foundry-summit&gt;
In less than a month 1,500 of Cloud Foundry community members will come together in Santa Clara, California for the 3rd annual Cloud Foundry® Summit &lt;http://www.cfsummit.com&gt;. Having been at every Summit since its inception, we’ve had a front row seat to the community’s growth and can tell you this will be far and away, the best Summit yet.


READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/ten-pivotal-customers-to-speak-at-cloud-foundry-summit&gt;
PIVOTAL DATA SCIENCE TEAM ITERATES FASTER, BEATS EXISTING MALWARE DETECTION TOOLS
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/pivotal-data-science-team-iterates-faster-beats-existing-malware-detection-tools&gt;
This post provides a case study in innovative IT security practices for a small, 6-week project. The challenges, approach, and outcomes of this data science-driven effort show how an innovative use of algorithms can do a better job detecting malware than existing, best-in-class malware detection tools and operate much faster than existing customer models within Apache Hive™.

 READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/pivotal-data-science-team-iterates-faster-beats-existing-malware-detection-tools&gt;
- VMware open sources IAM, cloud OS tools &lt;http://www.businesscloudnews.com/2015/04/21/vmware-open-sources-iam-cloud-os-tools/&gt;
 - HortonWorks, IBM, Pivotal Align Hadoop Platforms on ODP Core &lt;http://www.eweek.com/enterprise-apps/hortonworks-ibm-pivotal-align-hadoop-platforms-on-odp-core.html&gt;
 - Surge in real-time big data and IoT analytics is changing corporate thinking &lt;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/surge-in-real-time-big-data-and-iot-analytics-is-changing-corporate-thinking/&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
