<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Event_SpringOne2GX2013.SpringOne 2GX 2013 9-4 Registrants only Email Send</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>SpringOne 2GX 2013 - What to expect at the event</subject>
    <textOnly>WHAT TO EXPECT AT THE EVENT
Not to be missed at SpringOne 2GX (details below):

 - Visit the Pivotal Lounge and Demo Lounge for expresso drinks and technical experts

 - Sponsor receptions with cocktails and snacks

 - Mon 4:30-5:30pm and 8-9:30pm
 - Tues from 6pm-7pm 

 - Birds-of-a-feather sessions with key developers 

 - Tues from 9pm-10pm

 - Game night with cards, games and beer! 

 - Wed from 7-10pm

 - Cool free stuff you do not want to miss!
Pivotal Demo Lounge
Visit the Demo Lounge (Hyatt 2nd floor) for espresso drinks and Pivotal commercial technology:

 - Pivotal Application Products - Talk with the experts, or just play with: 

 - Spring XD, for fast data collection, transformation, analysis &amp; ingestion
 - Pivotal HD, for big data analysis using standard SQL
 - RabbitMQ, for sensor data collection and distribution with MQTT &amp; AMQP
 - GemFire XD, for fast in-memory data grids

 - Pivotal Cloud Foundry - Did you know Cloud Foundry was made with Spring in mind? Stop by the Demo Lounge and ask for a Cloud Foundry demo to see how easy it is to deploy your Spring app to the cloud with no code chances.

 - Pivotal Training - How up-to-date are your Spring skills? What about the rest of your team? Come visit the Spring training team in the Pivotal Lounge. Learn about our extensive training offerings and certification program. We&apos;ve trained over 20,000 people on Spring technologies!

 - Pivotal Consulting - Talk to us about how we can help your organization get the most out of Spring! Experts available to discuss our rich history doing implementations of the Spring Framework, ranging from very large business transformations (Large Insurance Company in the mid-West) to targeted service modernization for the online store of a large technology company based in Cupertino. We have a very deep set of expertise on our team to provide everything fro Reference Architecture work to hands-on implementation across all facets of the Spring Framework. 

Sponsor Receptions:  Mon 4:30-5:30pm and 8:00-9:30pm, Tues 6-7pm

Join us for cocktails and dessert hosted by the SpringOne 2GX This is an excellent opportunity for you to understand how our partners can help optimize the building, running and managing of Spring-powered applications or deploying in the cloud. Come mingle with speakers and network with other conference attendees.

Birds-of-a-feather sessions: Tues 9-10pm
Join key developers in the respective areas for information and open discussions around the key technologies covered in the track.

Game night: Wed 7-10pm
Board games, Card games and beer! &apos;Nuff said. Bring your &apos;Magic the Gathering&apos; cards.
Cool free stuff you won&apos;t want to miss

 - Swing by the Pivotal Lounge Spring/Groovy/Grails table for an O&apos;Reilly eBook giveaway - Spring Data: Modern Data Access for Enterprise Java. Everyone gets a copy!

 - Prizes Prizes Prizes! Don&apos;t miss the Prizes Sheet in your attendee bag. It will explain the ways to get hoodies, buttons, vinyl decals, iPod touches, iPad minis, chocolates, headphones, messenger bags and more!

Looking forward to a great conference!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
