<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pivotal IT Comm.Casper V3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>An Important Message from Pivotal IT - Casper Update</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello to all Pivotal employees!



First, thank you for taking the time to enroll your computer with Casper. We&apos;re excited to roll out things like Self-Service for software and easy access to Pivotal VPN in the near future, and getting your machine enrolled helps us get those tools to you more easily. There have been a few issues that we know have been frustrating or confusing, so we wanted to give you an update on common questions:

Windows Computers



Given the difficulty resolving the Casper enrollment issue with Windows systems we&apos;re going to hold off enrolling them for now. If your primary and only system is Windows there&apos;s nothing more you need to do at the moment. We have a Windows-native management system coming soon and we&apos;d rather focus our efforts on that to provide the greatest benefit to our Windows users. Look for more news in the near future, and our apologies for the confusion.


Enrolling Contractors and Non-Pivotal Employees


A number of people have asked us if they should enroll their personal machine, or a machine managed by another company (EMC, VMware, etc.). In order to avoid management conflicts with partner companies, we only want to enroll Pivotal-owned computers with Casper.

Enrolling while connected to EMC&apos;s VPN/Network
EMC&apos;s firewall intentionally blocks traffic to other Casper servers, so trying to enroll while connected to EMC VPN or network will fail. Disconnecting from VPN or moving to a different network that has access to the open internet will allow you to enroll your computer with Casper.

Shoot an email to askIT@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:askIT@gopivotal.com&gt; if you have any questions or concerns.


Regards, 

Chris Curtis
Vice President IT</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
