<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Marketing Comms.Field Marketing Update 6-20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Field Update from Marketing</subject>
    <textOnly>June 20, 2014
Cloud Foundry Summit is a Wrap!
On June 11, Pivotal concluded the phenomenally successful Cloud Foundry Summit &lt;http://cfsummit.com&gt;. Close to 1,000 customers, members and developers from across the Cloud Foundry community gathered to discuss the current and future state of the industry&apos;s leading Open Source Platform-as-a-Service. The over 1,300 developer contributions to date, and wide range of ideas, confirm that Cloud Foundry is a game changer &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/cloud-foundry-pivotal/p-o-v/field-report-the-3-reasons-why-the-cfsummit-rocked&gt;. Session videos will be posted to the event site in the coming weeks, so stay tuned. 
Mark Your Calendar
Platform: The Pivotal Conference will take place on September 17-19 in San Francisco, CA. Additional information about the event will be available soon. For now…be sure to save the dates! 
What’s Next?
ACM SIGMOD/PODS Conference &lt;http://www.sigmod2014.org/&gt; (June 22-27 in Snowbird, UT)


 - Pivotal is exhibiting as a Gold Sponsor at this event.
 - Contact: Paul Santos &lt;mailto:psantos@gopivotal.com&gt;


Blog: Sigmod Paper: The Advantages of HAWQ (June 23)


 - A peer-reviewed paper on the results of a performance study of HAWQ, which was presented at the ACM SIGMOD/PODS Conference.
 - Contact: David Oro &lt;mailto:doro@gopivotal.com&gt;


Meetup: An Intro to Apache Spark (with Hadoop) for Plain Old Java Geeks &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Pivotal-Open-Source-Hub/events/184781662/&gt; (June 24 in Palo Alto, CA)


 - Pivotal is the organizer of this talk, which will provide an introduction to the principals and use of Apache Spark with a Hadoop/HDFS backend.
 - Contact: Tamao Nakahara &lt;mailto:tnakahara@gopivotal.com&gt;


Meetup: Cloud Foundry Application Security Groups with Mark Kropf &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Pivotal-Open-Source-Hub/events/183521842/&gt; (June 25 in San Francisco, CA)


 - Pivotal is the organizer of this talk, during which Mark Kropf will describe the work the Pivotal CF Runtime team is doing to implement application security groups.
 - Contact: Tamao Nakahara &lt;mailto:tnakahara@gopivotal.com&gt;


Spark Summit &lt;http://spark-summit.org/2014&gt; (June 30 - July 2 in San Francisco, CA)


 - Pivotal is exhibiting as a Silver Sponsor at this event. Conference passes may be purchased using discount code: Pivotal2014.
 - Contact: Paul Santos &lt;mailto:psantos@gopivotal.com&gt;


ACM SIGR Conference &lt;http://sigir.org/sigir2014/&gt; (July 6-11 in Gold Coast, Australia)


 - Pivotal is exhibiting as a Bronze Sponsor and Hugh Williams will be speaking at this event.
 - Contact: Paul Santos &lt;mailto:psantos@gopivotal.com&gt;


Pivotal Data Labs Webinar &lt;http://connect.gopivotal.com/Y0C080oA8000v002NUI0fJ2&gt; (July 8 at 9:00am, PDT)


 - Pivotal is partnering with Data Science Central to present this educational webinar. Ken Dowling will be speaking on the topic of Data Lakes.
 - Contact: Katherine Xavier &lt;mailto:kxavier@gopivotal.com&gt;


Meetup: Building a Distributed Data Ingestion System with RabbitMQ (July 16 in Palo Alto, CA &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Pivotal-Open-Source-Hub/events/187595852/&gt; and July 17 in San Francisco, CA &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Pivotal-Open-Source-Hub/events/187597992/&gt;)


 - Pivotal is the organizer of these talks, which will show what else RabbitMQ has to offer beyond simple messaging and queueing.
 - Contact: Tamao Nakahara &lt;mailto:tnakahara@gopivotal.com&gt;


OSCON &lt;http://www.oscon.com/oscon2014&gt; (July 20-24 in Portland, OR)


 - Pivotal is exhibiting as a Gold Sponsor and will have one speaking session at this event.
 - Contact: Tamao Nakahara &lt;mailto:tnakahara@gopivotal.com&gt;


VMworld 2014 US &lt;http://www.vmworld.com/community/conference/us&gt; (August 24-28 in San Francisco, CA)


 - Contact: Paul Santos &lt;mailto:psantos@gopivotal.com&gt;


EMC Forum &lt;http://hk.emc.com/campaign/global/forum2014/index.htm&gt; (September 5 in Hong Kong)


 - Pivotal is participating and will have speaking sessions at this event.
 - Contact: Sean Lee &lt;mailto:seanlee@gopivotal.com&gt; or Mica Tee &lt;mailto:mtee@gopivotal.com&gt; 


SpringOne 2GX &lt;http://springone2gx.com/&gt; (September 8-11 in Dallas, TX)


 - Pivotal is the event organizer and several Pivotal employees will be presenting sessions. 
 - Contact: Tamao Nakahara &lt;mailto:tnakahara@gopivotal.com&gt;


CIO Summit Singapore (September 19-21 in Singapore)


 - An EMC Federation-led event hosting 50 Global and Enterprise CIOs. Sean Lee will be representing Pivotal as a session speaker. Please note: Access to this event is by invitation only and strictly limited to the attending CIOs and speakers.
 - Contact: Katherine Xavier &lt;mailto:kxavier@gopivotal.com&gt;


Want more? Check out the News &amp; Events &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/news-events&gt;, Corporate Communications &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/departments/corporate-communications&gt; and Marketing Programs &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/pivotal-marketing-programs&gt; pages, and join us on Socialcast: @Marketing &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/79438-marketing&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
