<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NorthAm_Event_Denver_MeetUp_Q413.Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Meetup with Pivotal - The Art and Craft of Big Data Analytics - Oct 16</subject>
    <textOnly>Join Us. The Art and Craft of Big Data.
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},

On October 16, Pivotal will be hosting Boulder&apos;s Big Data Meetup &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Boulder-Denver-Big-Data/events/141972012/&gt;. Joined by industry leaders and experts, you will have an opportunity to connect and discuss with your peers around big data and analytics, customer use cases and exciting trends. The innovation and application of big data is an art form and not always transparent. Feeling crafty? Register now. &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Boulder-Denver-Big-Data/events/141972012/&gt; 
During this meet-up we will define and illustrate the five major sections of analytics and big data. We’ll describe use cases (examples) that demonstrate how this new analytics functionality can be applied to derive insights. We’ll then take a deep dive into an interesting use case that resonates with the audience, and expose what really happens at the developer level, and what is required to make these new “models” work. We’ll cover technologies such as R, SQL, Mahout, etc., and will detail how to operationalize a big-data analytics model. 
Pivotal is dedicated to setting a new standard for the industry – enabling businesses to store and analyze massive amounts of data cost-effectively, ingest huge numbers of events in real time, create insights with the data and events, and rapidly deliver applications and innovation to customers.
 &lt;http://www.meetup.com/Boulder-Denver-Big-Data/events/141972012/&gt;


I hope to see you there.

Best,

Ward Maddux
Check out Pivotal P.O.V.
Visit our Blog&gt;&gt; &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/&gt;
Read Pivotal&apos;s latest news.
Visit our Resources page&gt;&gt; &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/resources&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
