<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.SY - 8-21</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Cloud Platform Roadshow</subject>
    <textOnly>Team:

Pivotal has the opportunity to build the category-defining platform for next generation application deployment and operations for enterprises everywhere. We also have a following of developers, architects, operators, technical managers and executives around the world who are singing Cloud Foundry’s praises. Now is the time to lead this emerging market, and to help put our efforts into high gear, we’re kicking off a Cloud Platform 
Roadshow.

Through the Roadshow, we’re sending our Pivotal Cloud Foundry experts across the globe, spanning 15 cities from San Francisco to Munich between 19 August and 20 November. You’ll recognize most of those experts from our PaaS Business Team: James Watters, Matt Stine, Fred Melo, Jamie O’Meara, Austin Rutherford, and last, but not least, Andrew Clay Shafer &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/pivotal-people/pivotal-people-andrew-clay-shafer-devops-polymath-joins-pivotal&gt;.

Andrew reports into me and joined Pivotal about eight weeks ago, to drive technical thought leadership in the community, and to help meaningfully bring together the various strategic assets we have within the company across PaaS, Data and Labs. I’ve asked him to initially focus on leading our developer and operator community engagements and events. He is a thought-leader in agile, operations, devops, open source, and cloud computing. You might remember Andrew from his help and presence at our two Cloud Foundry conferences, and he has been instrumental in putting together our Cloud Platform Roadshow. 

In his own words:

“I joined Pivotal because I see Cloud 
Foundry’s potential for enterprises, where we package all the lessons learned from building modern application deployments, with architectures that scale. I’m still learning, but I see the opportunity to define a standard pipeline to deploy applications connecting data with people using agile methods as the confluence of everything I’ve worked on for the last decade. 

The Cloud Platform Roadshow is about Pivotal taking all the knowledge we have inside our walls and using it to build relationships and technical excellence in the Cloud Foundry community 
with hands on workshops focusing on the Pivotal product to support our mission in the field. The program and my understanding would not be possible without all the help I’ve had from Matt Stine, Cornelia Davis, Fred Melo, Jamie O’Meara, Austin Rutherford, James Bayer and obviously James Watters. I’d also like to call out Michelle Kerr and Michael Weir for their support and effort on the marketing and logistics. The roadshow is definitely a team effort, and my apologies for any errors of omission. I look forward to working together with all of them and the rest of you to make Pivotal successful.”

On behalf of myself, Rob, James, Andrew and the entire Executive Team, we wish everyone the best of luck!

-Scott</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
