<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Email_Data_Nurture_Q215.Email 2: Top Trends NEW</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>IT Transformation - Top Trends in Data Science</subject>
    <textOnly>EVENT NAME
Tagline
With a global team of 30 data scientists, doing innovative work in almost every vertical market, Pivotal has a rich view into the underlying trends and shifts impacting the industry. Below are some highlights of top trends in data science, identified by the Pivotal team.

The Shift from Point Solutions to Platforms
Companies today have their pick of point solutions to explore new opportunities to extract value from their data. But these are simultaneously introducing integration pain points that enterprises will increasingly reject. One of the key developments in data science we’re seeing evolve is the collective market savviness towards the importance and value of horizontal 
analytical platforms. 

Data and the Internet of Things
Expansive use of built-in sensing and computing capabilities are transforming businesses and industries. We are already seeing many additional interesting Internet of Things (IoT) &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/a-peek-under-the-hood-of-the-connected-car-what-it-does-how-it-applies-to-iot-systems?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=bigdata-targetaccount-nurture-q22015&gt; applications gain 
adoption. As the year progresses, companies of all types will look to sensors to instrument the physical world, and as such, will see an amazing richness in creative use cases for the data flowing in.

Hadoop Alone Is Not Enough
Data lake 
architecture is needed to house as much data as needed, all in one place. High-scale, real-time apps will need in-memory solutions. In other cases, enterprises need a relational layer to run SQL. In the months ahead, we’ll see enterprises move beyond Hadoop alone in order to power an ambitious data science strategy, and implement a data-science-centric platform and tool environment.

For additional trends, and a more in depth look at how they will impact enterprise 
organizations worldwide, check out Pivotal’s Top Trends in Data Science for 2015 blog &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/pivotals-top-predictions-for-data-science-and-big-data-in-2015?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=bigdata-targetaccount-nurture-q22015&gt; and webinar &lt;http://pivotal.io/agile/webinar/top-data-science-trends-for-2015-webinar?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=bigdata-targetaccount-nurture-q22015&gt;.

The Pivotal Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
