<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.TP - Q3-Q4 Announcement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Q3 Wins Analysis, Q3 Top Reps &amp; Reference Performance Report, Customer Podcasts, and more</subject>
    <textOnly>Congrats on Q3 and welcome to Q4. We&apos;ve continued analysis of top Pivotal CF and Big Data Suite wins &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/assets/external-slides&gt; this quarter with great stories at Discover, the NFL and more. As always, we&apos;ve created a scripted, anonymized external slide, and an internal win slide with full interview transcripts for each win.  

Q4 has gotten off to a quick start with some solid deals closing early in the quarter. We&apos;ve started a new program to announce deals over $250K as they happen, keeping the drumbeat going throughout the quarter on the @ringthebell channel on 
socialcast. Tune in for the latest and greatest on how we are winning in the market.

Brush up on your storytelling ability with our Customer Story Podcasts &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/assets/field-podcast-1&gt; which Neela Chaudhari released last quarter. Hear fellow reps tell their best customer stories in their own words and master your ability to tell these stories as well. 

Finally, thanks for your continued support of our reference program which was rolled out last quarter. You have been very collaborative with an almost 50% approval rate on requests. Our top reps last quarter were Raj Dosanjh, Paul Chesen, and Matthew Procise who each completed 3 requests in Q3!  Nice work gentlemen, and everyone keep it up. Find out more in the Q3 Reference Performance Report &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/references/reference-performance-report---q3&gt;.  

Setting up your client champions to speak with prospects and participate in marketing activity helps all of us and is necessary for us to reach the growth levels we&apos;ve planned for this year and next. To supercharge this--between now and FY2015 Sales kickoff, we&apos;re announcing 2 for 1 activity points on completed reference 
activity. So continue to log those reference requests and help out on requests. YOU could win that Rolex &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/references/2014-prize-catalog&gt;.  

If you have questions or comments on any of the above, please let Sophia Tseng &lt;mailto:stseng@pivotal.io&gt; know.  

Make it happen.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
