<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.May/June 2015 Webinar Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Improving Legacy Apps w/Spring; Debug &amp; Maintain Spring Boot Apps; Spring Showcase for Personal Cloud Storage Apps</subject>
    <textOnly>Improving your (legacy) Application with Spring
Speaker: Marten Deinum

Spring has been around since the release of “J2EE Design and Development” in 2002. Spring and Java have evolved quite a bit since that time. In those years a lot of applications have been developed. All those &quot;legacy&quot; applications that are around have proven their value and that is why they lasted.

In this session we will explore how we can improve our legacy applications by doing some refactoring or redesign (component based development) but also by introducing (newer) Spring IO technologies.
Europe
Tuesday, May 12, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMImprovingyourlegacyApplicationwithSpring_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, May 12, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMImprovingyourlegacyApplicationwithSpring_Register.html&gt;
Debug and Maintain your Spring Boot App
Speaker: Greg Turnquist, Pivotal

So you have decided to build an application using Spring Boot? Sooner or later, something will go wrong. It does not matter how experienced we are. How will Spring Boot help us figure out what went wrong and fix things?

This talk introduces lots of tools to help us debug and manage &quot;bootiful&quot; apps. You will learn how to use Boot&apos;s autoconfiguration report, override Boot&apos;s settings &amp; beans, create custom metrics/health checks/app info, and create custom JMX info &amp; custom CRaSH commands.
Europe
Thursday, May 28, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMDebugandMaintainyourSpringBootApp_Register.html&gt;
North America
Thursday, May 28, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMDebugandMaintainyourSpringBootApp_Register.html&gt;
A Comprehensive Spring Showcase: Personal Cloud Storage Application
Speaker: Erdem Gunay

Turkcell launched a personal cloud storage service few years ago. Adding new business features was costly in terms of time and budget on the legacy solution. The user experience needed to be improved. Finally, it was decided to build a new solution where Spring Boot and Spring Framework projects play crucial role as the backbone.

The project was completed just in 6 months starting from scratch. The solution was built on top of Spring Boot and many Spring IO Platform projects, allowing the development team focus on business logic instead of configuration &amp; integration details. The project has been divided into deployable modules (API, backend, migration, test automation) accessing micro services that are responsible for one task only. Join Erdem for a review of the migration effort and new architecture - all enabled by Spring Boot.
Europe
Tuesday, June 9, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMComprehensiveSpringShowcasePersonalCloudStorageApplication_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, June 9, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMComprehensiveSpringShowcasePersonalCloudStorageApp_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
