<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.6-8-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Acquires Quickstep</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of June 8, 2015
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/jignesh-patel-on-pivotals-acquisition-of-big-data-project-quickstep&gt;
Jignesh Patel on Pivotal&apos;s Acquisition of Big Data Project Quickstep
On Monday, Pivotal announced an exciting acquisition of Quickstep Technologies, big data query technology from the University of Wisconsin-Madison. As part of the acquisition, Professor Jignesh Patel will be joining Pivotal and starts his tenure here sharing why this is such a great move for Pivotal customers, the Quickstep technologies and himself.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/jignesh-patel-on-pivotals-acquisition-of-big-data-project-quickstep&gt;
Pivotal Cloud Foundry 1.4 - A Potted Tour
June 10, 2015
A platform is only useful to developers if it is kept up to date. What are the new features and capabilities in the PCF 1.4 release? Goodies include logging changes, security updates, AutoScaling and many more.

 
Listen Now &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/podcasts-pivotal&gt;
3 Biggest Questions Companies Have Before Starting to Tackle Apache Hadoop
June 5, 2015
After attending the Pivotal Big Data Roadshow in Atlanta, Pivotal’s Stacey Schneider validates that it is still early days for most companies on their journey to transform to a data-savvy technology company. Many attendees use the roadshow as a free orientation to starting this journey, and have many questions. Summarizing the 3 most popular questions from the event, she answers: How can I convince my org to start on big data now? Do I really have to run it? Is a Data Lake really all one big thing?


Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/p-o-v/3-biggest-questions-companies-have-before-starting-to-tackle-apache-hadoop&gt;
Allstate is Disrupting How Insurance Does Technology
May 27, 2015
During a keynote presentation at the Cloud Foundry Summit 2015, Andy Zitney, Senior Vice President of Infrastructure Services at Allstate, offered a wide-angle view of deploying disruptive technologies within a large enterprise. Zitney’s talk, “Developing the Freedom to Disrupt”, covered not only his experiences within the 90-year-old insurance company, but also his time working in financial services. Cloud Foundry has played a critical role in transforming how these companies innovate within a defined corporate structure, he explained.


Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/case-studies-2/allstates-andy-zitney-is-disrupting-how-insurance-does-technology&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
