<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Spring Exchange - 11/14.Spring Exchange UK 11/14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Spring Exchange Annual Conference in London - November 6-7th</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {{lead.First Name:default=There}},
Would you like to find out the latest with SpringIO, the widest used Java framework available? Fancy learning and sharing with like minded developers to tackle common problems?

JOIN US AT THE SPRING EXCHANGE &lt;https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014&gt;, THE ANNUAL CONFERENCE ON SPRING IN LONDON ON NOV 6-7TH

 Thanks to the great input and ideas contributed by our community and the support of Dave Syer and others, we have been able to put together a program that rocks! We&apos;re planning on three track over two days, covering Enterprise Java tech, Big Data and Spring XD, Spring in Production, SpringIO, Spring Data, REST and microservices. There&apos;s a beginners track for those just getting started too. At the end of day one, we&apos;re providing a unique forum to explore ideas about these topics with hundreds of other members of the Spring and Java community during our park bench panel discussion: this is an experience you won&apos;t get back at the office. So if you&apos;d like to spend the day learning all the newest tools and best practices in Java and Spring, to have meaningful conversations to help you write more powerful software, and to discover how to best deliver what your business needs, do come along!

CONFERENCE DETAILS 
WHAT: Spring eXchange 2014 &lt;https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014&gt;
WHEN: November 6-7th 
PROGRAM: https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014#program &lt;https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014#program&gt; 
TICKETS: https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014 &lt;https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014&gt;

 Featuring Dave Syer, Josh Long, Ben Hale, Russ Miles, Mark Pollack and other top experts in the Spring and Java community, this year will be the sixth anniversary of this cornerstone conference for the Spring and Java community - and it’ll be our best yet. Expect to meet members of the Pivotal Spring Framework team and to learn about the most comprehensive programming and configuration model for modern Java-based enterprise applications. Share your ideas with leading innovators in the Java movement: you can trust us to invite the best!

 After the success of last year, it was clear we needed a bigger venue for this year&apos;s Spring conference. So we have secured the BDC in Islington, where we will be able to accommodate London&apos;s sizeable and ever growing #springX community. With great spaces for talks and discussions, unrivalled technology capabilities and fantastic transport links in one of London&apos;s most buzzing areas, we could not think of a better venue to host this year&apos;s Spring eXchange.

REGISTRATION We&apos;re close to the event, so get your ticket and guarantee your spot at Spring eXchange 2014 &lt;https://skillsmatter.com/conferences/1941-spring-exchange-2014&gt;!

See you in November!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
