<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pivotal IT Comm.Spanning Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>An Important Message From Pivotal IT</subject>
    <textOnly>&gt;&gt; Introducing Spanning Backup

Mistakes happen, and sometimes we accidentally delete important email, documents, contacts, or calendar events. Pivotal IT has added the Spanning backup service to GoPivotal&apos;s Google Apps so that you can restore anything you might have deleted or corrupted. 
To restore a missing or corrupted email, document, contact, or calendar entry, visit here &lt;https://spanningbackup.com/?domain=gopivotal.com&gt; or simply click the &quot;Spanning Backup&quot; link under the More menu in your email interface.
 
 
&gt;&gt; What can Spanning do for you?
 
Let&apos;s make it easy! 
 Spanning can make your life easier by offering the following benefits: 


 - Point-in-time restore: This gives you the option to access historical versions of all data and restore the desired version of information. 

 - Metadata backup: This means that Spanning helps restore your data to its full and original state, including document directory structure, nested folders, site structure, sharing and permissions settings, and more. 

 - Email search and filter: This lets you easily find and select emails to be restored by date, label, sender, and subject line.

 Easily Restore any kind of Google Apps data

Check out these demo videos!
&gt;&gt; Restore lost Gmail &lt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WVNOFqwawkg&gt;

&gt;&gt; Restore Google Drive docs and folders &lt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j9-03Dje63k&gt;

&gt;&gt; Restore Google Calendars &lt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w7angsjlHHE&gt;

&gt;&gt; Restore Google Contacts &lt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZPnZvDJrAH8&gt;

&gt;&gt; Restore Google Sites &lt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RNv2qz_qlgE&gt;
 
Log in now &lt;http://www.spanningbackup.com/signin&gt; to check it out!
 
Questions? Email us &lt;mailto:askit@gopivotal.com&gt;. 



Follow Us: Twitter &lt;http://www.twitter.com/gopivotal&gt; | LinkedIn &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/gopivotal&gt; | Facebook &lt;http://www.facebook.com/gopivotal&gt; | Google+ &lt;https://plus.google.com/105320112436428794490&gt;




© Pivotal - FOR INTERNAL USE ONLY - DO NOT DISTRIBUTE.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
