<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Corp Comm 10-24-2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 1, No. 1</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 1, No. 1

EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products


Business, Products, and People—Working Together
 
 Hello and welcome to our biweekly Pivotal Newsletter, Vol. 1, No. 1! While my day job is keeping the trains running on time for Scott Yara, I’m excited to be pitching in and helping Internal Communications for a while as Newsletter Editor.
 
 “Working Together” is a common theme throughout this awesome issue—look for it in the 
Business update from APJ, the Products update on Spring, and the People updates from HR and Corp Dev, and get to know one of our employees a little better in our fun “Hello, my name is …” section.
 
 You’ll notice our newsletter follows the Communications 
Framework described at our last Town Hall &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B4EXeyHbia9oeXVQYjliaWlzSWc/preview&gt;; we have sections for Business, Products, 
People, and a Special Guest. Big thanks to our contributors, as well as to Michael Weir and Shannon Dunn for this beautiful template and to Katherine McGreal for setting up our space on Inside Pivotal &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; and creating our Socialcast &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt; group. Please feel free to post questions/feedback there, or contact me directly: rbaldwin@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:rbaldwin@gopivotal.com&gt;
 
 Finally, be on the look out for an announcement on Pivotal’s 
Halloween contest—looking forward to seeing your costumes on the Halloween 2013 &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89822-halloween2013&gt; Socialcast group!
 
 “Coming together is a 
beginning; keeping together is progress; working together is success.”—Henry Ford











BUSINESS UPDATE
Melissa Ries
 Vice President and General Manager, 
 Asia Pacific &amp; Japan







Pivotal Innovation Center Opening and Pivotal APJ Summit
 
What a week in APJ! On Tuesday, October 22, we celebrated the opening of the Pivotal Innovation Centre in Singapore &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/about-pivotal/press-center/10212013-PIC&gt;. This Centre is a joint project, almost two years in the making, with the Infocomm Development Authority of Singapore (IDA) &lt;http://www.ida.gov.sg/&gt;. With a foundation built on Big Data, the Centre is the first lab in the region and the first of its kind to be developed in Asia. It is dedicated to helping customers accelerate delivery of prototypes that prove the feasibility and return on investment of advanced analytics applications and Big Data platform technologies. We couldn’t be more excited about the benefits this will provide to government agencies and leading enterprises as they begin their technology transformations.
 
 On October 23 and 24 we are hosting (or “hosted”, depending on when you read this) our very first Pivotal 
APJ Summit. I want to extend a special thanks to Peter Cooper and Mica Tee for being the driving spirit behind this VERY large undertaking. We appreciate all of the support we received from every group in the company, as well as the individual contributions made by Paul Maritz, Adrian Colyer, Jags Ramnarayan, David Oro, Andy Piper, Roz Gregory, Jacqueline Ho, the Data Science team led by Greg Whalen, and many others joining us here 
in Singapore. Some highlights: 


 - Agenda of great speakers here &lt;http://www.pivotalsummit.shobiziems.com/speakers.html&gt;.
 - More than 500 registrations—435 of which are customers and partners!
 - 23 C-level engagements, including StarHub, Bank of Thailand, NTT, Commonwealth Bank of Australia, and BHP Bilton.
 - 30+ media and analysts attending from the region.














PRODUCT UPDATE
Adrian Colyer
 CTO, Application Fabric







Spring Success: Conference, Website, Platform, and Deals!
 
 In September, Pivotal hosted more than 1,000 attendees in Santa Clara for the annual SpringOne 2GX &lt;http://www.springone2gx.com/conference/santa_clara/2013/09/home&gt; conference. We launched the new Spring website, http://spring.io &lt;http://spring.io/&gt;, live on stage during the opening keynote. This site gets approximately 5 million visitors a year and is a great example of what Pivotal can do when we work together. The site is built from the ground up using Spring, in a joint collaboration between Spring developers and Pivotal Labs. Furthermore, the entire site is running live on Cloud Foundry at run.pivotal.io &lt;http://run.pivotal.io/&gt;. Collaborating together in this way helped us to improve the Spring developer experience. We used feedback from the Pivots working on the project, to grow knowledge and experience on building modern Spring apps within the Pivotal Labs team, and to refine the Java buildpack support for Spring within Cloud Foundry. We plan on open sourcing the code for the website as a live reference app for Spring.
 
 In conjunction with the spring.io &lt;http://spring.io/&gt; website, we also announced the Spring IO platform—bringing 
together the core Spring APIs into a cohesive and versioned platform for modern application development. Spring binds the Pivotal product portfolio together from an applications perspective, with strong support for Cloud Foundry, RabbitMQ, Redis, GemFire, Hadoop, and even HAWQ and GPDB via Spring’s SQL support. The success of Spring also translates into commercial success for Pivotal: in the last quarter, Spring was instrumental in securing a number of million-dollar-plus deals.











PEOPLE UPDATE
Joe Militello
 VP, Human Resources







What’s New and Upcoming in HR: HR@ and Systems
 
 Your HR team has been working on a variety of different projects to help support Pivotal’s growth and to 
make this a great place to work. Three highlights are: 


 - We recently launched HR@GoPivotal.com &lt;mailto:HR@GoPivotal.com&gt;. HR@ is a central source of Human Resources support, managed by our global HR team and available to assist you with any HR-related questions. We are encouraged by its early adoption—over 500 tickets have been submitted since our soft launch in August! Please keep the great questions coming.
 - We are also undergoing an in-depth assessment of all HR technologies and applications. Our long-term goal is to ensure that our systems are user friendly, intuitive, mobile, easily accessible (no VPN!), and reflect the culture we are building. As you can imagine, it will take time and effort to achieve this goal. We will keep you updated on our progress.

 - Finally, as we announced at the October Town Hall, the Pivotal Organization 
Chart is posted to Inside Pivotal &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/home&gt; until we launch the Pivotal Online Directory later this quarter.


As we continue to make Pivotal a special place to work, we’d love to hear from you. Please feel free to reach out to your HR Business Partner. Our team member list is located here &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/departments/human-resources&gt;.











PEOPLE UPDATE
Leo Spiegel
 SVP Strategy &amp; Corporate Development,
 Corporate Development Department







Who We Are and Our Most Recent Project: Xtreme Labs Acquisition
 
 The Corporate Development Department at Pivotal is responsible for helping to achieve Pivotal’s 
strategic goals, by leveraging mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A), investments (both into Pivotal [e.g., GE] and into interesting companies), and strategic partnerships, including but not limited to technology alliances. Our team does not work with partners looking to sell or provide services around Pivotal products—that function is managed by Scott Aronson’s Field Operations team.
 
 We’re divided into two groups: the Corporate Development Group, which focuses on M&amp;A and 
investments and includes Mike Maxey, and the Business Development Group, which focuses on strategic partnerships and includes David Menninger, Jim Totte, and Mal Knox. We also have a very close relationship with EMC Ventures, and in particular Daniel Docter, who is dedicated to Pivotal.
 
 We always have a bunch of balls in the air, but the most recent major project we completed is the acquisition of Xtreme Labs. Xtreme Labs provides agile development services and technology focused on mobile devices. The company is based in Toronto, Canada, and is recognized as the “go-to” company for mobile solutions. Mike Maxey (or Maxey—yes, he has a first name!) did a spectacular job in helping us complete this deal. Xtreme Labs will now become part of our Pivotal Labs group, and its founders, Amar Varma and Sundeep (Sunny) Madra, will report to Rob Mee. Farhan Thawar will report to Edward Hieatt and be responsible for the Pivotal Labs—Toronto location. We are thrilled that the approximately 300 individuals from Xtreme Labs have joined the Pivotal family!











HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Ben Hale
 Staff Engineer, Cloud Foundry Java Experience







At Pivotal, I…
 Lead the Cloud Foundry Java Experience team.
 
 You can find me…
 At the Southampton, UK, office.
 
 Currently, I’m working 
on…
 The Java buildpack. It allows users to push applications to Cloud Foundry without having to worry about the infrastructure being used to run them or having to configure the services being used by them. The buildpack hides all of the stuff developers shouldn’t care about so that they can focus on what’s important.
 
 In my spare time…
 I bicycle. A lot.
 
 Something you probably don’t know about me…
 I’m on the cusp of becoming a dual citizen.
 
 To me, Pivotal…
 Is an opportunity to fundamentally change what a software developer cares about. If we do our job right, container configuration, memory limits, service bindings, scaling, and more will all fade to the background. This will allow developers to focus on what they’re best at—writing code.









Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
