<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Labs_Email_NewslettersFromSales_Q214.Weekly Media Newsletter_Sheetal Jaitly_May</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Labs Media Weekly</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {{lead.First Name:default=}},
I hope you had a great weekend. This week we will be in NYC at the M1Summit.  I will be in attendance and on a panel, let me know if you’re attending as it is always great to connect. We were busy last week at the Collision Conference in Vegas. The conference had a great group of startups and speakers.  
Below is our weekly email series, highlighting top stories impacting media companies in the mobile space. This was a very big week in news and we have curated some of the most important stories for you.  We hope you continue to find this content useful and informative.
1. AT&amp;T to buy DirecTV for $48.5 Billion &lt;http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2014/05/18/att-buys-directv/9247795/&gt;  
AT&amp;T agreed Sunday to buy DirecTV for about 
$48.5 billion in yet another mammoth deal in the pay-TV space this year that would immediately boost the telecom giant&apos;s customer base at a time of confounding industry challenges. This move is one of many we have been seeing in the battle for subscribers and infrastructure. This acquisition is hot off the heals of the TVEverywhere craze and the disruptors have disrupted the big players.  
2. Google Names New Head of Its Glass Business
Some significant HR changes at 
Google Glass we’re hearing. First off is the departure of lead electrical engineer Adrian Wong, to competing face computer Oculus. Second off is the bringing on of Art.com’s Chief Marketing Officer Ivy Ross to head the division. The Harvard-trained Ross has a rich, non-tech background, having held several high-level marketing positions at companies such as Mattel, the Gap, Disney, Coach and Old Navy. Perhaps Ross’ most applicable experience to Google Glass is a stint at contact lens manufacturer Bausch &amp; Lomb in the early 90s, where she was Vice President of design and development for Outlook Eyewear. Coincidence?
3. Pinterest Raises $200 Million
Pinterest Inc. raised $200 million in a funding round that gives the Web-scrapbooking startup a $5 billion valuation, up from $3.8 billion seven months ago. The money came from existing investors, including SV Angel, Bessemer Venture Partners, Fidelity Investments, Andreessen Horowitz, FirstMark Capital and Valiant Capital Partners. The new round brings the total raised to $764 million, Pinterest said in an e-mailed statement yesterday. The funding for Pinterest, which has yet to start generating significant sales, is part of a spate of fundraisings at multibillion-dollar valuations. Uber is in talks to raise funds at a valuation of $10 billion or more, according to people familiar with the talks, while room-sharing service Airbnb and online-storage service Dropbox were valued at $10 billion in their latest fundraising rounds.
4. Amazon&apos;s mysterious giant locker in San Francisco will give birth to a Nissan
Amazon.com has constructed a larger version of its delivery lockers in a downtown San Francisco plaza. What it’s storing inside is a mystery. It’s a big box. Big enough to fit a car, which may be the point. Amazon is holding a promotional event there beginning Friday during which people will be filmed using the locker, according to a person familiar with the matter. Later, Amazon will send out codes to some customers which they can use to open the locker and claim prizes. While Amazon is famously secretive with new initiatives, its delivery lockers are already operating in many cities, often in convenience stores and parking garages. The lockers allow customers who aren’t home to still receive packages — they are sent a code that unlocks one of the drawers.
5. Samsung is rebranding London Heathrow’s Terminal 5 as ‘Terminal Samsung Galaxy S5’
Samsung&apos;s marketing juggernaut is reaching new heights today with the announcement that Heathrow&apos;s Terminal 5 will be rebranded for two weeks to promote the company&apos;s flagship Galaxy S5 Android phone. Starting on Monday, every area of the terminal will feature the &quot;Terminal Samsung Galaxy S5&quot; moniker, with all the signage and digital screens promoting the handset and projecting images of it. Russell Taylor, Samsung&apos;s UK marketing VP describes this as a &quot;one-off opportunity to push the boundaries like no other brand has been allowed to do before.&quot; A Heathrow Airport spokesperson clarifies that Samsung hasn&apos;t bought the actual naming rights to the terminal, just an expansive ad 
campaign to be distributed within it. She says &quot;Samsung want to call it Terminal Samsung Galaxy S5 and we are relaxed about that.&quot;
6.  TV somewhere, sometimes: Pay TV’s rocky path towards a streaming future
Ask any TV executive about TV Everywhere, and you’re going to hear plenty of praise for the industry’s efforts to stream live and on-demand programming to pay TV subscribers. But if you keep them talking, you’re inevitably going to get a long laundry list of problems.  Only 17% of users know a TVE offering exists.  There is a ton of room here for growth and it is the future of content consumption.  The fragmentation in the industry is an issue but with this challenge there is a lot of opportunity.  
7. Google Glass to give a courtside view of the NBA
The NBA&apos;s love affair with Google Glass is continuing through the playoffs, with the 
Indiana Pacers adding a new feature to its in-stadium Glass live streaming: celebrities. The Eastern Conference team that&apos;s had one of the best records in the league this year already uses Glass to beam live pictures from around the court to its scoreboard, but now it&apos;s doing it with famous attendees donning the headset. The first of these new Glass-casters is NFL defensive end Robert Mathis, a longtime member of the Indianapolis Colts and last season&apos;s leader in sacks.
Have a great week!

Sheetal Jaitly
Mobile Director - Media, Sports &amp; Entertainment
Pivotal Labs | CAN 416.908.9995 | US 650.847.8549 
sjaitly@pivotallabs.com &lt;mailto:sjaitly@pivotallabs.com&gt;  
www.pivotallabs.com &lt;http://www.pivotallabs.com&gt; 
@sheetaljaitly &lt;https://twitter.com/sheetaljaitly&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
