<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.1-26-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of January 26, 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of January 26, 2015
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/press-release/pivotal-cloud-foundry-record-breaking-fastest-first-year-sales-growth-for-an-open-source-product&gt;
PIVOTAL CLOUD FOUNDRY REPORTS RECORD-BREAKING 2014
Yesterday, we were honored to announce that in less than a year, Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/pivotal-cloud-foundry&gt; has booked ~$40 million in software sales and secured a 
customer portfolio of top global brands, making it the fastest growing open source product ever by first-year sales.

Pivotal Cloud Foundry has emerged as the platform of choice across all industries where agile transformation has become a competitive 
advantage, as evident by a surging demand from Fortune 100/500 enterprises who are choosing Pivotal Cloud Foundry for IoT build outs.

To learn more, read the press release &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/press-release/pivotal-cloud-foundry-record-breaking-fastest-first-year-sales-growth-for-an-open-source-product&gt;.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/press-release/pivotal-cloud-foundry-record-breaking-fastest-first-year-sales-growth-for-an-open-source-product&gt;
EPISODE #13: WEDNESDAY, JANUARY 28TH, &quot;USING SERVICE BROKERS IN PIVOTAL CF&quot;
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us this week, Wednesday, January 28th for Episode #13 of our All Things Pivotal Podcast Series, &quot;Using Service Brokers in Pivotal CF&quot;.

Simon talks about services architecture in relation to Pivotal Cloud Foundry and how they work. Services are what&apos;s consumed by applications running on the Pivotal Cloud Foundry platform.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
PIVOTAL OPENS CHICAGO OFFICE
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-opens-chicago-office-reception-open-now-hiring&gt;
Announcing the Pivotal Chicago is now open! To celebrate Pivotal’s new accessibility for local businesses, Pivotal is offering members of the 1871 digital startup community access to Pivotal Tracker. The city is surrounded by start-ups and growth companies as well as a number of large Fortune 500 corporations, making it a great location for technology companies like Pivotal. We are looking for talented, Chicago-based team members to help us focus on agile development, design and product management practices, enterprise innovation, and mobile/web application development.

 READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-opens-chicago-office-reception-open-now-hiring&gt;
PIVOTAL PEOPLE - MICHAEL COTÉ ON JOINING PIVOTAL AND BUILDING BETTER SOFTWARE
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/pivotal-people/pivotal-people-michael-cote-on-joining-pivotal-and-building-better-software&gt;
As a prior programmer, cloud strategist, and industry analyst, Michael Coté has seen the software industry from a number of perspectives, including Director of Cloud Strategy at Dell. Recently, he joined Pivotal to work on the Cloud Foundry team, and, in this Q&amp;A, gives us a rundown on his background, what attracted him to Pivotal, why open source matters, and more.
 
 READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/pivotal-people/pivotal-people-michael-cote-on-joining-pivotal-and-building-better-software&gt;
- 5 Things You Don’t Know about Platform as a Service &lt;http://www.hottopics.ht/stories/enterprise/5-things-you-dont-know-about-platform-as-a-service/&gt;
 - Four Ways to Achieve a Winning Mobile-First Strategy &lt;http://www.finextra.com/blogs/fullblog.aspx?blogid=10420&gt;
 - Why Do Managers Hate Agile? &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2015/01/26/why-do-managers-hate-agile/&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
