<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_PCF Roadshow_Q314.Invite - Singapore</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You&apos;re Invited: Pivotal Cloud Platform Roadshow - Singapore</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/cloud-platform-roadshow/singapore?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=pivotal-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=paas-pcp-roadshow&gt;
If you are concerned with the business end of your organisation, want to know why Platform as a Service (PaaS) is getting the ears of the board? Want to know how it can change the 
way you compete in the market via technology innovation?
 
 Attend to learn what PaaS can do and see what clever organisations are doing to outpace new market entrants and leapfrog existing ones.
 
 If you are interested in developing, deploying, and scaling applications for 
the Cloud Generation then stay for the workshop. Join the Pivotal engineering team for a hands-on workshop with Pivotal Cloud Foundry while you network with peers and build some new skills.
 
 Who Should Attend?
 Seminar
 This seminar is geared to those in R&amp;D, operations, finance, innovation and IT concerned with applications, cloud and big data. The content is of value to anyone concerned with organizational risk.
 
 Workshop
 The keynote presentations set the stage for the workshop. This workshop is geared to application developers, enterprise architects, and anyone who wants to get hands-on experience developing an app in a PaaS environment. 
 




AGENDA


1:30 PM – 2:00 PM
 Registration &amp; Coffee


2:00 PM – 2:30 PM
 Keynote: Software Kept Eating the World


2:30 PM – 3:00 PM
 Innovation: Who&apos;s Doing It Using PaaS?


3:00 PM – 3:20 PM
 Tea Break


3:20 PM – 4:30 AM
 Workshop - Lab 1 - The Developer Experience


4:30 PM – 6:00 PM
 Workshop - Lab 2 - Architecture and the Operator Experience


6:00 PM – 7:00 PM
 Happy Hour



Register &lt;%20http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/cloud-platform-roadshow/singapore?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=pivotal-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=paas-pcp-roadshow&gt; now for this exclusive event. The workshop is FREE; space is limited.
THURSDAY

November 6, 2014

IDA Lab @ National Design Center

#03-04

111 Middle Road

Singapore
REGISTER &lt;%20http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/cloud-platform-roadshow/singapore?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=pivotal-email-link&amp;utm_campaign=paas-pcp-roadshow&gt;
PRESENTER

Jamie O&apos;Meara, Platform Community Engineer</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
