<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.7-7-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Healthcare Success Story</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of July 6, 2015
&lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/healthcare-success-story-wellcare?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;
Healthcare Success Story - How WellCare Accelerated Big Data Delivery to Improve Analytics
In this webinar, speakers from WellCare, Attunity and Pivotal discuss how WellCare uses Attunity Replicate to offload data quickly and easily from its SQL Server and Oracle systems into Pivotal Greenplum Database &lt;https://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-greenplum-database?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt; to support real-time reporting and analytics.


Watch the replay to learn about:


	- Big data challenges and opportunities for healthcare providers
	- Increasing reporting speeds to improve healthcare analytics
	- Enabling a real-time data initiative for big data success
	- Incorporating Hadoop into an existing EDW environment to achieve a successful data lake
	- Implementing the joint solution of Attunity and Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;https://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt; to enable significant optimizations in your EDW environment
REPLAY &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/webinar/healthcare-success-story-wellcare?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;
Podcasts
The Agility Frontier - Continuous Delivery and Pivotal Cloud Foundry
July 01, 2015
What’s Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;http://pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt; have to do with continuous delivery? Fresh off presenting at a recent Jenkins User Conference &lt;https://www.cloudbees.com/jenkins/juc-2015/us-east&gt; on that topic, I ask Karun Bakshi to go over his presentation &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/karunbakshi/continuous-delivery-summit-washington&gt;. We discuss how Pivotal Cloud Foundry helps enable continuous delivery and also some of the “deleted scenes” from his talk.
 
Listen Now &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-conversations/features/the-agility-frontier-continuous-delivery-and-pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;
Simplifying Data Science Workflows with Pivotal Cloud Foundry
July 02, 2015
Ian Huston and Alexander Kagoshima of Pivotal Labs delivered a presentation at the Cloud Foundry Summit 2015 demonstrating how they have used Cloud Foundry to deliver data-driven applications to clients. Data scientists synthesize a wide range of skills in their efforts to understand complex data sets and deliver insights, and Cloud Foundry enables practitioners to quickly get to work, rather than losing time setting up servers or performing operations tasks. 



Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/simplifying-data-science-workflows-with-pivotal-cloud-foundry?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;
Big Data
UC Berkeley&apos;s AMPLab Drives Big Data Innovation
July 07, 2015
UC Berkeley’s AMPLab brings together academics and businesses to engage in dialogue and collaboration to develop the next generation of big data technologies. Pivotal is a sponsor of AMPLab, supporting UC Berkeley’s effort to connect the brightest minds who are innovating within the big data and data science sphere.



Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/uc-berkeleys-amplab-drives-big-data-innovation?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-7-7-15&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
