<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Labs_Newsletter_May2014_Q214.Monthly Newsletter - May 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Labs News - May 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Pivotal Labs News - May 2014



LAUNCH Beacon: Retail, Payments &amp; Location &lt;http://events.launch.co/beacon&gt;

In case you missed our Mobile &amp; Wearables &lt;http://events.launch.co/mobile/&gt; event last year, you certainly don’t want to miss LAUNCH Beacon &lt;http://events.launch.co/beacon&gt; taking place in NYC June 16th.
 
Beacon will focus on the intersection of Retail, Payments and Locations and will bring together some of the hottest emerging companies and disrupters in the space. Hosted by the folks at LAUNCH &lt;http://launch.co/about/&gt; and backed by us @ Pivotal Labs &lt;http://www.pivotallabs.com/&gt;, this one-day invite only &quot;meet-up&quot; will feature a combination of demos, fireside chats, breakouts and more.
 
On stage we have Founders from these amazing startups: Zady, Nomi, Boutiika, Brickwork, SonicNotify, MakeSpace, Rounded, Red Clay, Aisle411, Perch and many others.
 
In the audience, we’ve got some of the most influential individuals in the space from awesome brands like Ralph Lauren, Amex, Nordstrom, Samsung, Walmart, Michael Kors and many others.
 
Don’t miss out on the opportunity to be a part of the conversation. Register at http://events.launch.co/beacon &lt;http://events.launch.co/beacon&gt; or send me a direct message &lt;mailto:ijaffer@pivotallabs.com?subject=LAUNCH Beacon&gt;.


U.S. Retail Apps Report &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/us-retail-apps-report-2014/&gt; &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/us-retail-apps-report-2014/&gt;
Launching today, our popular Retail Apps Report provides insight into the quality of mobile apps offered by the top 25 U.S. mCommerce retailers. Using publicly available data on the U.S. iTunes Store and Google Play, we compiled customer feedback, average ratings, and which platforms are targeted by retailers.
 
Click here to download the 2014 U.S. Retail Apps Report &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/us-retail-apps-report-2014/&gt;.


Webinar - Google Wallet: The Fanatics Experience &lt;https://gopivotal.webex.com/gopivotal/lsr.php?RCID=06524ddf01b21822526565de8f2b6ee7&gt;

Your customers are using mobile throughout their shopping journey, but are you losing money because mCommerce purchases aren&apos;t completed? Learn how Fanatics used Google Wallet to boost conversions and reduce abandoned shopping carts.
 
Watch the on-demand webinar &lt;https://gopivotal.webex.com/gopivotal/lsr.php?RCID=06524ddf01b21822526565de8f2b6ee7&gt;.


Pivotal Tracker for iOS 7 &lt;http://www.pivotaltracker.com/community/tracker-blog/tracker-ios-7-app-now-available&gt;
Tracker has been redesigned for iOS 7 (click here to download &lt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/pivotal-tracker/id444623375&gt;). We’ve made many changes to the UI including:


 - Clean view of panels &amp; stories
 - Redesigned story &amp; epic editing
 - Improved notifications


Click here to learn more &lt;http://www.pivotaltracker.com/community/tracker-blog/tracker-ios-7-app-now-available&gt;.


Last Month&apos;s Top Blogs

How to Maintain Separate Design and Development Backlogs &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/separate-design-backlog/&gt;

In the past, separate design backlogs have been prohibitively difficult to integrate into an agile team’s workflow. Now that it’s feasible, a separate Design Backlog is appropriate when you have multiple platforms with design concerns which are independent of platform, or when it’s important to estimate design work without affecting development velocity. 

Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/separate-design-backlog/&gt;.


Feedback in conversation: An adventure in meta-process &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/feedback-in-conversation/&gt;

Development is all about feedback loops. We use analytics and AB tests to see how people respond to new features and design changes, and we tighten feedback loops within our teams with co-located workspaces, daily standups, and other tricks. These techniques, however, are for the most part geared toward feedback about what we are building, rather than how we are building it. The latter, I think, is a much more powerful question. 

Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/feedback-in-conversation/&gt;.


Developing; Fast and Slow &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/developing-fast-slow/&gt;

Daniel Kahnemann’s &quot;Thinking; Fast and Slow&quot; is an excellent book describing, amongst other things, the many ways in which our brains process signals and inputs from our environment. We&apos;re talking here about various stimuli which affect our behavior both consciously and subconsciously.
 
Read the full blog &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/developing-fast-slow/&gt;.


Where to Find Us in the Near Future


Ruby Motion \ &lt;http://www.rubymotion.com/conference/2014/&gt; (May 28-29 @ San Francisco) \ The conference will feature speakers exclusively from the RubyMotion community.

Andy Pliszka, Engineer

 

Fireside on Sandhill \ &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/Pivotal-Presents-Fireside-Chat-Greylock&gt; (May 29 @ Palo Alto) \ a conversation about open platforms in the enterprise, and also a look into what it means for startups.

Speaking: Jerry Chen (Partner, Greylock Partners); Scott Yara (President and Head of Products, Pivotal); and Alex Williams (Founder, The New Stack)

 

AnDevCon \ &lt;http://andevcon.com/&gt; (May 30 @ Boston) \ AnDevCon is the technical conference for software developers building Android apps.

Speaking: Emir Hasanbegovic, Engineer

 

RubyNation DC \ &lt;http://www.rubynation.org/&gt; (June 6-7 @ Washington) \ RubyNation is a community event run for and by the DC software development community. 

Speaking: Andy Pliszka, Engineer

 

Northside Brooklyn \ &lt;http://northsidefestival.com/&gt; (June 12-19 @ NYC) \ The Northside Festival is New York City’s largest and most accessible discovery festival.

Speaking: Farhan Thawar, VP Engineering</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
