<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.SA - 6-2-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Final Q2 Sales Note</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,
At the end of 2013, I wrote that 2014 is our breakout year. That means showing customers and investors that their trust in Pivotal is well placed because we’re turning a big vision into customer value, and big business for us.
At our first Pivotal Club in Mayacoba Mexico (think tequila), we spent time with some of our most successful team members in 2013. We saw first-hand what big success looks like – Monsanto using Pivotal analytics to increase crop yields and help feed millions; Pivotal big data helping fix the ticketing system for China Rail, which moves 235 million people over Chinese New Year alone; Mobile app strategies creating new fan experiences for the NFL and NBA. It’s humbling to see the impact Pivotal can have on billions of people.
We continue to strengthen our bench in field operations. I’m delighted that we’ve added vital customer support focus through the leadership of Iain Gray, who will strengthen a continuum where wins are followed by delivery that turns new customers into loyal ones.
We executed across our three GTM motions (Data, PaaS, Agile) in Q1 and into Q2. We saw 11 seven-figure deals in Q1, with bookings up 64% y-o-y. 
Highlights to date include:
Big data and analytics powers ahead with Vodafone (EMEA), where Gemfire and Rabbit MQ will radically improve marketing and customer insights. With Samsung (APJ) we went up against Oracle and Cloudera to win two deals with Pivotal HD and GPDB. 
Agile attracted forward-thinking health insurer Humana (Americas), to help them create a retail-like health experience through mobile and accelerate their development cycle. When Nordstrom struggled to bring their customer experience to mobile, Pivotal stepped in and through our influence their entire SW development team will head to San Francisco to learn our methodology.
We’re helping Axel Springer in EMEA transform from a paper-based to digital-based media business, and Pivotal CF will help China’s largest electronics retailer Suning set up a ‘third platform’ to run its business across clouds. We landed a multi-million Cloud Foundry deal with AT&amp;T for Pivotal CF to enable their enterprise big data business, network services, and much more.
Even more exciting is the pipeline. After starting the year at 9% field coverage, we’ll exit this quarter with a global pipeline opportunity in PaaS across 70% of the field! The big data pipeline extends across the whole field. Notable is huge early momentum for our Big Data Suite. In the eight weeks since it became available, nearly 40% of you have active BDS pipeline opportunities, and more than double that for Q3. I’m confident we’ll continue to see it grow!
With all this opportunity on the table we have to focus on the basics to close June strong. There were instances in Q1 where execution tripped us up on the way to the finish line, so understand the workflow processes – from quote to close to booking.
You’ve pulled in great customer wins and stories that are helping Pivotal become known more for being amazing with customers, as opposed to being the shiny new thing. Keep them coming, and reach out to Sophia Tseng &lt;mailto:stseng@gopivotal.com&gt; to get them documented. We’re on the path for a breakout year, and we’ll be even better with more customer success stories. 
Marketing continues its air cover to build awareness and ultimately pipeline. Pivotal is spearheading the upcoming Cloud Foundry Summit from June 9-11 &lt;http://cfsummit.com/&gt;, with an all-star lineup of technical and business leaders from the Cloud Foundry community. More than 600 attendees are expected and our platform will be on full display, so reach out to your base to stir up interest. Details are also being worked on for a big Pivotal-led platform conference in the Fall.
Finally, I’m delighted to announce that the Pivotal Club venue location in 2015 will be the Ritz Carlton, Kapalua &lt;http://www.ritzcarlton.com/en/Properties/KapaluaMaui/Default.htm?utm_campaign=TBPSUSEGPB173&amp;src=ps&amp;pId=rztbppc%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank&gt; in Hawaii, from June 4-6 (think Mai Tai). Every one of you should feel that you could be part of this celebration. Save the date, I want to see you there!
Stay focused, use the momentum to close June strong, and remember that the entire executive team and I are ready and willing to jump in and help.
Make it happen!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
