<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.06-30-2015 Data Org Change</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Changes in the Data Organization</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Colleagues,

We wanted to let you know about a number of important changes to the Pivotal Data organization. These changes are directly related to our accelerated pursuit of product alignment and simplification, and leadership in the marketplace.

Right up front we want to acknowledge that today’s changes would not be possible without the extraordinary work of Sunny Madra 
and Gavin Sherry over the last 9 months. Sunny and the extended data team have delivered three straight quarters of overachievement, setting the stage for us to move more quickly to align company-wide engineering resources and bring our data services to Pivotal Cloud Foundry.

Our healthy data business, with 
Pivotal Big Data Suite, provides a tremendous foundation for us to achieve long-term success with our customers and is an essential component in funding our future. We will continue to invest in and grow this part of our business.

The following changes are effective immediately:

Scott Yara will act as interim business lead for Data Products.

Elisabeth Hendrickson will become Vice 
President, Engineering for Data Products.

Duncan Lord will become Senior Director, Product Management for Data Products.

Suds Menon, Jags Ramnarayan and Richard Lamb will lead a new strategic initiative for Pivotal (Project &quot;SnappyData&quot;) that is 
closely aligned with our mission. Reporting to Scott Yara, this group will also continue to provide leadership and support to ensure continuity for Pivotal&apos;s GemFire business.

Gavin Sherry, in the short term, will take some well-deserved time off. Upon his return, he will report to Scott Yara and help lead vision, technical strategy and evangelism for our Data Products.

Sunny Madra will lead a new initiative (currently in stealth mode) in Corporate Development, leveraging his unique experience as a business leader, 
product leader and successful investor.

Nithin Rao will join Sunny in the new Corporate Development initiative.

Thank you to Sunny and Gavin for their exemplary leadership and congratulations to all in their new roles. Further detail for the extended data organization will be forthcoming in the next few weeks.



Regards,

Scott and Rob</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
