<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.September 2014 Webinars</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Microservices with Spring Boot and Process Driven Spring Applications with Activiti</subject>
    <textOnly>Microservices with Spring Boot
Speaker: Josh Long

Microservices? A thing? Or hype? What does it mean in practice? The answer, like so many Facebook statuses, is complicated. In broad strokes, Microservices offer a refreshed approach to application architecture. Microservices are a new way to describe many of the patterns that have fallen out of large-scale applications in practice over the recent years. There is no doubt that the approach works.

The question is: how does one build a microservice architecture? Join Josh Long for this webinar introducing Spring&apos;s support for building microservice architectures.
Europe
Tuesday, September 16
 3:00PM GMT Summer Time
 (London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_MicroserviceswithSpringBoot-JoshLong7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, September 16
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_MicroserviceswithSpringBoot10AM_Register.html&gt;
Process Driven Spring Applications with Activiti
Speakers: Josh Long and Joram Barrez, Activiti

Today&apos;s applications are complex, distributed systems that - taken together - produce results. Tracking the flow of work through that system, however, becomes increasingly more painful as automated- and human-driven tasks are integrated into business processes. Business can&apos;t react to what it can&apos;t see. Business can&apos;t measure what it can&apos;t see. &quot;Workflow&quot; describes the sequence of processes through which a piece of work passes from initiation to completion. Workflow systems, like Activiti, describe and then execute these processes. Activiti is an open-source, Apache 2-licensed workflow engine that works with Spring and Spring Boot.

In this webinar, join Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long and Activiti-ninja Joram Barrez for a look at how to distill, describe and reuse complex business processes using Spring (and Spring Boot) and Activiti.
Europe
Tuesday, September 23
 3:00PM GMT Summer Time
 (London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_ProcessDrivenSpringAppsActiviti7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, September 23
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_ProcessDrivenSpringAppsActiviti10AM_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
