<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.5-16-14 V2N10</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 2, No.10</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 2, No. 10










 









EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products







“Redefine” was the theme at EMC World &lt;http://www.emcworld.com/index.htm&gt; last week in Las Vegas, which according to the 
dictionary means “to reexamine or reevaluate especially with a view to change.” As part of the Federation (EMC, VMware, and Pivotal), we’re not only on a journey to redefine ourselves, but as the tip of change, Pivotal is helping customers carve their paths to the 3rd-generation 
of computing.

 This edition of the Pivotal Newsletter focuses on EMC World, where Pivotal showed up in fine form. The Business Update sheds light on our Alliances; we get insight into Product Management for Solutions and Partners in the Product Update; see what collaboration between Pivotal Labs and Pivotal Data Labs looks like in the Agile Update; Marketing summarizes the EMC World event in our People 
Update.

 And if you’re interested in what’s around the corner, check out the updated Inside Pivotal Calendar &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/calendar&gt;.

“Intelligence is the ability to adapt to change.”—Stephen Hawking













BUSINESS UPDATE
Nick Cayou
 Vice President, Alliances

Michael Wood
 Director, Alliances Engineering







EMC: Investor and Partner

 As many Pivotal folks know, EMC is both an investor and key go-to-market partner for Pivotal products and services. In Q2 ‘14, we formalized the management and governance of the EMC and Pivotal relationship under the Alliances group, with dedicated teams on both sides of the table working to forge a successful partnership.

 As you’ll read in the following sections of the newsletter, 
Pivotal is key to EMC’s transition to what IDC calls the “3rd Platform”, and the excitement around Pivotal within EMC is high.

 Our goal is to help EMC navigate this fundamental market shift in a way that allows Pivotal to maintain an independent identity and open 
ecosystem, while leveraging the phenomenal EMC reach, sales engine, and brand, as we grow our Big Data and PaaS business.

 Throughout 2014, we’re focusing on a few key areas with our EMC counterparts:

Product and Support Integration 



 - Ensuring that the Data Computing Appliance (DCA) continues to drive near-term revenue for both Pivotal and EMC.
 - Developing a roadmap for future versions of the DCA as an EMC converged infrastructure product which will incorporate more of Pivotal’s software titles.
 - Integrating the Pivotal Big Data Suite assets with EMC’s portfolio of information infrastructure products, including ViPR, Isilon, Documentum, RSA and Vblock.


Marketing and Field Enablement 


 - Ensuring that Pivotal’s major go-to-market priorities (Big Data Suite and PaaS) are integrated with EMC’s formal global sales and technical training and enablement process.
 - Developing a “Pivotal Specialist” team (sales and technical) within EMC.
 - Conducting regional marketing and sales enablement sessions.
 - Aligning our outbound and field marketing strategies.


EVP Solutions 


 - Helping EMC and the Federation position and deliver on the Business Data Lake, Security Analytics and Software Defined Data Center solutions.


As we continue to formalize the relationship with EMC, we’re open to any feedback and requests from our colleagues at Pivotal. Please feel free to reach out to us if you need anything.

 Thanks,
 Nick and Michael











PRODUCT UPDATE
Duncan Lord
 Director, Product Management for Solutions
 and Partners







EMC, VMware, and Pivotal (EVP) Solutions

 When we package combinations of software, hardware, and services from our Federation of companies to 
address specific business needs, we enhance customer value. We call these solutions “EVP” (for EMC, VMware, and Pivotal) or “Federation” Solutions. The Federation is a major focal point for Pivotal, EMC and VMware in 2014, as companies look to combine relevant elements of our collective technology portfolio in SKUs that not only provide value, but are also easy to buy.

 Strictly speaking, the moment we transitioned the Data 
Computing Appliance (DCA) from Pivotal to EMC, we had our first EVP solution, with software from Pivotal and a hardware platform from EMC. We’re in the process of working with our partners to scope the effort required to integrate other Federation offerings into easy-to-order solutions, including ViPR, Isilon, DSSD (the innovative new rack-scale flash storage company just acquired by EMC &lt;https://www.emc.com/about/news/press/2014/20140505-06.htm&gt;), various VMware products, and others.

 EMC field teams learn about new product and solution offerings through sales plays, which include a range of materials such as playbooks, 
sales tools, training, etc. Pivotal software is a key component of both the Federation’s Data Lake and Security sales plays (and potentially others) through 2015, and we are contributors in the creation of these plays in a way that pulls Pivotal software through the EMC core field, and eventually the VMware field 
sales motions.

 The Federation’s importance was in full display at EMC World last week, where EMC touted Pivotal along with ViPR, DSSD, and other products that the EMC leadership clearly sees as strategic.

 Some of the product highlights for me at EMC World include: 


 - Susheel Kaushik’s demo in a session with the Product Manager from ViPR
 - CJ Desai’s breakout &lt;http://bcove.me/tpt2uawt&gt;, mentioning the DCA Data Lake
 - Logan Lee’s demo during Paul Maritz’s keynote &lt;http://bcove.me/0xw8czt5&gt;, deploying Pivotal HD as a Pivotal CF service
 - Sunny Madra showcasing an app developed by Pivotal Labs on stage with Jeremy Burton
 - Pat Gellsinger’s keynote &lt;http://bcove.me/0xw8czt5&gt;, announcing VMware vCloud Hybrid Service (vCHS) supporting the latest release of Pivotal CF


For more information on EVP Solutions, please check out our Inside Pivotal EVP site &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/departments/evp&gt;.











AGILE UPDATE
Kaushik Das
 Senior Principal Data Scientist, Pivotal Data Labs







Showcasing Collaboration at EMC World

 The Pivotal booth at EMC World was centrally located and quite noticeable! Pivotal Data Labs staff were in 
the booth giving a working demo of a Social Media Sentiment Analysis Engine, where users can type in any term and an analysis of that term is carried out across Twitter feeds. I’d like to thank Derek Lin and Sarah Aerni for taking turns to explain the demo and answer questions.

How The App Works

 Visitors to the booth were able to see the incidence of tweets that contained a term over time, along with the sentiment 
associated with the tweets. They could also view word clouds that showed which topics were being talked about, and a host of other cool visuals.

 Here are a few screen shots:







 This demo was the fruit of a collaboration between Pivotal Data Labs (Data Scientists + Data Engineers) and Pivotal Labs. The fantastic GUI created by the Pivotal Labs team drew lots of attention. The topic and sentiment analysis was based on MADlib &lt;http://madlib.net/&gt; algorithms working within the Pivotal platform, which were created by Srivatsan Ramanujam.

 Thank you all for a great collaborative 
effort!












PEOPLE UPDATE
Michelle Kerr
 Vice President, Corporate Marketing







EMC World 2014 by the Numbers

 New job, new team, and great results. That sums up my experience last week at EMC World 2014 &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/emc-world-2014&gt;, and less than two weeks into the job, I know I made the right decision to join Pivotal. I’m thrilled to help contribute to the Pivotal mission, and lead a team that is already making it happen!

 The theme of EMC World was “Redefine”, and at Pivotal that is exactly what we are doing — redefining and revolutionizing the next generation platform. As a premiere member of the Federation we had wide exposure throughout the conference. The Pivotal booth was a standout, and the buzz and press and analyst interactions were notable. Below are some results of a job well done!

 By the Numbers 


 - 2069 social media mentions
 - 37 original news articles and counting &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/document/d/1tFgtBwLLaZqhvhVJeyHW1RdEVifkAVI2VnksNEcHWHI/edit&gt;
 - 28 analyst meetings
 - 27 one-to-one media briefings
 - 1 press conference with the Federation
 - 1 investor relations briefing to 80 members of Wall Street
 - 1 Main Stage Keynote with Paul Maritz &lt;http://emcworld.com/emctv.htm?id=3542110137001&gt;

 - 3 EMC TV interviews with Paul Maritz &lt;http://emcworld.com/emctv.htm?id=3541838231001&gt;, Bill Cook &lt;http://emcworld.com/emctv.htm?id=3538377709001&gt;, and Michael Weir &lt;http://emcworld.com/emctv.htm?id=3541838215001&gt;
 - 14 Breakout sessions
 - 4 Full days of vLab sessions &lt;http://www.emcworld.com/emcvlab.htm&gt;
 - 55 Booth Duty Sessions
 - 1616 Booth scans
 - 40 Booth presentations




 Thank you to all who participated in the content, presentations, sessions, demos, booth, and customer meetings that made Pivotal shine.











HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Paul Santos
 Sr. Marketing Specialist, Corporate Marketing







Hello, my name is…
 Paul Santos, but for some reason people call me “Paulie” - probably not to confuse me with Paul Maritz.

At Pivotal, 
I…
 I do marketing operations — or more specifically, I execute trade shows (like EMC World), assist with field marketing activities, work with finance to manage the marketing budget, am keeper of the Pivotal swag closet, and try to keep up with the latest office 
gossip.

You can find me…
 On the 4th floor of the San Francisco office most days of the week, but I make appearances in Palo Alto from time-to-time.

Currently, I am working on…
 Getting through June, an event tidal 
wave…Hadoop Summit, Cloud Foundry Summit, GigaOM Structure, and multiple smaller field events.

In my spare time…
 I go for long walks on the beach with my dog, Gizmo.

Something you probably don’t know about 
me…
 I have an identical twin brother that does half my work.

To me Pivotal…
 Is more than just the place I work, it is family.

 Gizmo!














WELCOME TO PIVOTAL!
 
 






Please join us in welcoming employees who have joined between 4/29 - 5/12:

Jordan Bangia, Pivotal Labs – Engineering Intern, Toronto
Cedric Cheung, Sales Ops 
– Business Analyst, Hong Kong
Matthew Dickenson, Pivotal Labs – Engineering Intern, San Francisco
Daniel Farrell, Sales – Field Engineer, Americas West
Greg Gentschev, Pivotal Labs – Product Manager, San 
Francisco
Geoffrey Giesemann, Pivotal Labs – Software Engineer, New York
Iain Gray, VP of Customer Success, North Carolina
Sunny Jain, IT – HRIS Technical Consultant, Palo Alto
Linda E Joy, Pivotal 
Labs – UX Designer, New York
Shivkumar Krishnan, App Fabric – Software Engineer, Palo Alto
Woohee Lee, Pivotal Labs – Engineering Intern, Toronto
Katherine Loughridge, Facilities – Regional Manager, Palo 
Alto
James Lyon, Sales – Account Manager, Americas West
Waqas M Malik, Pivotal Labs – Engineering Intern, Toronto
Salomé Mortazavi, Pivotal Labs – Product Designer, Toronto
Spencer 
Newsham, Sales – Account Manager, UK
SeoHong Ng, Sales – Administrative Assistant, Singapore
David Poore, Tracker – Software Engineer, Denver
Mitchell A Rose, Finance – Financial Analyst, Palo 
Alto
Leo Rossignac-Milon, CF – Engineering Intern, San Francisco
Naor Saadia, VRP – Software Engineer, Israel
Todd Sedano, Pivotal Labs – Software Engineer, Palo Alto
Sang-Don Shin, GSS 
– Customer Engineer, Australia
Stuart Smith, Sales – Account Manager, Americas West
Raoul Socher, Sales – Account Manager, Americas West
Chunmo Son, GSS – Customer Engineer, Palo Alto
Karel 
Vanbeekom, IT – Client Support Specialist, New York
Rahul Verma, Pivotal Labs – Engineering Intern, Toronto
Dennis Wendell, Sales – Field Engineer, Americas North
Bob Zinga, IT – Security Engineer, 
Palo Alto
Timothy Zorio, HR – Generalist, Palo Alto










Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
