<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.May/June 2015 (2) Webinar Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Register now for Spring Webinars: Spring Boot &amp; Devops, Boot Case Study, CI with Cloud Foundry, Java Templating</subject>
    <textOnly>Debug and Maintain your Spring Boot App
Speaker: Greg Turnquist, Pivotal

So you have decided to build an application using Spring Boot? Sooner or later, something will go wrong. It does not matter how experienced we are. How will Spring Boot help us figure out what went wrong and fix things?

This talk introduces lots of tools to help us debug and manage &quot;bootiful&quot; apps. You will learn how to use Boot&apos;s autoconfiguration report, override Boot&apos;s settings &amp; beans, create custom metrics/health checks/app info, and create custom JMX info &amp; custom CRaSH commands.
Europe
Thursday, May 28, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMDebugandMaintainyourSpringBootApp_Register.html&gt;
North America
Thursday, May 28, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMDebugandMaintainyourSpringBootApp_Register.html&gt;
A Comprehensive Spring Showcase: Personal Cloud Storage Application
Speaker: Erdem Gunay, Turkcell

Turkcell launched a personal cloud storage service few years ago. Adding new business features was costly in terms of time and budget on the legacy solution. The user experience needed to be improved. Finally, it was decided to build a new solution where Spring Boot and Spring Framework projects play crucial role as the backbone.

The project was completed just in 6 months starting from scratch. The solution was built on top of Spring Boot and many Spring IO Platform projects, allowing the development team focus on business logic instead of configuration &amp; integration details. The project has been divided into deployable modules (API, backend, migration, test automation) accessing micro services that are responsible for one task only. Join Erdem for a review of the migration effort and new architecture - all enabled by Spring Boot.
Europe
Tuesday, June 9, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMComprehensiveSpringShowcasePersonalCloudStorageApplication_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, June 9, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMComprehensiveSpringShowcasePersonalCloudStorageApp_Register.html&gt;
CI on the Cloud with Jenkins, Spring and Cloud Foundry
Speaker: Jamie O’Meara, Pivotal

This presentation will highlight an integrated development process that involves Spring code built with CloudBees Jenkins Enterprise and deployed to CloudFoundry. A software lifecycle of continuous delivery from source code control (Git) to Jenkins build (Maven and Gradle) to live deployment on a Cloud Foundry instance will be shown.

We will demo using Jenkins to do a blue/green application deployment. With a Cloud Foundry blue/green Jenkins deployment, you can push a new version of the application and have a software router add that to an existing version of the application&apos;s route. The two versions are then load-balanced, allowing for testing of the new version and easy replacement or fall-back to the existing version. Developers can run builds on private and public clouds with deploy to either/both Jenkins running on a PaaS and integrated into the PaaS. We will run a hands-on demo and show the beauty and simplicity of an integrated build pipeline with Spring, Jenkins and Cloud Foundry.
Europe
Tuesday, June 23, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMCIontheCloudwithJenkinsSpringandCloudFoundry_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, June 23, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMCIontheCloudwithJenkinsSpringandCloudFoundry_Register.html&gt;
JSTL to Thymeleaf: Transitioning Your Template
Speaker: Phil Dutson, ICON Health and Fitness

Thymeleaf is a fantastic template engine that can help you create sites faster and get code shipped. There exists however a problem, using th e template engine requires a mind-shift in how to get &quot;normal&quot; tasks accomplished. This leaves many developers in the lurch and frustrated.

In this talk I will cover the common pitfalls that developers can avoid and give examples on how to solve the common problems encountered when switching from the venerable JSTL to Thymeleaf.
Europe
Tuesday, June 30, 2015
3:00pm GMT Summer Time 
(London, GMT+01:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMJSTLtoThymeleafTransitioningYourTemplate_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, June 30, 2015
 10:00AM PDT
 (San Francisco, GMT-07:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webiar_10AMJSTLtoThymeleafTransitioningYourTemplate_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
