<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Corp Com 11-21</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 1, No. 3</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 1, No. 3

EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products

Gaining Momentum

 Next week is Thanksgiving in the US. What are you thankful for? I’m thankful that I work with people who inspire me.

 This edition of the biweekly Pivotal Newsletter displays examples of momentum, which can be found around every corner of the company; we’re gaining it at Labs, within our Data 
Products, in Finance, and in Real Estate and Facilities.

 If you’re planning to attend DataBeat’s 2013 Data Science Summit on Dec 4-5 in Redwood City, CA, don’t forget you can use promo code Piv-VIP for 20% off registration &lt;http://www.eventbrite.com/e/databeat-2013-tickets-5613606448?discount=piv-vip&gt;. Our CMO, SVP Products, and Global Head of Data Science Services are just a few of the awesome speakers &lt;http://venturebeat.com/events/databeat2013/speakers/&gt;! 

“Big results require big 
ambitions.”—Heraclitus

BUSINESS UPDATE
Edward Hieatt
 VP, Responsible for Pivotal Labs

Pivotal Labs Opportunities and Outlook

 Pivotal Labs has had quite a year. We’ve gone from 3 office locations to 7, roughly doubled in size to 420 consultants (part growth, part due to the Xtreme Labs acquisition) and we’re on track to work with over 200 clients. Another significant development was getting used to working with the Pivotal field – until this year, Labs had never had a dedicated sales team. As we move into 2014, an explicit focus will be working more hand-in-hand with other Pivotal product teams. Labs can be the tip of the spear with new clients, but there’s a huge and important opportunity for Pivotal’s products to become key parts of Labs engagements with certain types of clients.

 Recent clients include: 

 - Viacom – MTV’s “TV everywhere” application (Toronto)
 - Ugo – First Open Mobile Wallet in Canada (Toronto)
 - Covidien – in-operating room mobile concierge support over video (VBoulder)
 - Sendgrid – next generation newsletter (Boulder)
 - Sony Pictures – application to manage and store 12 petabytes of TV/movie data in cloud
 - AwesomenessTV/Dreamworks – web and mobile apps to help YouTube start to manage their channels
 - NBCUniversal – Labs engagement with Pivotal technologies (New York)
 - XO – our new mobile app resulted in 10x impressions over predecessor (New York)
 - San Francisco 49ers – iOS app for managing fan experience of new stadium (San Francisco)
 - Humana – mobile apps for wellness and rewards programs (San Francisco)
 - Funding Circle – crowdfunded loans for small business, helping with US expansion (London)
 - Not On The High Street – Etsy-like online retailer; helping them manage seasonal demand (London)


PRODUCT UPDATE
Josh Klahr
 Head of Product Management for Pivotal Data Fabric

It’s Been a Busy Time in the World of Pivotal Data Fabric!

 In the past month we’ve launched a number of new products, deepened our 
commitment to the Open Source community, and participated in one of the top Big Data industry events:

Pivotal Data Dispatch: Pivotal Data Dispatch &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/#folders/0B6bXEicnSkOQSFdRdTF6bnJXbmM&gt; (PDD) was launched in partnership with the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE Euronext) at the Pivotal Singapore Customer Summit on October 23. PDD enables enterprises to provide end users with self-service access to data from Hadoop, MPP, and legacy databases under strong security, auditing and compliance.

GemFire XD: Pivotal GemFire XD &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/document/d/1yFMYB-kFzzfj6krBnJP0cWiaJXNnr7XlxYEdpQRcChQ/edit&gt; is the industry’s premier “In-memory with Big Data” relational OLTP data store, combining the power of storing and processing data 
in memory with the scale-out persistence provided by Pivotal HD. Pivotal GemFire XD supports ANSI SQL and allows the creation of linearly scalable, highly available, elastic applications that have high throughput, low latency and are designed to run at cloud scale.

Pivotal HD:  Released on November 8, Pivotal HD Enterprise 1.1 &lt;https://emc.webex.com/emc/ldr.php?AT=pb&amp;SP=MC&amp;rID=24411527&amp;rKey=22e5996644d130aa&gt; is a commercially supported distribution of Apache Hadoop 2.0.5, which allows users to write distributed processing 
applications for large data sets across a cluster of commodity servers. This release &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B13yHK1CJuzkNVNUNnF2dklKNHM/edit&gt; includes Pivotal Realtime Services (GemFire XD beta) to the family of products that includes Pivotal Advanced Database 
Services (HAWQ) and Pivotal Command Center.

Strata Conference + Hadoop World: Pivotal made a strong showing at in New York city: 

 - One of only two Elite Sponsors, with visible signage, notebook bag insert, sponsorships of lunch, pub crawls, onsite interviews, and more.

 - Speakers and Speaking Engagements (Standing Room Only) 


 - Annika Jimenez: Visa’s Big Data Response to Cyber Threats &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/news-2/annika-jimenez-on-disruptive-data-science-at-the-strata-conference&gt;
 - Yours Truly (Josh Klahr): Designing Your Data-Centric Organization &lt;http://www.youtube.com/embed/D86udfrVzrI?autoplay=1&gt;

 - Scanned roughly 250 leads at the Pivotal booth
 - Delivered great demos &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/folderview?id=0B6bXEicnSkOQaHI5dVFjbWlDMzA&amp;usp=sharing&gt; – Pivotal Data Dispatch, Pivotal HD, HAWQ, GemFire XD, Spring XD

 - As part of the launch of Pivotal Data Dispatch, jointly hosted a party at the New York Stock Exchange with over 240 Attendees (and we rang the closing bell &lt;http://exchanges.nyx.com/new-york-stock-exchange/pivotal-celebrates-recent-launch-pivotal-data-dispatch&gt;!).


PEOPLE UPDATE
Robert O’Donovan
 Chief Finance Officer, Corporate Finance

The Who’s Who of Pivotal Finance, and Some of the Things We are Working On

 Well … Lots going on in Finance, but top of mind right now 
is that we’re working on 

 - A strategic 4 year plan for Pivotal
 - FY14 planning
 - Setting up and operationalizing systems and process in our business
 - Building strong business partnerships and providing insights into our business to help Pivotal to grow and be successful


The Finance team likes to work hard, and also have some fun. Since the team is quite new, I thought I would take this opportunity to introduce them and share a few fun facts.

Kelly Yagi is our Corporate FP&amp;A (Financial Planning &amp; Analysis) leader as well as managing Finance Operations &amp; Commissions. Outside the office, Kelly likes to spend most of his time with his family, including his wife and two sons. He loves sports, fishing and biking. Kelly is a big Johnny Cash fan and can frequently be heard singing cowboy songs around the office.

Mike LeBlanc provides finance support for Products &amp; Platform and GSS and is working on a number of cross-Pivotal operational workstreams – including 
facilities, T&amp;E, inventory, and more. In his spare time, Mike is trying to get to know California with his family (wife Jane, 4 year old daughter Josie, and 1 year old son Oliver).

Lori Ellingboe manages everything “tax&quot; related, except payroll taxes. Lori is training for a trek around Mont Blanc (Switzerland, Italy, France) next summer with her kids and her brother’s family.

Greg Wright is the Accounting Controller and is “growing a killer stache” (these are his words). He enjoys watching Boston teams win championships, playing bar shuffleboard, chasing his puppy around Chrissy Field, skiing, getting injured in stupid ways and complaining about the weather in SF.

Ed Ho works on Business Strategy and spends his spare time with his 
family trying to see what California has to offer, being recent transplants from the cold Northeast. Something you probably don’t know about him is that he really isn’t a finance person (in his own words…although being an economist, he is fairly close to being one of us!).

Matt Eng runs Finance and Business Operations for Pivotal Labs and Cloud 
Foundry. Matt is a New England Patriots fan and stays active by swimming, biking, running, skiing and enjoying time with his family. He also owns a rather infamous couch, which is housed in his office in SF!

 Last, but not least…

Norma Stanton is the (awesome) admin support to our Finance and Legal departments. When she’s not setting up meetings, creating expense reports, and getting us up on Inside Pivotal (coming soon) and Socialcast &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/90728-finance&gt;, she enjoys spending time with her 
family, going shopping, and trying to get out to see the world as much as possible. Something you might not know about her is that she is a big San Jose Sharks hockey fan!

PEOPLE UPDATE
Lisa Davern
 Director, Real Estate &amp; Facilities

What Is New in Real Estate &amp; Facilities?

At Pivotal Real Estate and Facilities &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/real-estate-and-facilities/home&gt; (REF), our mission is to align our physical location strategy with Pivotal&apos;s business strategy and concentrate our resources where they will be best utilized. We are in the beginning phases of defining our Global Location Strategy with leadership input and plan to have our road towards REF success by Q1 &apos;2014. Some changes to work sites have simultaneously occurred while we are still defining the Strategy based on immediate business needs.

 We have determined that Pivotal’s Headquarters will consist of two sites: 


 - San Francisco (North Bay HQ): We expanded in San Francisco to an additional floor in August of this year. We now occupy the 4th and 5th floors of 875 Howard Street. This is the first site to blend all Pivotal businesses. Christian Sepulveda (Pivotal Labs) led the project team to a successful opening of the 4th floor. Michael McGinley and Liz Miller help make the day-to-day operations of this office a vibrant, efficient, and collaborative place to work!
 - Palo Alto (South Bay HQ): Starting the week of January 2, 2014, we will be relocating and expanding the South Bay Area HQ site from San Mateo to 3495 Deer Creek Road in Palo Alto. We will be the sole tenant in this 2-story, 80,000+ square foot building. This site will also blend all Pivotal businesses and give Pivotal Labs a launching pad for their South Bay business growth.


Other exciting site updates this year: 


 - NYC: We expanded and relocated from 841 Broadway to 625 Avenue of the Americas. Josh Knowles (Pivotal Labs), was the front-runner in finding and implementing this new location, Michael Schubert was critical to the set-up of the day-to-day operations and Stephen Patrick, Renata Granderson-Williams and Brianne Brown keep everything running smoothly each day!
 - China (Shanghai &amp; Beijing): We opened two new serviced office locations - Ray Feng (Head of R&amp;D Center, China) was forefront to moving Engineering and Global Support in China to serviced office locations.
 - London: We are opening our new London office in the Shoredictch Area of London during the first week of December. JB Steadman (Pivotal Labs) has had this vision of expansion and worked effortlessly to bring it to fruition. In addition to JB, we had a lot of local leadership input from Alexis Richardson (Application Products), Michael Nautusch (Data Science), and Russell Acton (GTM). Another consolidated location for all Pivotal businesses to collaborate!
 - Bentonville, Arkansas: This is another new office, opening the first week of December. We have been collaborating with David Saunders (Field Engineering), who is working on the Walmart account.

HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Michael Barinek
 Director of Engineering, Pivotal Labs Boulder/Denver

At Pivotal, I…
 Founded the Pivotal Labs Boulder office in 2010 and recently opened the Pivotal Labs Denver office.

You can find me…
 Splitting my 
time between the Boulder and Denver offices.

Currently, I’m working on…
 Sales, recruiting, project delivery, and client relationship/satisfaction management.

In my spare time…
 I enjoy the mountains, 
snowboarding, and hikes with the family. I&apos;m also an avid golfer.

Something you probably don’t know about me…
 In addition to a MS in Software Engineering, I have a MS degree in Metamorphic Petrology and have led Geology field courses in Colorado and Utah.

To me, 
Pivotal…
 Is all about smart people pairing on great projects. 

Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
