<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.10-13-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of October 13, 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of October 13, 2014
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
ANDREW CLAY SHAFER, DEVOPS POLYMATH, JOINS PIVOTAL
Join us for our ongoing podcast series, All Things Pivotal, covering technology at the intersection of cloud, agile development, and big data, and what it all means for business. Every week, host Simon Elisha will share the latest news, interview Pivotal technologists, and explore how people are harnessing sophisticated data and cloud technologies to build applications that achieve extraordinary things. Episode two, &quot;Why customers want to use Pivotal CF&quot; will be available this Wednesday, October 15.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
CHURN PREDICTION IN RETAIL FINANCE AND ASSET MANAGEMENT (PART 2)
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/churn-prediction-in-retail-finance-and-asset-management-part-2-2&gt;
In our previous blog post &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/case-studies-2/churn-prediction-in-retail-finance-and-asset-management-part-1&gt;, we detailed the challenges of establishing the dependent variable given varying definitions of “customer” and “churn”. Here, we look at predictive and explanatory modeling including data assets, analytics algorithms, and resulting customer applications. Financial firms collect large volumes of data from all realms of our daily lives. These data assets are used to build predictive models for many purposes, such as understanding and predicting customer behavior. 


READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/case-studies-2/churn-prediction-in-retail-finance-and-asset-management-part-2-2&gt;
APACHE WAY AT PIVOTAL
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/apache-way-at-pivotal&gt;
This post explores Pivotal&apos;s relationship with the Apache Software Foundation and &quot;The Apache Way&quot;, or the ASF governance model. There’s a lot to be said on what a winning open-source strategy looks like. Whatever it is, if you are an enterprise infrastructure vendor in 2014, you can’t survive without having one. The only sustainable way of doing so is to build long-term relationships with open source communities. This, of course, means that businesses now find themselves thinking deep and hard about open source community governance.


READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/apache-way-at-pivotal&gt;
- NYC: Big Data Jam Session with Pivotal and Isilon at Strata - October 16 &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/strata-hadoop-world-big-data-jam-session-pivotal-isilon&gt;
 - Three Ways to Use Cloud as a Service &lt;http://www.wired.com/2014/09/three-ways-cloud-as-service/&gt;
 - Hadoop Wins Converts Outside of Silicon Valley &lt;http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2014-10-09/hadoop-data-software-spreads-beyond-silicon-valley&gt;
 - OpenStack Founding Father McKenty Joins Pivotal’s Cloud Foundry Team as CTO &lt;http://www.datacenterknowledge.com/archives/2014/09/30/openstack-founder-mckenty-to-lead-pivotals-cloud-foundry/&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
