<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pivotal IT Comm.9-23 Old Domains</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Closing out Google Apps for &apos;gopivotal&apos; + ‘pivotallabs’ and Important Actions</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi All,

We’ve been working from our new pivotal.io &lt;http://pivotal.io/&gt; domain for a few months now. Bringing the company to a single domain has made it easier for teams across Pivotal to work together, and we appreciate your patience and cooperation to help us get here.

Take Action Now 
All of your data should now be in your pivotal.io &lt;http://pivotal.io/&gt; account.  Please check that you have your email messages, Google Drive docs, and that any Sites you own are intact and transitioned. 

Closing out Google Apps for &apos;gopivotal&apos; + 
‘pivotallabs’ 
On Tuesday, October 21st, we will turn off everyone&apos;s access to the old gopivotal.com &lt;http://gopivotal.com/&gt; and pivotallabs.com &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/&gt; accounts for Google Apps.
 



 -  Email sent to your @gopivotal.com &lt;http://gopivotal.com/&gt; or @pivotallabs.com &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/&gt; email address will continue to forward to your @pivotal.io &lt;http://pivotal.io/&gt; account indefinitely, even after access to your old account is turned off. 
 - Your old Google Apps account and its contents will be held in backup until November 24th, but you will need IT’s help to access it. 
 - On Monday, November 24th, we will delete the old accounts and their contents, and you will not be able to recover data from them, even with the help of IT.


Once again, please take time to have one last look to ensure that you have everything you need in your new pivotal.io &lt;http://pivotal.io/&gt; account.

If you have trouble finding anything, please let us know. We’re here to help! You can reach us at: ask@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:ask@pivotal.io&gt;

Drew</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
