<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.7-7-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of July 7, 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of July 7, 2014
&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/agile/press-release/06262014-pivotal-releases-spring-io-platform&gt;
SPRING IO RELEASE FROM PIVOTAL EXTENDS THE PLATFORMS DRIVING MODERN APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT
Pivotal, the company at the intersection of big data, PaaS, and agile development, today announced that it has released Version 1.0 of Spring IO™ &lt;http://spring.io/platform&gt;. Open source, lean, and modular, Spring IO brings together the core Spring APIs into a single, cohesive and versioned foundation for modern applications to help Java developers innovate and develop applications faster. Spring IO supports any modern enterprise Java workload – mobile, web apps, integration, web services, batch, relational, noSQL, reactive and big data applications, as well as APIs and micro services. Enterprises save time and costs, and can innovate and go to market faster.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/agile/press-release/06262014-pivotal-releases-spring-io-platform&gt;
HEADLINE IN ALL CAPS FOR UPCOMING PODCAST
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
PIVOTAL AND EMC COME TOGETHER TO SHORE UP THE DATA LAKE
&lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-and-emc-come-together-to-shore-up-the-data-lake&gt;
Pivotal and EMC have combined to shore up the way forward for the Business Data Lake to right size the economics and complexity of big data. Today, EMC and Pivotal are releasing a new turnkey bundle that packages EMC’s leading Isilon technology with Pivotal’s enterprise hardened Hadoop distribution, Pivotal HD &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-hd&gt;. Together, these technologies solve some of the enterprise’s hardest problems around big data, including failover, backup, replication and scalability. With these challenges addressed, enterprises of all sizes now have the help they need to bridge their big data efforts to a Data Lake architecture quickly and affordably. 


READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-and-emc-come-together-to-shore-up-the-data-lake&gt;
PIVOTAL HAWQ BENCHMARK DEMONSTRATES UP TO 21X FASTER PERFORMANCE ON HADOOP QUERIES THAN SQL-LIKE SOLUTIONS
&lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/products/pivotal-hawq-benchmark-demonstrates-up-to-21x-faster-performance-on-hadoop-queries-than-sql-like-solutions&gt;
This week at the ACM SIGMOD Conference &lt;http://www.sigmod2014.org&gt;, the premier international forum for database researchers, practitioners and users, Pivotal announced the architectural benefits and results for its brand-new cost-based query optimizer. The results bore out Pivotal’s statement that HAWQ &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/white-paper/a-true-sql-engine-for-hadoop-pivotal-hd-hawq&gt; is the world’s fastest SQL query engine on Hadoop, with benchmarks demonstrating it is capable of up to 21 times faster performance and three times the queries supported for Hadoop. Moreover, it showed the performance and productivity improvements that a 100% ANSI SQL compliant optimizer such as HAWQ can offer in comparison to other solutions which only offer SQL-Like Compliance.



READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/products/pivotal-hawq-benchmark-demonstrates-up-to-21x-faster-performance-on-hadoop-queries-than-sql-like-solutions&gt;
- Why Big Data Is The New Natural Resource &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/ibm/2014/06/30/why-big-data-is-the-new-natural-resource/&gt; 
 - Price Wars: Parallels Between Airlines and the Public Cloud &lt;http://www.eweek.com/blogs/storage-station/price-wars-parallels-between-airlines-and-the-public-cloud.html&gt;

 - 
OpenStack and Cloud Foundry Poised to Transform Managed Services &lt;http://mspmentor.net/cloud-computing/062714/openstack-and-cloud-foundry-poised-transform-managed-services&gt;


 - 
5 More Reasons Tesla&apos;s Open Source Policy Could Make It Rich &lt;http://www.fool.com/investing/general/2014/06/30/5-more-reasons-teslas-open-source-policy-could-mak.aspx&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
