<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.GS - Monthly Announcement May 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Field Operations: May Sales News Flash</subject>
    <textOnly>PIVOTAL FIELD OPERATIONS
A Message from Greg Stroud
MAY 2014 SALES NEWS FLASH
Global Field Operations Team,
Starting this month, we are increasing our field communications to send you on a monthly basis, an update of all things new and pertinent to Sales. With that being said, please take the time to read the communication carefully; as there are a number of policy, process, and pricing changes that you should be aware of. 
What’s New
Deal Desk Improvements are on the way. We are happy to announce that there is some improvements coming to the Deal Desk in Q3, which will maximize Sales Management visibility, boost deal value, decrease the time to approval and reduce the possibility of end of quarter issues.
ACTION: We have established a new Interim Process for NON-STANDARD proposals: Effective immediately, you will be required to follow these steps before you may make any non-standard proposals (this includes discounts greater than the rep level).


 - Ensure that your SFDC Opportunity reflects what you are going to propose to the customer
 - The Deal Desk Approval Form &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANT29PTldGd0wxUlhuMmhsQ25maVVSNWF0ZXhv/edit?usp=sharing&gt; must be downloaded, completed and attached to the SFDC Opportunity
 - Contact the Deal Desk using @deal_desk in the Opportunity’s chatter feed


The Deal Desk will turn around non-standard proposal approvals within 48 hours. If you have any questions regarding the process please feel free to contact the deal desk at pivotal-deal-desk@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:pivotal-deal-desk@gopivotal.com&gt;.
SFDC Updates. After our SFDC April cleanup, the data is looking better than ever. Help keep it that way by revisiting these bad data reports &lt;http://connect.gopivotal.com/625IUJ0090001n900o9dD00&gt; and make sure they are clean. We will remind you to cleanse any bad data on a quarterly basis as well.
Product upon opportunity entry is now required. When an opportunity is entered, you will now be prompted to add products immediately after saving their new entry.
Opportunity Lead Source field is now required. This field is typically auto-populated, but if blank, you will need to pick the appropriate referral source before you are able to continue and submit.
Single Sign-On (SSO) is coming to SFDC within the next few weeks and you will no longer need to type a username/password to access SFDC. To access SFDC through SSO, please use this link https://pivotal.my.salesforce.com &lt;https://pivotal.my.salesforce.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank&gt; to access. You may continue to leverage SSO through Okta as well.
Big Data Suite and APP Suite SKUs will be available in mid-June with more detail to come in the June Field communication. For questions on selling the Big Data Suite, please contact pivotal-deal-desk@gopivotal. Rabbit MQ commercial and Web Server SKUs were removed on May 12th. The only SKUs that remain available though EMC Select include the vFabric Suite, tc Server and Open Source Support SKUs.
Register for Pivotal Network. Starting April 14th, any customer may go to Pivotal Network to evaluate our full portfolio of products. We encourage you to log in and familiarize yourself with the system at https://network.gopivotal.com &lt;http://connect.gopivotal.com/625IUJ0090001nc00o9dD00%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank&gt;. Pivotal and EMC customers will be directed to Pivotal Network to download their licensed products. Sales of Pivotal products through VMware will continue to be delivered through the VMware customer portal.
Re-launch of Business Critical Support. This Service provides remote
 designated support engineers to compliment Pivotal Premium Support.
 Additional information on Business Critical Support may be found here &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANVC1mOHloQUthbWotRTBoQ09mWXpPdF9JQWxn/edit?usp=sharing&gt; and on the Field Operations Inside Pivotal page. Remote Designated Support Engineer services receive 1x commission and receive quota retirement.
Pivotal Data Dispatch should no longer be actively introduced into your accounts. We do not want you to quote or sell PDD at this time. If you have already introduced PDD into your sales cycles, please work with Jim Totte in business development and Oak Barrett in product management to work out the appropriate course of action. 
Federation Rules of Engagement, including compensation models through the EMC and VMware channels may be found here &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANZDVWYjUwa1Rxdk0/edit?usp=sharing&gt;.
Resource Links


 - Pivotal Ts &amp; Cs &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANdm0za21JYllHaGJCLU5lQ2Vpa3BJQURHbXE0/edit?usp=sharing&gt;
 - Global Field Operations Inside Pivotal page &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/departments/global_field-operations&gt;


Regards,
Greg</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
