<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.Sales Announcement 10-22</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Product Announcements from Scott Aronson</subject>
    <textOnly>Team - 

This week, three big announcements will help demonstrate Pivotal&apos;s leadership. 
The first highlights our success in APJ with the inaugural Asia Pacific Pivotal Summit and the opening of The Pivotal Innovation Centre in Singapore. As the first lab of its kind in Asia, this unique space will be a collaborative testing ground for customers, providing Pivotal resources dedicated to developing advanced proof of concepts and prototypes across all industries. Please join me in congratulating the APJ team. Both The Centre and The Summit will be a launching pad for growth in APJ.

 On October 23rd, Pivotal will announce two significant additions to the Data Fabric portfolio. These products represent our continued innovation and commitment to helping enterprise customers maximize value from Big Data, on Hadoop and beyond. 
Below you&apos;ll find links that will point you to related training materials and FAQ sheets to help prepare for customer conversations.

New Product Announcement: Pivotal Data Dispatch

Pivotal Data Dispatch (PDD) brings on-demand, self-service data access to the Big Data worker. Pivotal Data Dispatch enables IT to establish approved, controlled environments for end users to access internal and external datasets from Hadoop, NoSQL and traditional databases. GA&apos;ing in Q4 2013, Pivotal Data Dispatch is a software product originally developed by NYSE Technologies, and exclusively licensed, re-branded, supported and taken to market by Pivotal.

To learn more about pricing, packaging, the NYSE technologies relationship, support and services please visit our FAQ &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0BzpvA8bvSbSXM2tiaTBLcWY2OUU/edit?usp=sharing&gt;. For sales training, check out Pivotal&apos;s field enablement site &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/#folders/0B6bXEicnSkOQSFdRdTF6bnJXbmM&gt; for a spotlight webinar and slides.

New Product Announcement: Pivotal HD with Pivotal GemFire XD

Pivotal brings in-memory data processing to Hadoop with Pivotal HD 1.1 and Pivotal GemFire XD. This proven enterprise class in-memory data service delivers a unique data platform for real-time applications on Hadoop, and when combined with HAWQ, delivers a commercially supported package for closed-loop analytics. Pivotal GemFire XD is a software product that will be available in &apos;beta&apos; as an add-on package with Pivotal HD, starting with Pivotal HD 1.1 within its GA release in November 2013.

To learn more about pricing, packaging, support and services please visit our FAQ &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/document/d/1yFMYB-kFzzfj6krBnJP0cWiaJXNnr7XlxYEdpQRcChQ/edit&gt;. For sales training, check out Pivotal&apos;s field enablement site &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/#folders/0B6bXEicnSkOQSWVSa1dPUjNxNGc&gt; for slides. The spotlight webinar will be available soon on Socialcast and Salesforce.com.

News like this is a great start to Q4. 
Let&apos;s use it to our advantage. 

Best of luck in your pursuits...

- sa




© Pivotal - FOR INTERNAL USE ONLY - DO NOT DISTRIBUTE.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
