<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Webinar_The Business Data Lake – an evolution in Data InfrastructureQ114.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You&apos;re Invited: The Business Data Lake Presented by Pivotal and Capgemini</subject>
    <textOnly>Webinar: The Business Data Lake – an Evolution in Data Infrastructure
Hi {{lead.First Name:default=there}},
Join us &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/Datalakewebinarregister.html&gt; for our monthly webinar series, &quot;What You Can Do With Hadoop.” Each session will contain both technical and business topics, use cases, thought leadership from industry experts, customer examples and more. Our next webinar – The Business Data Lake – an Evolution in Data Infrastructure – is scheduled for Thursday, January 23, 2014 at 9AM PST. 
 &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/Datalakewebinarregister.html&gt;

Capgemini and Pivotal are joining forces to take Hadoop to the next level of business transformation. Announcing our strategic partnership &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/press-center/12042013-capgemini&gt; last December, Capgemini and Pivotal are co-innovating around Big Data and analytics to address the increasing volumes of data organizations are facing today. Our first area of focus showcases a new approach to data access and analytics: the Business Data Lake. 
The Business Data Lake promises to increase the amount of data being captured and stored using Hadoop, and more importantly increase the amount of data being analyzed and operationalized within the business – turning insight into action. Please join us &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/Datalakewebinarregister.html&gt; for this exclusive webinar with Capgemini and learn how the Business Data Lake:







 - Can become the rich data repository for future business needs
 - Allows IT to address business needs in a timely and efficient manner
 - Utilizes Hadoop as the data substrate to help build Big Data applications of the future
 - Impacts business and operations with greater degree of insight
 - Helps increase top line revenue
 - Plans to bring the enterprise and industrial Internet in parallel with the consumer Internet









We look forward to your participation, 
The Pivotal Team




Have questions? Contact us &lt;mailto:pivotal-operations@gopivotal.com&gt;.
Check out Pivotal P.O.V.
Visit our blog &gt;&gt; &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/&gt;
Pivotal HD Community Forum
Join Now &gt;&gt; &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/community/pivotal-hd&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
