<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Event_CFPlatform_Q214.canopy emil</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>CF Summit Recap - Sent by Pivotal on behalf of Canopy</subject>
    <textOnly>July 2014





 &lt;http://www.canopy-cloud.com&gt;


 












Follow up to 
Cloud Foundry Summit



 As a Gold sponsor of the Cloud Foundry Summit in San Francisco a couple of weeks ago, Canopy would like to thank you for attending and hope that you found the event valuable and enjoyable. 

 We&apos;d like to recap two significant announcements &lt;http://www.canopy-cloud.com/press-release/june-11-enterprise-paas-cloud-platform-for-digital-business&gt; that we made at Cloud Foundry Summit, and invite &lt;http://www.bit.ly/cloudfabric&gt; you to a webinar on July 8th to learn more.




Canopy joins Cloud Foundry Foundation










Canopy and Pivotal announced that Canopy is joining the Cloud Foundry Foundation as a Silver member






We&apos;re excited about helping to create an open ecosystem to foster the growth and development of enterprise Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) that&apos;s agile, flexible and easy to use.




Introducing Canopy Cloud Fabric powered by Pivotal CF










Canopy announced we&apos;re extending our cloud platform for adaptive digital enterprise with the new Canopy Cloud Fabric solution which delivers Pivotal CF as a managed cloud service with additional value-add from Canopy







 With Canopy Cloud Fabric you get the best of Pivotal CF coupled with: 


 - Choice of tenancy options to meet various levels of dedication: multi-tenant, virtual private or fully private
 - Choice of locations around the world to meet data locality/sovereignty requirements
 - Choice of hosting arrangements, including the option to host your own dedicated private PaaS in your own datacentre
 - Range of application and data services provided and managed by Canopy, including the option to host services locally to your application to remove network latency issues 
 - Consulting, customisation and developer services to customise the solution to meet the specific needs of your organization 
 - All of the above managed and supported by Canopy with rock solid enterprise class service levels.



To learn more, attend &lt;http://www.bit.ly/cloudfabric&gt; our webinar on July 8th and to take Canopy Cloud Fabric for a test drive apply &lt;mailto:cloudfabric_admin@canopy-cloud.com?subject=Application to join Canopy Cloud Fabric Early Adopter Program&gt; to join our Early Adopter Program.











What next?








Attend Adaptive Digital Enterprise Webinar




 Join our webinar on July 8th to learn how Canopy can help you to cloud-enable existing applications, as well as accelerate development of new cloud-native applications. &lt;#1&gt; 
 &lt;http://www.bit.ly/cloudfabric&gt;














Apply for Cloud Fabric Early Adopter Program




 Canopy is offering an early adopter program through which qualifying organizations can test drive the Canopy Cloud Fabric service with no charge for a limited time.  &lt;#1&gt;

 &lt;mailto:cloudfabric_admin@canopy-cloud.com?subject=Application to join Canopy Cloud Fabric Early Adopter Program&gt;














Follow us




Want to stay up to date on what we&apos;re doing around PaaS and big data/analytics? &lt;#1&gt;
 &lt;http://www.twitter.com/CanopyPaaS&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/canopy-cloud&gt;
 &lt;http://www.facebook.com/Canopy&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/user/canopycloud&gt;





















 Atos, EMC and VMware bring you Canopy &lt;http://www.canopy-cloud.com&gt;, an end-to-end provider of enterprise cloud services</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
