<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.May(3) 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Spring integration 4.0-The New Frontier, Data-Driven Apps with Spring and Neo4j, and Spring Ask Me Anything</subject>
    <textOnly>Spring Integration 4.0 - The New Frontier
The Spring Integration team has been hard at work on the latest release of the popular integration framework. Before version 4.0, it was impractical to define a complete Spring Integration flow without using XML. With this major release, the existing basic annotation support has received an overhaul and those who prefer to use java @Configuration classes can now define their applications without needing to use any XML (of course, XML is still supported as well).
 
In this session we will cover these major changes to the framework, explaining how and when to use them. It will be mainly demonstration and code walk through, and we will build a useful Spring Boot / Integration application from scratch.)
Europe
Tuesday, May 13, 2014
3:00pm BST Time
(London, UTC+01:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_SpringIntegration4.0TheNewFrontier7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, May 13, 2014
10:00am PDT
(San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_SpringIntegration4.0TheNewFrontier10AM_Register.html&gt;
Data-Driven Applications with Spring and Neo4j
Speakers: Josh Long (Pivotal) and Michael Hunger (Neo Technology)

Spring Data Neo4j 3.0 is here and it supports Neo4j 2.0. Neo4j is a tiny graph database with a big punch. Graph databases are imminently suited to asking interesting questions, and doing analysis. Want to load the Facebook friend graph? Build a recommendation engine? Neo4j&apos;s just the ticket. Join Spring Data Neo4j lead Michael Hunger (@mesirii) and Spring Developer Advocate Josh Long (@starbuxman) for a look at how to build smart, graph-driven applications with Spring Data Neo4j and Spring Boot. 50 lucky registrants per event will get free copies of Spring Data: Modern Data Access for Enterprise Java! &lt;http://shop.oreilly.com/product/0636920024767.do&gt;
Europe
Tuesday, May 20, 2014
3:00pm BST Time
(London, UTC+01:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_Neo4JTechnology7AM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, May 20, 2014
10:00am PDT
(San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_Neo4JTechnology10AM_Register.html&gt;
Spring Ask Me Anything
Speaker: Josh Long

Join us for a one-hour office hours with Spring community advocate, Josh Long. Josh will bring along guests from the Spring teams at each &quot;episode&quot; to focus on particular topics.

 

Speaker: Josh Long

Join us again next month for a one-hour office hours with Spring community advocate, Josh Long. Each month Josh and a member of the Spring team will explore a new topic.
North America
Thursday, May 22, 2014
 12:00pm PDT 
 (San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_May_AskmeanythingaboutSpring12PM_Register.html&gt;
North America
Thursday, June 26, 2014
 12:00pm PDT 
 (San Francisco, UTC-07:00)
Register &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/OSS_Webinar_June_AskmeanythingaboutSpring12PM_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
