<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global_Event_Cloud Platform Roadshow - CenturyLink_Q215.Atlanta Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank you for Attending the Cloud Platform Seminar in Atlanta</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {{lead.First Name:default=There}},

Thank you for attending the recent Cloud Platform Seminar in Atlanta showcasing Pivotal Cloud Foundry (PCF) on CenturyLink Cloud. You can access the content that was presented from the links below.

We were excited to share CenturyLink’s transformation journey with Pivotal Cloud Foundry and hope the hands-on workshops gave you the opportunity to experience the ease of deploying PCF on CenturyLink 
using CenturyLink Blueprints, and the speed of pushing an app on PCF.

Whether you attended one or all of the sessions, we hope you gained a deeper understanding of how a cloud native platform such as PCF can accelerate and simplify how you develop, deploy and scale applications 
in the cloud.

If you would like to learn more, please contact us &lt;mailto:info@pivotal.io&gt; to schedule a technical evaluation of Pivotal Cloud Foundry with the Pivotal team.  Interested in 
understanding CenturyLink’s Cloud Services better? Learn more here &lt;http://www.centurylink.com/business/enterprise/cloud/cloud-computing.html&gt;.

Your feedback is important to us. Please take our short survey &lt;https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/RXNJQ2K&gt; so that we can continue to make future workshops informative and relevant. 

Our presentation slides are available to you here:

 


 - Software Kept Eating the World &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/pivotal-centurylink-cloud-platform-seminar-presentations-software-kept-eating-the-world&gt;
 - Customer Use Case: CenturyLink and Their Journey to Cloud Foundry &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/pivotal-centurylink-cloud-platform-seminar-presentation-customer-use-case-centurylink-and-their-journey-to-cloud-foundry&gt;
 - The Developer Experience &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/pivotal-centurylink-cloud-platform-seminar-presentation-the-developer-experience&gt;
 - Architecture &amp; Operations &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/pivotal-centurylink-cloud-platform-seminar-presentations-architecture-operations&gt;
 - Enabling Continuous Delivery &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/pivotal-centurylink-cloud-platform-seminar-presentations-enabling-continuous-delivery&gt;




Thank you again for joining us,
Pivotal and CenturyLink</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
