<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>SystemMaster_HR_Comm.Joe Comm 5-16-draft3174</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Directory and Organization Charts Now Available in Social Cast</subject>
    <textOnly>Pivotal Directory and Organization Charts Now Available in Social Cast
I’m very excited to introduce a great new feature to our Social Cast application: The Pivotal Directory and Organization Charts! &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/home&gt; This feature will enable more visibility into the People of Pivotal – allowing employees to find colleagues and view the organizations they report into. To access the organization charts, sign into Social Cast, search for a colleague, and below their name you will be able to select “View Org Chart”. You can toggle through the chart or search for people directly. 


The Pivotal Directory will be only as good as the profiles in it, and it’s built for you to customize your profile. Each Pivotal employee now has a basic Social Cast directory profile that includes name, title and location information. We encourage each of you to personalize your information, adding details such job titles, phone numbers, and pictures, to make it easier for colleagues to connect with you.

Going Mobile

Social Cast is also mobile enabled! To download the app, visit the App Store, search for “socialcast”. Once downloaded, enter Pivotal’s community name gopivotal-com.socialcast.com. Your user name will be your gopivotal e-mail address and your password will be your social cast password.

If you have any trouble accessing Social Cast or if you have corrections to any information that is not editable – please submit a request to askIT@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:askit@gopivotal.com&gt;. 

Let us know how it goes by providing your comments and feedback on the Social Cast Human Resources Group page.

Thank you, 

Joe

VP, People



Search any person within Socialcast and find “View Org chart” below their name:



Click on the “View Org Chart” to get expanded reporting lines and teams:</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
