<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Webinar_ Spring_Webinar Monthly Program.January 2015 Webinar Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spring Webinars: Building Scalable Data Apps w/Spring &amp; GemFire and Introducing Java DSL for Spring Integration</subject>
    <textOnly>Building Scalable Data Applications with Spring and GemFire
Speaker: Luke Shannon
 
 GemFire is Pivotal&apos;s distributed In Memory Data grid. In this session we will cover simplifying configuring a GemFire grid using Spring Data GemFire, and explore how data is dynamically distributed and made highly available as the grid resources are increased or decreased to meet increased client demand. GemFire access and testing patterns using Spring will be reviewed in detail. 
 
 We will walk through creating a domain object and using Spring Data GemFire Repositories to perform CRUD operations on a GemFire grid, creating a Spring MVC/Spring Boot application that uses GemFire as its persistence layer, review how Spring Boot and Spring Data GemFire can be used to help with GemFire test cases and how Spring Data GemFire can make creation and execution of GemFire functions easier. We will also explore how Spring XD can be used to load and monitor data changes in the grid. This will be a hands on, code oriented session.
Europe
Tuesday, January 13, 2015
 3:00PM GMT Time
 (London, GMT)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMBuildingScalableDataApplicationswithSpringandGemFire_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, January 13, 2015
 10:00AM PST
 (San Francisco, GMT-08:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMBuildingScalableDataApplicationswithSpringandGemFire_Register.html&gt;
Introducing the Java DSL for Spring Integration
Speaker: Gary Russell
 
 The Spring Integration JavaConfig and DSL extension provides a set of convenient Builders and a fluent API to configure Spring Integration message flows from Spring @Configuration classes. The Java DSL for Spring Integration is essentially a facade for Spring Integration. The DSL provides a simple way to embed Spring Integration Message Flows into your application using the fluent Builder pattern together with existing Java and Annotation configurations from Spring Framework and Spring Integration as well. Another useful tool to simplify configuration is Java 8 Lambdas.

Developers joining this webinar will learn the DSL basics and see it in action.
Europe
Tuesday, January 27, 2015
 3:00PM GMT Time
 (London, GMT)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_7AMIntroducingtheJavaDSLforSpringIntegration_Register.html&gt;
North America
Tuesday, January 27, 2015
 10:00AM PST
 (San Francisco, GMT-08:00)
Register &lt;http://connect.pivotal.io/OSS_Webinar_10AMIntroducingtheJavaDSLforSpringIntegration_Register.html&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
