<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.GS- Monthly Announcement June 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Field Operations: June Sales News Flash</subject>
    <textOnly>PIVOTAL FIELD OPERATIONS
A Message from Greg Stroud
JUNE 2014 SALES NEWS FLASH
Global Field Operations Team,
As we enter the last month of the quarter, please take the time to read the communication carefully; as there are a number of policy, process, and pricing changes that you should be aware of. 
Your SFDC Opportunities Matter
The opportunities/deals that you are working as part of your total pipeline are the fuel of Pivotal. Visibility into your deals through the Salesforce application is critical. Every deal matters! The executives and GTM product teams are taking action and making strategic company decisions based on the data that you are providing on your opportunities. So make sure that all of your deals, both in and out of Quarter, are in SFDC, and expect to see more emphasis on opportunity management in the coming months.
Scheduling Your Pivotal EBC - Opportunity Must be in SFDC
As you reach out for EBC support, you will be asked to provide the associated SFDC Opportunity number. Please have this information handy. Information to help you plan your customer EBC may be found here &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANOGxEWW1pV1FWazdjdjJXOVRWTEVrV295UUow/edit?usp=sharing&gt; and the list of all EBC speakers and their areas of expertise may be found here &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AruO4XIa64ANdGkzWU1WeE1NMlFSclJHdUNOcG5WcVE&amp;usp=sharing&gt;.
Compensation for BDS/PCF Subscription Renewals
The sales force will be compensated in FY15 for subscription renewals of the BDS and PCF product! This should alleviate any confusion so keep selling!
Got a Question About Pivotal Product Pricing?
Q2 Product Availability &amp; Pricing &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AruO4XIa64ANdGVNUW00d2F0NWZ0TGhzTGJrSkFkNFE&amp;usp=sharing&gt; is your one-stop resource for Pivotal pricing information. We recommend that you bookmark this page.
Operations Update - What’s New
Business Management
 As Pivotal grows the Sales Operations team is expanding and formalizing its support &amp; alignment to each business unit. The Business Management function will focus on Forecasting/Pipeline, Bookings, Financial Management, and Reporting.  We have put in place resources in each of the territories below to ensure coverage as we move forward. Check out the new Sales/Operations Territory Mapping here &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B7uO4XIa64ANU2NOTVZFbjJzbk0/edit?usp=sharing&gt;. 
Federal &amp; North
Business Manager - Chris Braney
Deal Desk – Ian Manter
West &amp; South
Business Manager – Chris Want
Deal Desk – Tom Kadlick
APJ
Business Manager - David Lo
Deal Desk – Eric Landon
EMEA
Business Manager – Ian Bignell
Deal Desk – Eric Landon
Moving forward, if you have any questions relating to business operations, your starting point will be the Business Managers.
Pivotal Customer Service. Global Support Services is in the midst of building out a new Pivotal Customer Service Team. Today, there is a small team that is able to assist in servicing you and your customer’s requests to provide a single entry point into the Customer Technical Support Team.  The current team is located in Palo Alto but they will soon have a Global Team providing 24X7 assistance. You can contact the Customer Service Team in the following ways:
Submit a Support Ticket here &lt;https://support.gopivotal.com/hc/en-us&gt;
How do I register for Pivotal Support? &lt;https://support.gopivotal.com/hc/en-us/articles/202277046-How-do-I-register-for-Pivotal-Support-&gt;
How do I submit a technical support request? &lt;https://support.gopivotal.com/hc/en-us/articles/202278056-How-do-I-submit-a-request-for-Pivotal-support-&gt;
Phone: 1-877-477-2269 
Email: customer-service@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:customer-service@gopivotal.com&gt; 
Note:  Customers with Purchases prior to 4/14/2014 still need to leverage the previous support methods through EMC and VMware.  An effort to migrate legacy customers is underway and communication about timing and details will follow as timelines are finalized.
Products – What’s to Come in June
The Pivotal App Suite and Big Data Suite will be on the EMC/Pivotal price list June 9th. The Pivotal App Suite is also now available on the VMware price list. Stay tuned for an announcement on http://blog.gopivotal.com/ &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com&gt;
Spring IO GA: an easier way to use Spring, whether on PCF or standalone is available June 6. An announcement will be made on June 17, here https://spring.io/blog/ &lt;https://spring.io/blog/&gt;
RabbitMQ on Google Compute Engine: connect GCE apps to PCF apps. Announcement on the Pivotal blog on June 19. (Soft-launched in late May here &lt;https://developers.google.com/compute/docs/rabbitmq-cluster-on-compute-engine?hl=en&gt;.
Pivotal Web Server 3.0: built on the faster, more streamlined Apache HTTP Server 2.4. GA expected mid-June. Details found here &lt;http://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.4/new_features_2_4.html&gt;. 




Regards,
Greg</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
