<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.6-26-14 V2N13</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 2, No.13</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;#top&gt;







 &lt;http://gopivotal.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;
NEWSLETTER
VOL. 2, NO. 13






Thursday, June 26, 2014











IN THIS ISSUE



 - Editor Welcome: June Bugs &lt;#editor-welcome&gt;

 - Business Update: PaaS is Here – and it’s all About Cloud Foundry &lt;#business-update&gt;

 - Product Update: Spring IO 1.0 Release: Simpler, Faster Java App Development &lt;#product-update&gt;

 - Agile Update: Labs Gets Lean Startup Gurus, and More &lt;#agile-update&gt;

 - People Update: R&amp;D Has its Execution Rhythm &lt;#people-update&gt;

 - Hello My Name Is… Surinder Pal Singh Bindra &lt;#my-name-is&gt;

 - New Hires: Welcome to Pivotal! &lt;#new-pivots&gt;












 &lt;#editor-welcome&gt; 








EDITOR WELCOME
JUNE BUGS
Steve Casale &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1033819-stephencasale&gt;, Sr. Manager, Corporate Communications




There’s hardly been a mid-summer’s pause at Pivotal. It’s just as well. The company has been out in force, articulating how the intersection of data and agile development, enabled by the software workshop of PaaS, are the modern tools of next generation computing. You’ll see snapshots of how that is all coming together in all of this issue’s updates. 

 We’ve tweaked the newsletter format to make it a bit easier to navigate (hat tip to comrade Dararith in Corporate Marketing). Click to read what you want, continue on, or head back to the top. We&apos;re now looking to make it responsive to your mobile device, for an easy read anywhere. Stay tuned.
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#business-update&gt; 








BUSINESS UPDATE
PAAS IS HERE – AND IT’S ALL ABOUT CLOUD FOUNDRY
James Watters &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/920258-jameswatters&gt;, VP Product and Ecosystem for Cloud Foundry




Nowhere was it more evident that PaaS is the software workshop for an application economy (and that Cloud Foundry is it) than at the recent Cloud Foundry Summit &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/platform-as-a-service/cloud-foundry-summit-2014&gt;. The event affirmed the Cloud Foundry community’s open source core, and the power of commercial PaaS as lead by Pivotal CF.

Summit snapshots (l to r: James Watters with David Lewis and Dr. Swamy Kocherlakota from BNY Mellon; Pivotal CF powers Atos’ cloud; Pivotal’s Cornelia Davis)

 I started Day 2 with why 
PaaS is the center of a new software-centric world. And the passion and creativity that developers and customers are bringing to PaaS through Cloud Foundry and Pivotal CF are testament to this trend. Their stories included: 													 


 - Cisco’s Ken Owens extolling the virtues of running next-generation WebEx on Cloud Foundry
 - Germany’s largest publisher, Axel Springer, using Pivotal CF to remake itself as a digital publisher &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GKJ6YgIZm88&gt;
 - BNY Mellon, selecting Pivotal CF as the platform to evolve its enterprise
 - Core Logic fueling innovation through Pivotal CF &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZWkfOe1-tc&gt;
 - Monsanto building on Pivotal CF &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RJCB7OGeY9o&gt; to realize a cloud vision for data-driven agriculture
 - SAP using Cloud Foundry as the cornerstone of its platform strategy &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V-SfC1lsun0&gt; to serve 200,000 customers across 170 countries
 - Philips Digital Health leveraging Pivotal CF to ignite an agile innovation engine &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=62wTc-YS_Yw&gt;
 - NTT building auto-scaling with BOSH &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/Pivotal/tue-1430-breakoutyudaintt&gt;
 - HP unveiling its Helion Cloud based on Cloud Foundry
 - IBM growing its billion-dollar investment in BlueMix (Open Stack + Cloud Foundry cloud!)


From Pivotal, James Bayer’s Cloud Foundry roadmap and Onsi Fakhouri, who created fireworks around DIEGO &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1OkmVTFhfLY&gt;, were just a few of the many bright spots.

 Pivotal CF continues to 
spearhead a commercial PaaS &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/platform-as-a-service/press-release/06102014-pivotal-extends-lead-in-enterprise-paas-with-new-pivotal-cf-services-and-new-customers&gt; that offers developers and IT operators the 
automation, data access and ease essential for agile, application-driven businesses. We released Version 1.2 in May, and remain on track for 1.3 by the end of June. This includes portability (we now run on vCHS); add-on services 													such as Redis, MongoDB, Elastic Search; and additional networking controls.

 We’re building awareness and delivering to market all the great things we’ve developed together, and the pipeline 
and upside grows. Want to help build this powerful platform? Sign up for a Pivotal Web Services account &lt;run.pivotal.io&gt; and push at least one app to the cloud now!
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#product-update&gt; 








PRODUCT UPDATE
SPRING IO 1.0 RELEASE: SIMPLER, FASTER JAVA APP DEVELOPMENT
Al Sargent &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/914434-alsargent&gt;, Director, Product Marketing, Application Fabric




Spring IO™ 1.0 has arrived &lt;https://www.gopivotal.com/agile/press-release/06262014-pivotal-releases-spring-io-platform&gt;, making it easier than ever for the largest Java developer community to build enterprise applications. Spring IO unites dozens 														of Spring and third-party artifacts &lt;http://docs.spring.io/platform/docs/1.0.0.RELEASE/reference/htmlsingle/&gt; into 													a cohesive, versioned release – giving developers a solid 
foundation to build mobile, Big Data and web applications, as well as cloud microservices &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/mstine/microservices-cf-summit&gt;.

 Before Spring IO, developers tested foundation components on their own (a 
time-consuming task). With Spring IO, Pivotal took care of that testing, enabling developers to focus on building application functionality.

 Spring IO extends Pivotal’s core product plays. It runs on Pivotal CF commercial PaaS or Cloud Foundry and integrates with Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt; components, including Pivotal HD &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-hd&gt; and Pivotal 													GemFire. &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-gemfire&gt; The open source Spring IO is freely downloadable &lt;http://platform.spring.io/platform/&gt;, while Spring IO support comes with the purchase of Pivotal CF. Customers running Spring IO independently of Pivotal CF can purchase support via the Pivotal App Suite &lt;https://network.gopivotal.com/products/pivotal-app-suite&gt;.

 Spring IO honors the commitment to portability. It runs anywhere Java 7 or 8 does – and, in addition to Cloud Foundry or Pivotal CF, it runs on standalone Java Virtual Machines (JVMs), servlet engines like Apache Tomcat, Pivotal tc Server &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/products/pivotal-tc-server&gt; and Jetty, or Java EE 1.6 + application servers such as Oracle WebLogic, IBM WebSphere and RedHat JBoss.

 Spring IO 1.0 is another step in our journey to define an agile culture of modern app 
development.
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#agile-update&gt; 








AGILE UPDATE
LABS 
GETS LEAN STARTUP GURUS, AND MORE
Danny Burkes &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/983881-dannyburkes&gt;, Director of Pivotal Labs, San Francisco




We’re delighted to welcome Janice Fraser and Jason Fraser (from the Lean Startup consultancy, Luxr &lt;http://www.luxr.co/&gt;) to our San Francisco offices, and they have hit the ground running. Both joined Pivotal in early June, with two more Luxr specialists set to join us shortly. Since their start in 2010, Luxr has partnered with Pivotal Labs around product strategy and lean and agile methods for many startups and enterprises. Bringing Luxr’s high caliber Design and Product Management team to Pivotal Labs is a natural extension of a great partnership. Read more about this in Janice’s blog &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/news-2/our-agile-team-grows-stronger&gt;.

 Janice represented Pivotal at the recent and outstanding Pivotal Labs’ sponsored LAUNCH Beacon event &lt;http://blog.launch.co/blog/launch-beacon-wrap-up-thanks-for-coming.html&gt; in New York on June 16, which brought together more than 300 attendees from the hottest emerging companies and disrupters at the intersection of retail, payments and locations.

 We continue to help customers large and small create new experiences and ways to do business. Current projects span enterprises like Nordstrom, AT&amp;T, CoreLogic and Capital One, and start-ups and innovators such as Funding Circle, MetroMile, Perforce, and Euclid Analytics (Adam Wilson, Euclid Analytics CMO &amp; SVP of Product, gave a standout presentation at LAUNCH Beacon).

 We’re moving at the speed of the cloud (or fog in SF). See you next round!
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#people-update&gt; 








PEOPLE UPDATE
R&amp;D HAS ITS EXECUTION RHYTHM
Hugh Williams &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/980045-hughwilliams&gt;, SVP, Research &amp; Development




We’re assembling the products modern companies need to thrive in a cloud world: PaaS, application fabrics, and the products and science to master data. To build them in the right way, Rob Mee and I have spent a lot of time these past few months creating a common framework of software engineering principles, which we shared at an engineering all hands around how to “Build It Right” at Pivotal.

 With the formation of our weekly Data business review team and processes, we’re getting into the right execution rhythm. We’ve also reoriented the Data Fabric team around the key functions of quality, product management, and development. I’m pleased to welcome Suhail Ansari &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1050221-suhailansari&gt; and Jamie Buckley (who starts at the end of the month) to Pivotal to lead our Data Fabric Development and 
Data Fabric Product Management, respectively. Both come from eBay and were instrumental in the innovation and quality that helped reinvigorate the company. Additionally, the capable Randy Macblane &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/913927-randymacblane&gt; now leads our consolidated App Fabric team.

 The results are winning over customers. Our Pivotal Greenplum Database story resonates so completely with Morgan Stanley that they recently awarded us their CTO 
Award for Innovation. We won the pro-Spring battle inside of Netflix. Expedia is all-in on Pivotal GemFire to match their users to real-time hotel offers. There are racks of Pivotal HD and Pivotal GPDB at Walmart. Most exciting are the POCs (such as at John Deere) using the entire Pivotal stack – from Pivotal Labs, to Pivotal CF, to Pivotal Big Data Suite.

 I couldn’t be more excited for the team at the 2014 halfway point, and I look forward to a great second half!
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#my-name-is&gt; 








HELLO MY NAME IS…
SURINDER PAL SINGH BINDRA
Surinder Pal Singh Bindra &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1032723-surinderpalsinghbindra&gt;, Sr. Mgr. Product Development, Pivotal Real-Time Database, and Head of Pune R&amp;D Center



At Pivotal I…
Manage Pivotal’s Pune R&amp;D Center (located on the VMware campus in Pune, India). This includes managing the Pivotal GemFire, Pivotal SQLFire and Pivotal GemFire XD product lines from Pune, and working with my team to get quality releases out on time.

You can find me…
In my office of course! Or at home playing with my kids.

Currently, I am working on…
We just released Pivotal GemFire XD 1.0.1, which allows our enterprise customers to leverage the latest and greatest XD features in stand-alone mode. I’m also focused on ensuring a timely release of Pivotal GemFire 7.5, which adds lots of exciting features that allow developers to write more advanced applications.

 I’m also planning and facilitating the work for new product features, including one of the most desired features for Pivotal GemFire XD 1.1 – “non-collocated joins”. I am also in the process of setting-up a customer support organization for Pivotal GemFire, Pivotal SQLFire and Pivotal GemFire XD. The organization will be based in Pune and grow over time.

In my spare time…
I meditate and read religious material. I dabble in Android development (I have a couple of apps in the Play store). I love to mentor kids, and visit and work with underprivileged children in and around Pune.

Something you probably don’t know about me…
My two loving daughters help me hone my teaching skills at home.


Surinder Pal Singh with his daughters (and student teachers)

To me Pivotal…
Is an opportunity to work on great products enabled by a group of extremely talented people.
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;














 &lt;#new-pivots&gt; 








Welcome to Pivotal!




We’re happy you’re here! Please welcome new employees who joined Pivotal between June 12 and 23:

Sumbil Alvi, Software Engineer, Toronto
Tom 
Anderson, Software Engineer, London 
Richard Arturo, Account Manager, Americas West
Maxim Avezbakiev, Advanced Field Engineer, Global
Mahdi Azarafrooz, Software Engineer
Mary Baldwin, Product Manager, Santa Monica
Jennifer Black, Technical Writer, San Francisco
Jennifer Cruz, Customer Support Tech 2, Palo Alto
Andrew Declerk, College Intern, Palo Alto
Robert Dimsdale, Software Engineer, San Francisco
Shelby Doolittle, Software Engineer, San Francisco
Nancy Finnegan, Account Manager, Americas West
Spencer Gibb, Engineer
Daxiang Hao, College Co-op Student, Beijing
Ashley Heys, Global 
Support Services
Anirudh Jain, College Intern, Beaverton
Sufyaan Kazi, Senior Field Engineer, London
Sahil Khanna, College Intern, San Francisco
Rosemary King, Product Manager, London
Sadasivan 
Krishnamoorthy, Senior Field Engineer, Americas West
Madhura Kulkani, College Intern, Beaverton
Emery Lee, College Intern, Palo Alto
Christian Lewis, Senior Field Engineer, Americas West
David Mareiro, Principal Product Marketing Manager, Hopkinton
Tamara Moona, Product Manager, Toronto
Joe Nagy, Marketing Director, London
Anthony Oliveri, Account Manager, Americas West
Ian Ornstein, College Intern, Santa Monica
Veronica Orzechowski, Associate Marketing Program Manager, Toronto
James Osborn, ISR Product, Austin
Naomi Plasterer, Software Engineer, San Francisco
Prasad, Radhakrishnan, Senior Field Engineer, Americas West
Steven Schoenhaus, Account Manager, Americas West
Andrew Shafer, Senior Director and Software Engineer, Pittsburgh
Aakash Shah, Software Engineer, San Francisco
Anirudh Sharma, Product Manager, Toronto
Yaw Tan, Senior Data Scientist, Singapore
Nicole Wilczynski, College Intern, Palo Alto
Charles Wu, Principal Product Manager, San Francisco
Eddie Zuniga, College Intern, Palo Alto

*Corrections* - Last issue many new hires listed had incorrect title correlations. Below are the names, with their correct titles. - Editor

Janice Fraser, Senior UX Designer
Xiaochen Yuan, UX designer
Joe Grandja, Senior Solutions Architect
Nader Ziada, Senior Solutions Architect
Jason Fraser, 
Senior Product Manager
Neela Chaudhari, Senior Product Marketing Manager
Cora Iberkleid, Senior Field Engineer
Timothy Spann, Senior Field Engineer
Charles Svodboda, Senior Field Engineer
Domenic Curro, Software Engineer
Jean De Klerk, Software Engineer
Mark Hetherington, Software Engineer
Qihong Chen, Senior MTS
Giovanni Echon, Principal Risk Analyst
Christopher 
Woodstock, IT Client Support Specialist
Jay Froehling, Pivotal Sales Director
Sudha Duvvuri, Designated Support Engineer I
Wendy Kha, College Intern
Pradeepkumar Konda, College Intern
Jerry Lin, College Intern
Leonardo Neves, College Intern
Xin Qi, College Intern
Ankur Uprit, College Intern
Sina Vaziri, College Intern
Christopher Rovtar, Account 
Manager
BACK TO TOP ↑ &lt;#top&gt;


















InsidePivotal &lt;http://insidepivotal.com&gt;       SocialCast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter?&gt;






www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://gopivotal.com&gt;




 &lt;http://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/&gt;
 &lt;http://twitter.com/gopivotal&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/gopivotal&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;
 &lt;https://www.facebook.com/gopivotal&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/105320112436428794490/posts&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/gopivotal&gt;










© 2013-2014 Pivotal Software, Inc. All rights reserved. Priviledge &amp; Confidential.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
