<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV 8-19-2015 A/B Testing.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Cloud Foundry Has Crossed $100 Million in Annual Revenue</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of August 17, 2015
&lt;http://pivotal.io/how-far-weve-come?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;
Pivotal Cloud Foundry Has Crossed $100 Million in Annual Revenue
Pivotal has just celebrated one of the best quarters in the history of our company and we&apos;re just getting started.
 
 On Tuesday, we announced that Rob Mee will become our new CEO. Rob Mee has been credited for shaping the software development cultures of some of Silicon Valley’s most influential and valuable brands. He&apos;s an exceptional leader and technologist, passionate about our mission and committed to our principles and values.
 
 Paul Maritz will remain on Pivotal&apos;s board of directors as Executive Chairman and will continue to be actively involved with Pivotal and our customers.
LEARN MORE &lt;http://pivotal.io/how-far-weve-come?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;
We Transform How The World Builds Software
August 18, 2015
When we started Pivotal Labs back in 1989, our goal was to give developers the tools to build software more collaboratively and efficiently. We believed that software was the way to make an impact, that it could truly change industries, and the world. We still do, now more than ever.



Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news/we-transform-how-the-world-builds-software?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;
Point of View
How Far We&apos;ve Come
August 18, 2015
Over the past 35 years, I have been fortunate enough to have had a ringside seat at three major transitions in the computer industry: first the birth of the Software &amp; PC era, then the Internet and Web era, and now the Cloud era at Pivotal. During this time I have had the privilege of working with incredibly smart and interesting people, and have seen the enormous impact that technology can have on the world. The latest wave of change that is blowing through the world is perhaps that most interesting of all, as the world is moving beyond the automation of what was previously done with pen and paper, giving birth to new capabilities and ways of relating to people that we have not seen before—not just quantitatively but qualitatively too.



Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news/how-far-weve-come?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;
Podcasts
All About The Pivotal Cloud Foundry 1.5 Release
August 19, 2015
The latest and greatest is Pivotal Cloud Foundry release is out! With beta support for things like Diego and Windows 2012, as well as new security features including single sign on, app manager and S3 file store support, there are lots of goodies packed in it. In this episode, host Simon Elisha gives a quick run through of some of the highlights.
 
Listen Now &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-perspectives/features/all-about-the-pivotal-cloud-foundry-1-5-release?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-19-2015&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
