<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Mark Thomas - Everything Apache Tomcat</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>OSS_Event_Meetups.SF Pivotal Labs Office</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Meetup: Everything Apache Tomcat with Mark Thomas - Tuesday, September 24th</subject>
    <textOnly>Everything Apache Tomcat with Mark Thomas
Join us Tuesday evening (September 24, 2013), at the San Francisco Pivotal Labs &lt;https://maps.google.com/maps?q=875+Howard+Street+5th+Floor,+San+Francisco,+CA&gt; office for a meetup with Mark Thomas! (http://www.meetup.com/Pivotal-Open-Source-Hub/events/136113432/)

 - 875 Howard Street 5th Floor, San Francisco, CA
 - Tuesday, September 24, 2013

 - Schedule: 
 - 5:30-6:30pm Networking drinks and pizza
 - 6:30-8:00pm Introductions and talk by speaker
 - 8:00-8:30pm Continued discussion

It is a busy time in the Tomcat community. Release candidates for Tomcat 8 have started to appear (the second one should be out by the time of this meet-up), JSR-356 WebSocket support has been back-ported to Tomcat 7 and a much needed overhaul of the website and documentation is underway.

The first half of the meet-up will look at the changes in Tomcat 8, covering new and changed features in both the specifications and Tomcat specific features. This will include the new support for JSR 356 which is also now part of Tomcat 7. The topics for the second half will be decided by the audience. I&apos;ll have material with me to cover security, memory leaks, clustering, reverse proxies and performance. There should be time to cover any two of these. If there is a lot of interest in some other Tomcat related topic then I&apos;m happy to cover that as well. The evening will wrap up with an opportunity to ask any remaining questions.

Bio: Mark Thomas

I have been an Apache Tomcat committer since November 2003. I initially worked on Tomcat in my free time but since August 2008 I have been employed by SpringSource (now part of Pivotal) to work on Apache Tomcat. I spend most of my time working on Tomcat but I also work on tc Server, Pivotal&apos;s Servlet, JSP, EL and WebSocket container based on Apache Tomcat. Additionally, I lead the Pivotal Security Team.

I am the Apache Tomcat 7 release manager where I try to release a new version every month or so. I am currently focused on Tomcat 8 development which will support the new versions of the Servlet, JSP and EL specifications as well as adding JSR356 (WebSocket) support. I am a member of the JCP expert groups for JSR 340, JSR 341 and JSR 356.

Elsewhere as the ASF, I am a member of the ASF security team, a member of the ASF infrastructure team and I am also on the Commons PMC where I focus on Commons Pool and DBCP.

I am a member of the ASF.

See you at the event.

To manage preferences for your Spring related communications, please go to http://play.gopivotal.com/OSSSubscriptions.html. To unsubscribe from all communications, please go to http://play.gopivotal.com/UnsubscribePage.html.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
