<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Q4 Wins Announcement 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Q4: Big Wins, and New Assets for Sales</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

Congrats to all on what was a massive quarter for Pivotal across all lines of business. We had some groundbreaking deals this quarter including huge wins like Corelogic, Samsung, and Allstate--Deals that are remarkable not just for the large dollar values won, but also because of the degree of investment across our technology and methodology portfolio. Customers agree that our combination of software and skills expertise make us unique partners for organizations that seek to evolve and embrace the challenges posed by a new software-driven economy.

We have continued analysis of top Pivotal CF and Big Data Suite wins &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/assets/external-slides&gt; this quarter. As always you can find anonymized, scripted business case slides you can use to share these stories, as well as detailed wins analysis. New this quarter, we are now making available the actual interviews with the reps who have won these deals. These are easily downloadable in mp4 format for your use on the road.

The @RingTheBell program was widely embraced on socialcast in Q4 and will continue throughout this fiscal year. Tune in on the @RingTheBell &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89227-ringthebell&gt; channel to stay apprised of significant deals as they happen.

Additional podcasts &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/assets/field-podcast-1&gt; are also available to brush up on your storytelling ability. Find out more about customers like Expedia, Southwest, and Vodafone, told straight from the reps themselves.

Finally, thanks for your continued support of our reference program. Joe Hold is the top rep this quarter with four completed reference requests including the brand new Corelogic video &lt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PWzVwytrX4&gt;, Case Study &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/sites/default/files/CoreLogic_Case%20Study_111714.pdf&gt;, as well as the Corelogic press release we saw in December. Find out more in the Q4 Reference Performance Report &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/customer-marketing-and-programs/references/reference-performance-report---q4&gt;.

If you have questions or 
comments on any of the above, please let Sophia Tseng know.

Make it happen.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
