<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.2-12-15 V3N4</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 3, No.3</subject>
    <textOnly>VOL. 3, NO. 3
Thursday, February 12, 2015
Editor Welcome: What the Emperor Saw &lt;#editor-welcome&gt;
Business Update: Pivotal and Capgemini Navigate the Data Lake  &lt;#business-update&gt;
Product Update: Engineering Gets Ready for the New Data &lt;#product-update&gt;
Agile Update: Chicago – Growing our New Pivotal Labs Office &lt;#agile-update&gt;
People Update: Your Concierge – More than Greets the Eye &lt;#people-update&gt;
My Name Is... Amy Benoit &lt;#my-name-is&gt;
New Hires: Welcome to Pivotal! &lt;#new-pivots&gt;
EDITOR WELCOME
 What the Emperor Saw
 Steve Casale &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1033819-stephencasale&gt;, Sr. Manager, Corporate Communications
In a scene from the “Last Emperor”, child-emperor Puyi (the last of China’s Manchu rulers) opens the gates from the Forbidden City and glimpses for the first time the 20th century unfolding beyond his walls – witnessing a future no longer shaped by the imperial hand, 
but one that was literally marching by him.
 
 It’s a stretch, but it reminded of the setting for next week, when Pivotal lays out its data vision, and sets the tone at the 2015 Sales Kick-off &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/events/sales-kick-off-2015&gt;. There are no warlords at the gates of change, but Pivotal is coming full circle on its unique vision for the future.
 
 More on that next time. For now, enjoy this interlude with two features on how modern data management, and preparing for our data future is already underway, while Labs’ Austin Vance recounts an opening for our new office in Chicago that was all around grand.
 
 Finally, the GSS-hosted global Hackathon winners are in &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal-support/home/fun/hackathon&gt;!  Watch the video, and vote for the People’s choice &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/forms/d/1Nw1FTKCrP3FpOdgmpyLx-UWCkJ5BNDZEggqxiMjZ8_E/viewform?c=0&amp;w=1&gt;. And don’t forget to encourage your customers to attend Pivotal’s New Approach to Big Data &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/inside-pivotal/events/pivotal-strategy-update?pli=1&gt; event in San Francisco, 
next Tuesday.
BUSINESS UPDATE
 Pivotal and Capgemini Navigate the Data Lake 
 Jocelyn Parker &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/927788-jocelynparker&gt;, Global Alliance Manager, Capgemini
Since the launch of our strategic partnership with global IT consultancy Capgemini at the tail-end of 2013 &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/capgemini-and-pivotal-announce-a-strategic-partnership-to-deliver-next-generation-integrated-big-data-and-analytics-solutions&gt;, we’ve been moving in lock-step with Capgemini around Pivotal’s vision to 
“store everything, analyze anything and build the right thing” through the Pivotal Business Data Lake &lt;http://www.capgemini.com/big-data-analytics/pivotal/&gt;.
 
 Throughout 2014, Capgemini used the 
Business Data Lake to surface insights at the point of action using Pivotal technologies.One outcome is a $17M pipeline of Pivotal software for 2015.
 
 We made progress on many fronts:


 - Booking $3.4M in Capgemini-influenced revenue
 - Training 150+ Capgemini resources on components of the Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt; (BDS)
 - Creating Capgemini field team with dedicated Pivotal revenue goals

 - Joint marketing and enablement materials &lt;https://marcoms.capgemini.com/bam/pages/search.php?search=%21collection3928&amp;k=eed031a5e9&gt; for the Business Data Lake, and the “Anomalous Behavior Detection” use 
case



Our partnership will only grow in 2015. Capgemini has formed a global practice, called “Capgemini Insights and Data”, with Pivotal as a core component of that strategy. Another big Capgemini initiative, called “Insights Platform”, is powered by Pivotal technology and will be offered as a managed service. This end-to-end solution serves up Pivotal BDS as a hosted service, on- or off- premise, giving customers more choice for a modern data analytics solution.
 
 Other efforts will include building expertise and resources around Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/pivotal-cloud-foundry&gt; and Pivotal BDS – with a go-to-market focus in Oil &amp; Gas, Financial Services, Manufacturing and the Auto industry &lt;http://www.capgemini.com/news/capgemini-launches-new-automotive-insights-laboratory-to-help-car-manufacturers-leverage-big&gt; – where Capgemini can provide hosted POC and production environments.
 
 We’ve also got more to announce this 
month, with Capgemini and data integration specialists Informatica &lt;http://www.informatica.com/&gt;. Working with Informatica provides Capgemini proven tools for data management to ensure clients’ Business Data Lakes don&apos;t turn into data swamps.
 
 We’re mapping out new territory in business transformation with Capgemini, and we look forward to continuing the journey this 
year!
PRODUCT UPDATE
 Engineering Gets Ready for the New Data 
 Elisabeth Hendrickson &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/966801-elisabethhendrickson&gt;, Engineering Director
You know what I love about Pivotal&apos;s business model? All three major components of our business are mutually supportive. Pivotal Labs &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/&gt; writes apps. Pivotal Cloud Foundry &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/pivotal-cloud-foundry&gt; hosts apps. And real apps need data.
 
 Our Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt; (BDS) is – please forgive the pun – pivotal to what we do. So it shouldn’t be surprising that we’re investing heavily in data. Much of that investment will enable us to more consistently build and ship more reliable software, as we bring the engineering process in line with the way we build Pivotal Cloud Foundry.
 
 Until recently, data engineering teams used a variety of management tools – Trac, Jira, 
Rally and our own Pivotal Tracker &lt;http://www.pivotaltracker.com/?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=Google_Search_Brand_US&amp;utm_term=pivotal%20tracker&amp;utm_placement=&amp;utm_content=ad12_homepage&amp;utm_device=c&amp;gclid=CJD2vt7018MCFUeEfgod8zoAig&gt;. We’re now standardizing on Pivotal Tracker, the result of which will be greater visibility and easier team coordination. Data teams have also used a variety of source control and Continuous Integration (CI) tools: Perforce, Stash, Bamboo, Jenkins, Subversion, Pulse, GitHub and Cruise Control, oh my! Going forward, we&apos;ll be moving code to GitHub and settling on a common approach to CI to make delivery faster and 
easier.
 
 The engineering teams have already started improving test suites, ensuring that they run predictably with far less time-consuming manual interventions. In 2015, we&apos;ll tighten feedback loops so software releases become routine matters.
 
 However, this year won&apos;t just be about engineering process. One theme you&apos;ll see in every roadmap at Sales Kick-Off is how data continues its journey to the cloud. For example, the Pivotal GemFire Cloud Foundry Service team in Beaverton, Oregon is actively working on enabling the Pivotal GemFire Cloud Foundry service to do more than session management. Creating or extending our other data products as services on Pivotal Cloud Foundry is close behind.
 
 In short, 2015 is shaping up to be the year we truly achieve the original vision of Pivotal – as a unified company with a compelling set of products that work and make sense 
together. There is much more to come. I&apos;m excited for data this year and I hope you are too!
AGILE UPDATE
 Chicago – Growing our New Pivotal Labs Office
 Austin Vance &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1032797-austinvance&gt;, Chicago Office Director, Pivotal Labs
On Thursday January 29th, Pivotal Chicago hosted more than 140 customers, partners, and employees to celebrate the official opening of their new office space. Meg Graham from the Chicago Tribune dropped by just before the festivities to do a photo feature &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-opens-chicago-office-reception-open-now-hiring&gt;.
 
 We marked the 
occasion by announcing that all 1871  &lt;http://www.1871.com/&gt;(a co-working/innovation space) members will receive free access to Pivotal Tracker &lt;http://www.pivotaltracker.com/&gt;. A dozen Pivots, a handful Field Engineers, and Sales Managers have helped lay the foundation for Chicago. We are currently working with local companies including United Airlines, Cars.com, Allstate, Discover Financial Services and Lettuce Entertain You. We’re happy to help each grow their agile practice, and also get a taste of deploying to Pivotal Cloud Foundry.
 
 We’re excited to see so much buzz in the community. By hosting meetups with Women 2.0 &lt;http://women2.com/about/&gt;, Startup Grind &lt;http://startupgrind.com/chicago/&gt; and Chicago Java Users Group &lt;http://www.meetup.com/ChicagoJUG/&gt;, we have entered an emerging market with excellent traction.
 
 Finally, a special thanks to those who helped make this past year such a great one: Mike Barinek &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/958294-michaelbarinek&gt;, Edward Hieatt &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/949519-edwardhieatt&gt;, Emma Logue &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1046273-emmalogue&gt;, Veronica Orzechowski &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1060652-veronicaorzechowski&gt;, MK Meador and Jahnavi Stenflo &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1012834-jahnavistenflo&gt;, as well as all of the Chicago Pivots and Field reps. You’ve been amazing and I can’t tell you how happy I am with all the work we did this year.
 
 
 Opening buzz, and (l to r) Edward Hieatt, Mike Barinek, Howard Tullman (1871 CEO), and Austin Vance
 
 I’m excited to see where the rest of 2015 takes us. Here’s to an amazing year ahead!
 
 Coverage of the Chicago opening
 Chicago Tribune Photo Feature &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-opens-chicago-office-reception-open-now-hiring&gt;
 
Howard Tullman - CEO of 1871 blog &lt;http://tullman.blogspot.ca/2015/01/1871-ceo-howard-tullman-and-pivotal_30.html&gt;
 Tech Cocktail Article &lt;http://tech.co/pivotal-opens-office-chicagos-merch-mart-2015-01?utm_content=buffer446e4&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=facebook.com&amp;utm_campaign=buffer&gt;
PEOPLE UPDATE
 Your Concierge – More than Greets the Eye
 Michael McGinley &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1000878-michaelmcginley&gt;, Chief Happiness Officer, Facilities
At 875 Howard Street in San Francisco, when you walk off the elevators onto the fifth floor, two pleasant people will meet you at the front desk. You’ll be greeted with a smile, helped with whatever you need and generally taken care of. This is probably the first time most people will interact with Sandra Stotz &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1046051-sandrastotz&gt; and me, but it’s only a small part of what we both do as concierges!
 

 In general terms, our job is to manage the facilities and culture of the Pivotal San Francisco office on a daily basis. What this really means is managing the “flow” of comings, goings and activities for a typically fast-paced San Francisco day. This includes taking care of customers who may be here for the first time, helping our (and visiting) developers, getting various executives sorted, addressing general and administrative tasks, and everything in between.
 
 On any given day, we order lunch for the office, schedule new 
client meetings, manage conference rooms, setup for after-hours events, manage desk allocations (and varying expectations), and a myriad of other tasks to make sure that folks get what they need. We know we’re doing our job well when you don’t notice any of those details behind everyday activities – and we try to have some fun along the way.
 
 
 (l to r) Mike McGinley and Sandra Stotz, front and center!
 
 If you&apos;ve never met us, please stop by the front desk. We specialize in random questions and requests. So, if you’ve ever wondered what social events people attend after work, where the printers are located, what&apos;s the best restaurant for lunch, we’re here for you. All you have to do is ask!
MY NAME IS...
 Amy Benoit
 Amy Benoit &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/users/1060662-amybenoit&gt;, Global Field Onboarding Manager
 (French pronunciation: [bənwa]). Recently married, with a last name harder to pronounce than Levine.
Manage Global Field Onboarding under Global Operations, and Field Enablement &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/83203-pivotalfieldenablement&gt; – that is arming the Field to sell well!
Quarterly, in Palo Alto, running Pivotal&apos;s Global Field New Hire Trainings. Otherwise, I work from my home office in San Diego – which beats living in my home state of Massachusetts, especially right now as they&apos;re buried in snow.
Preparing for Sales Kick-Off and working on Pivotal&apos;s Q2 Field New Hire Training. If you are a Field manager with a new hire on-boarding in the next month, please reach out.
I love to be by the ocean, hence the cross-country move. There’s something about water that draws and fascinates me.
I have a one-inch vertical jump. It’s much higher when Malcom Butler makes the biggest play of his life in the Super Bowl. Then, I can fly (Super Bowl and American football talk &lt;http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2015/02/02/malcolm-butler-super-bowl-interception-celebration-rick-ross/22757763/&gt;). GO PATRIOTS!
 
 
 Amy in beach hangout La Jolla Shores, San Diego.
Impressive! I’m surrounded by very talented, accomplished colleagues who apply software to real-world problems to help businesses perform better. Even as self-proclaimed non-techie, I can understand that.
Welcome to Pivotal!
We’re happy you’re here! Please welcome the new employees who joined Pivotal from January 27th to February 12th
 
 Adrian Smolski, Sr. Field Engineer, APJ
 Alexis Rondeau, Software Engineer, New York
 Alka Das, Sr. Business Consultant, Palo Alto
 Amy Erickson, Sr, Administrative Assistant, London
 Angus Macdonald, Sr. Director, Alliances, Palo Alto
 Colin Jackson, Software Engineer, New York
 Corby Page, Sr. Field Engineer, Americas West 
 David McClure, Software Engineer, Santa Monica, CA 
 Evan Wang, Software Engineer, Boston
 Gary Olson, Sales Account Manager, Americas West
 Ignacio Elizaga, 
Member of Technical Staff 3, Cork, Ireland
 Jordan Fallon, Software Engineer, Denver, CO
 Kelly Indrieri, Sr. Marketing Communications Manager, San Francisco
 Lee Yanco, Product Manager, New York
 Melani Matsuo, College Intern, New York
 Norman Brazee, Sales Account Manager, Americas West
 Rohit Kapil, Pivotal 
Technical Staff Manager, Palo Alto
 Sani T Chabi Yo, Sr. Field Engineer, Americas East
 Svetlin Ralchev, Software Engineer, London
 Timothy Preston, Software Engineer, New York
 Woo Rim Lee, Executive Assistant, Seoul
 Xavier Prud Homme, Account Executive, Mexico 
City</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
