<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>APJ_Event_HK_Big Data Roadshow_Q315.01 Invite email_DA List_Aug21_0825</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Event Invitation: Pivotal Big Data Roadshow Hong Kong</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;https://pivotal.io/event/big-data-forum&gt;
Join a panel of experts to get the latest perspective on how big data analytics and applications are transforming organizations across a range of industries in Hong Kong.



This event provides an opportunity for those not in IT, but those engaged in the operational side of organisations to learn about:


 - New developments in the rapidly-changing world of big data
 - Best practices
 - How to leverage the technologies for business transformation
 - Big data projects in Hong Kong and their outcomes


In the keynote, Dr Toa Charm, Vice President &amp; Chair of BI and Big Data Special Interest Group of the Hong Kong Computer Society will look at the trends in big data in Hong Kong, where the market is heading and feedback from companies in Hong Kong engaged in big data projects. The event is ideally suited for those in marketing, sales, operations, finance and other lines of business managers from both local Hong Kong and multinational organisations.






AGENDA


1:45 PM - 2:00 PM

Registration


2:00 PM - 2:40 PM

Keynote - Big Data - Hong Kong Trends Perspective


2:40 PM - 3:20 PM

Redefine the Company Pulse - Industry Perspective


3:20 PM - 3:40 PM

Afternoon Tea


3:40 PM - 4:20 PM

Big Data - Insight Perspective


4:20 PM - 5:30 PM

Big Data Technologies - Innovation Perspective





Register now for this exclusive event. The workshop is FREE; space is limited.
FRIDAY

11th September 2015
 
Sheraton Hong Kong Hotel &amp; Towers

20 Nathan Road

Kowloon
REGISTER &lt;https://pivotal.io/event/big-data-forum&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
