<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.Ed H. 12-19-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Happy Holidays!</subject>
    <textOnly>Labs team,

I’m writing to you as I travel from a visit to our 200+ Pivot Toronto office yesterday to our new Santa Monica beachfront location today to help kick off a multi-year 
engagement with a new client. Just writing that makes me realize how far we’ve come in the past few years. As we come to the end of 2014, I’d like to reflect on what we’ve accomplished and where we stand today.

For the last 15 years, each year has seen us grow, in terms of our team size and our number of office locations; each year we’ve worked with an increasingly impressive client roster, building innovative and high quality products for clients; each year we’ve shared our methods and knowledge of technology with more and more of the software 
community.

Something is different these past couple of years, though. Established companies have realized that they need to change to survive - change their technology and their software development culture to let them innovate faster, stay relevant, and compete. It’s a clear industry trend and we feel it at Labs. Clients who in the past might have appreciated our approach but who were reluctant to take the plunge are now lining up to learn how we build applications, both in terms of process and technology (particularly mobile). They want to build products with us, to learn from us, and, in many cases, end up asking us to help with a broad transformation of their organization. All that is validation of the culture and mindset we have built over the past many years, thanks to your hard work and commitment to our beliefs about what works in software. Members of the C-suite in multi-billion dollar companies buy into our vision for software development, how to build and run teams, and even how we run our organization internally, from the perspective of HR, IT, Facilities, etc. In short, they want to be like Pivotal. Our mission statement at Labs is to transform how the world builds software; never has the reality matched that goal more than today. We’re doing something meaningful and long-lasting, and it’s thanks to the work you do every day.

A critical part of the reason we get such a positive response from clients is that they also see that Pivotal has the right technology to support Labs’ methods. In particular, they recognize that Cloud Foundry is necessary if they want to adopt the Labs way. You simply need a PaaS if you’re going to expect teams to iterate quickly, keep feedback loops tight, and generally keep product teams focussed on building features rapidly. Without Cloud Foundry, Labs’ methods might look to many clients like something they want, but can’t fully have because they’re blocked by their legacy technology. In turn, Cloud Foundry is at its most useful when software teams take advantage of its capabilities and work in a true agile style. This is why in 2014 we’ve seen Labs conversations turn into Cloud Foundry conversations, and Cloud Foundry conversations turn into Labs conversations: for our larger clients, the two are very much intertwined. Throw in our Data products, and it’s clear that as Pivotal we have the whole story.

So, the demand for Labs and Pivotal’s products is growing. We now need to make good on the potential of Cloud Foundry. As you know, growing the Cloud Foundry business is our path to success as a company. I expect at this point you understand how key Labs is to Cloud Foundry’s success. If we can identify where our clients can benefit from Cloud Foundry and educate them on its value, we can help the Cloud Foundry business grow by leaps and bounds. One of the success stories of Labs in 2014 is that we rotated the business as planned towards working with more clients who are candidates for Cloud Foundry. That means that Labs is poised to help the Cloud Foundry business in 2015 in a very tangible way. 2015 is the breakout year for Cloud Foundry, and all of us at Labs need to mindful of helping the Cloud Foundry effort in our daily work. As I’ve often said, it will only be when our daily work at Labs involves Cloud Foundry more often than not that we’re really aligned with Pivotal overall.

With that as a backdrop, now 
on to some details about Labs’ performance in 2014, and our plans for 2015. You’ll hear about these points in the Labs Town Hall this week or next, but I’ll include them here with my thoughts. First, our key achievements in 2014:


 - As I mentioned, starting early in the year, we began to rotate towards clients that are potential targets for Pivotal’s products. As planned, we’ve moved the ratio of enterprise:startup business by revenue from 50:50 at the end of 2013 to 80:20 today. This was a key goal for 2014 and I’m thrilled that between the efforts of the sales and delivery teams we not only achieved it, but achieved it earlier than planned (in Q3).
 - In the second half of the year, as Cloud Foundry hit its stride, we switched focus to aligning the Labs business with the platform. Good initial progress has been made based on the premise that for the typical enterprise, Cloud Foundry is the best technology to support teams who use Labs’ methods to get the speed and efficiency they’re looking for.
 - Labs hit its bookings goals for the year and contributed more profit than planned. Given the changes, growth and multiple priorities that Labs lives every day, I’m impressed and proud of the way the team came through and achieved those results. In the end, that performance is possible due to the work we do on projects each day for our clients. Congratulations to the whole team!
 - We opened up new offices successfully in Chicago and Palo Alto.
 - The integration of the Xtreme Labs business continued throughout 2014. I’d like to thank everyone in Toronto, in particular the former leadership of Xtreme Labs, for their flexibility and enthusiasm this year.
 - For the first time we had a full sales team applied to Labs overall. There’s still work to do to get the model right, but we’ve had some great successes this year, and my thanks go to the leadership of the Labs sales team for their hard work.


Of course, not everything was successful in 2014. Here are my thoughts on what we need to work on:


 - Our brand in the startup/VC space is strong, but because we’ve focussed on our rotation towards enterprise, we’re much less front-of-mind in the community. That has led to a real fall-off in inbound startup interest. We need to rebuild mindshare in the community, and I’m in discussions with our marketing team for how to go about that in earnest next year. The good news here is that with all the revenue coming in from enterprises, we have more room to discount startups and work with more, and more strategic startups - for example, those using new technologies (wearables!), those doing work that matches our company’s values, those who are interested in using PWS, etc.
 - It’s been hard to get some of our new offices off the ground. Boston and DC haven’t taken off just yet, although we remain committed to them long-term. The need remains sales pipeline, which is starting to come together in Boston; in DC, it won’t come as a surprise that working with government takes time, but we’ll get there.
 - Growing is never easy, and we’ve asked a lot of our office leadership team this year. We’ve learned a lot and we’re making changes to relieve the load on the team going into the new year. I’d like to make special mention of our office leadership: thank you ADs, ODs and regional leadership for their hard work in 2014.



Finally, here are our high-level plans for 2015:


 - We plan to grow the Labs business modestly in 2015. When we prove out Labs’ alignment with Cloud Foundry, we may step on the gas again in terms of growth, but for 2015 we plan to give ourselves room to focus on and experiment with aligning the two businesses.
 - Our financial targets aren’t completely locked in yet, but they will be approximately $120M for bookings, representing approximately 10% growth over 2014.
 - We’ll continue to support the development of Cloud Foundry by asking Pivots at Labs to rotate onto Cloud Foundry teams. It’s proved to be a great way for Labs to not only help build the product, but also to learn more deeply about the product, and to bring client feedback to the Cloud Foundry team. We now have a Cloud Foundry team alongside the Labs team in five offices, and we’ll look to increase that number in 2015. 
 - In terms of office expansion, we’ll continue to open in new cities as a way to work with a broader array of clients. In the US we will open up in Seattle and look to establish Boston and DC. In Europe we plan on a small presence in Dublin, Ireland. We will also finally establish a Labs presence in Asia, by opening an office in Tokyo and considering other possibilities in Asia.







 - In Toronto we’re making some changes in leadership as a consequence of the important role that office, with its focus on building Mobile for Enterprise clients, will play in introducing Cloud Foundry through the Cloud Foundry Mobile Services (CFMS) product: 


 - Farhan Thawar will run the CFMS team in 2015. I’d like to thank Farhan for his role running the Toronto office to date and helping transition through the acquisition, and I’m excited to see what he can make happen next year.
 - Boris Chan will be the Office Director in Toronto in 2015. Congratulations, Boris - you’ve done a great job this year helping to operate the office and I’m thrilled you’re in the new role.
 - Rahul Singh will be the VP Engineering for Canada, taking over from Farhan. Rahul has a long history with the Toronto team and helped to run the office in the past, and he brings his engineering background to the role. Thanks, Rahul, for stepping into this important job.



 - Carl Coryell-Martin, who several years ago helped to run our Singapore office, has returned and will open our Seattle office in the new year. Welcome back Carl!
 - Alex Luttschyn will lead the Labs sales team in 2015. Alex has been a force for Labs for several years, and I’m thrilled he’s agreed to take on the role. Alex, congratulations on your new role; the Labs team is looking forward to working more with you in the New Year.
 - We will introduce a new set of Innovation Workshop services that have come out of the work that Janice and Jason Fraser have done since they joined Labs earlier this year. The workshops are designed to help our clients hone in on what products they really want to build, and what direction those products should take. This is an exciting development because we expect that it will provide the bridge we’ve been looking for between high-level interest in Labs from clients, and actually getting to the product level of conversation that we need in order to successfully engage.



I’m not usually one for lots of org charts, but given our distributed nature and our scale I thought it would be useful for you all to see the details &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0BxijxDek1Z7xdGJQcy1kdjh3RGs/view?usp=sharing&gt; of how we will be organized in 2015.

I want to thank each of you 
for your work and commitment to Pivotal. I couldn’t be more excited about the future and it’s all thanks to the effort you put in day-by-day, helping clients build software better, learning from and coaching your teammates, and pushing forward the craft of building products. I wish I could connect directly with more of you each day, but I do feel a connection to you through our Labs leadership team and the results I see in our client’s feedback. I’m more than happy to talk to anyone directly - if you’d like to discuss something with me, or ask a question, just reach out and we’ll set up a session.

Happy Holidays to you 
and your families, and I look forward to a great 2015 working with all of you.

- Edward Hieatt</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
