<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.8-3-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Building Data-Driven IoT Applications</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of August 3, 2015
&lt;http://pivotal.io/building-iot-applications?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;
Building the Data-Driven Internet of Things (IoT) Applications
Automated homes. Connected cars. Smart cities. The Internet of Things (IoT) will forever change the way businesses interact with consumers and other businesses. In 2020, 25 billion connected “things” will be in use, reports Gartner IDC predictions are even higher as analysts estimate IoT will grow from 15 billion devices in 2015 to 30 billion devices in 2020.

Sign up now to access this 4-step primer and learn all about Building Data-Driven Internet of Things (IoT) Applications.
READ MORE &lt;http://pivotal.io/building-iot-applications?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;
Podcasts
Injecting Cloud Native Think into Java with Spring Boot, a talk with Josh Long
August 05, 2015
In the first part of a two part episode on Spring Boot and Spring Cloud, Josh Long and host Coté talk about the Spring Initializr and Spring Boot. They discuss the idea of doing process-based design (a key part of cloud native application development) in Java and how Initializr and Boot help with that. Also, they discuss how Boot can help with more governance and controls, while at the same time giving developers more autonomy and speed.
 
Listen Now &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/features/injecting-cloud-native-thinking-into-java-with-spring-boot?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;
The Forklifted Application
July 31, 2015
As a preview of an upcoming book on Cloud Native Java, co-author Josh Long, who is collaborating with Kenny Bastani, shares an excerpt on building cloud native applications with Spring and Cloud Foundry. This section of the book focuses on moving existing legacy applications to run on Cloud Foundry.
 

Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/features/the-forklifted-application?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;
Big Data
Pivotal Cloud Foundry Ignites Innovation for CenturyLink
August 03, 2015
The older and larger the company, the more difficult it is to adapt to today’s software development environment. This was the experience of the eighty-five-year-old company CenturyLink, a global communications, hosting, cloud and IT services giant. As a result, the Louisiana-based company partnered with Pivotal to enable cloud innovation with Pivotal Cloud Foundry.


Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal-cloud-foundry/case-studies-2/pivotal-cloud-foundry-ignites-innovation-for-centurylink?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io?utm_source=pivotal-email&amp;utm_medium=email-link&amp;utm_campaign=pov-newsletter-8-3-15&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
