<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.4-13-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of April 13, 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of April 13, 2015
&lt;http://www.emcworld.com/registration.htm&gt;
ON MAY 4-7: 106 COUNTRIES FROM THE EMC WORLD COMMUNITY WILL GATHER IN LAS VEGAS
EMC World is the place where the full range of EMC Communities come together. Connect with us at one of our keynotes, presentations or in the exhibit hall. We will be showcasing our solutions at the intersection of cloud, big data and agile development, powering enterprise transformation in booth #349. Come see our CEO, Paul Maritz speak on Enterprise Cloud and PaaS at his keynote on Tuesday, May 5th at 10:00 AM.

Enterprise Hybrid Cloud is the path to enterprise IT transformation, enabling organizations to run workloads smoothly and securely in private clouds, in managed private clouds hosted by service providers and in public clouds. Hear why Pivotal’s Cloud Foundry is gaining momentum as the open platform of choice for PaaS and agile application development next month in Las Vegas.
REGISTER &lt;http://www.emcworld.com/registration.htm&gt;
EPISODE #23: WEDNESDAY, APRIL 8TH, &quot;YOU ARE GOING TO NEED A PLATFORM, OPERATIONAL CONCERNS OF THE THIRD PLATFORM&quot;
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us this week, Wednesday, April 8th for Episode #23 of our All Things Pivotal Podcast Series, &quot;You are Going to Need a Platform, Operational Concerns of the Third Platform&quot;.

In this podcast, Michael Coté talks with Andrew Clay Shafer about one of his works in progress, a short essay on the operational needs of a cloud platform. Covering topics from access and runtimes to services, health, and failures, the discussion and dialogue gets right into the meat of cloud operations from a technical, cultural, and workflow perspective.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/podcasts-pivotal&gt;
BECOMING A FOUNDING CONTRIBUTOR OF &quot;PROJECT&quot; GEODE
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/become-a-founding-contributor-of-project-geode&gt;
Today, Pivotal announced the creation of “Geode”, the new in-memory distributed database that will form the open source core of Pivotal GemFire. As part of this announcement, Pivotal has submitted a proposal to The Apache Software Foundation (ASF) to establish and incubate Project Geode through collaborative development. The Project Geode community will remain in a fledgeling state until such time as ASF agrees to incubate the project. This post covers more on what Project Geode is, how to get involved, and how customers have been using Pivotal GemFire to date.

 READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/news-2/become-a-founding-contributor-of-project-geode&gt;
ORGANIZING FOR DEVOPS SUCCESS
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/organizing-for-devops-success&gt;
In this post, Cote provides a short overview of the changes needed for DevOps as a lead in to an article he recently wrote for FierceDevOps. Ultimately, he believes DevOps comes down to culture, that is, after you have some good technology to use cause it is also required to get there. But, the hard part seems to be the culture change.


READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/organizing-for-devops-success&gt;
- Indiana&apos;s Big Data Conference Gets Its Sponsors Back After Protest &lt;http://recode.net/2015/04/06/indianas-big-data-conference-gets-its-sponsors-back-after-protest/&gt;
 - The Six Burning Questions for Firms Looking to Make Money from Big Data &lt;http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/technology-topics/11511060/The-six-burning-questions-for-firms-looking-to-make-money-from-big-data.html&gt;
 - Yes, You Can Use Big Data to Drive Customer Loyalty. And Here&apos;s How to Do It &lt;http://www.computing.co.uk/ctg/news/2402725/yes-you-can-use-big-data-to-drive-customer-loyalty-and-here-s-how-to-do-it&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
