<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.4-3-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 2, No.7</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 2, No. 7

EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products

Learning Something New Everyday

 Happy Birthday Pivotal! On April 1, in Palo Alto, I was inspired by Paul Maritz’s talk, titled “Yes 
Virginia, there was life before Pivotal.” I love Pivotal’s culture of learning; if you’re in a Pivotal office on a Tuesday at lunchtime, look around to see if there’s a Tech Talk underway.


 In this edition of the biweekly Pivotal Newsletter, we learn that Pivotal Data Labs is open for business in the Business Update, we are educated about the benefits 
of Pivotal Cloud Foundry in the Products Update, discover that we have a huge presence in Canada in the Agile Update and are brought up to speed on how an engineering team can move to EMC (and still be very much a part of Pivotal) in the People Update.

 To close, big congrats to 
everyone involved in the launch of the Pivotal Big Data Suite &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal-data-services/2014-data-services&gt; this week! To learn more about this fundamental shift in how we 
do business, check out our website &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt; for a link to a scheduled webinar and cool ROI/Value tool. There’s also a press release &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/press-release/pivotal-changes-the-economics-of-big-data-forever-with-new-pivotal-big-data-suite-offering&gt;, blog &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/pivotal/products/pivotals-new-big-data-suite-redefines-the-economics-of-big-data-including-unlimited-hadoop-to-enterprises&gt;, data sheet &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/sites/default/files/Pivotal-Big-Data-Suite-DS.pdf&gt; and articles in Datacenter Dynamics &lt;http://www.datacenterdynamics.com/focus/archive/2014/04/pivotal-offers-all-flavors-database-one-subscription-service&gt;, Forbes &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/benkepes/2014/04/02/pivotal-launches-its-big-data-suite-the-operating-system-for-the-cloud/&gt;, GigaOM &lt;http://gigaom.com/2014/04/02/pivotal-hopes-its-new-big-data-pricing-makes-it-a-real-platform/&gt;, InfoWorld &lt;http://www.infoworld.com/t/hadoop/hortonworks-and-pivotal-vie-hadoop-dominance-239607&gt;, New York Times &lt;http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2014/04/02/pivotal-offers-a-big-data-bundle/?_php=true&amp;_type=blogs&amp;_r=0&gt;, The Register &lt;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2014/04/02/pivotal_pricing_change/&gt;, SiliconANGLE &lt;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2014/04/02/pivotal-gears-up-for-multi-front-war-with-big-data-suite/&gt;, 
and ZDNet &lt;http://www.zdnet.com/pivotal-big-data-suite-released-7000027948/&gt;!

“Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn.”—Benjamin Franklin

BUSINESS UPDATE
Annika Jimenez
 Co-Head, Pivotal Data Labs

Pivotal Data Labs: Open for Business!

 If you’ve been tracking the changes to Pivotal’s services strategy, you should have heard about 
the creation of Pivotal Data Labs (PDL), co-led by Mark Dunlap and myself. We gave the Field a preview at WWSKO &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B8gq5KRcTGfWcTZldXRicTRHYlk/edit&gt;. PDL is Pivotal’s differentiated, and highly opinionated, data-centric service delivery organization. We drive customer adoption of the full spectrum of Pivotal’s Data Fabric technologies. Additionally, we enable customer, partner and team success with a focus on documenting best practices and building shareable tools.

 PDL is the Data Fabric corollary to Pivotal Labs’ Application focus. We have brought together Data Science and our best Data Engineers/Architects to create this best-in-class team. When you think of PDL, consider some of our 2013 wins: Kaiser, Fidelity, Visa, DTCC, IRS and more.

 Pivotal Data Labs partners closely with the Customer Success Organization (CSO) as the delivery arm for expert services on the Pivotal Data Fabric technologies. For accounts aligned with the Pivotal vision, we deliver via these packages: 


 - Onboarding – Installs and validates a PDL-certified Pivotal data platform, and enables the people operating it 
 - Solutions Assurance – Informs the architecture and assists in deployment of a partner-led solutions deployment, driving towards a PDL-certified deployment 
 - Data Science Lab Primer, 100, 600 and 1200 – Deepens the customer’s analytic capabilities across all sectors (focused on building predictive models that are deployable on the Pivotal stack) 
 - Data Lab – Provides the opportunity for deep extended partnering to build the data-driven platform, models and applications that will move the needle for our most strategic customers 


In 2014, PDL is focused on building out a profitable and efficient expert data services team. To become differentiated and highly opinionated, we will be investing in building tools, documenting best practices and sourcing the enablement content for partners to magnify our market reach. Additionally, we will be building the bridge between our best-in-class Data services, and Pivotal Labs’ best-in-class Application Development services. This team is the best in the industry and we are open for business to drive Pivotal customer success!

PRODUCT UPDATE
James Watters
 Head of Product, Cloud Foundry

Pivotal CF In One Slide

 When I look back on Q1, I couldn’t be more proud of all we accomplished. In three months, we: 


 - Released Pivotal CF 1.1 &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/pivotal-cf-1-1-advances-enterprise-paas-with-new-capabilities-2&gt;.

 - Announced our Cloud Foundry Foundation &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/press-center/02242014-cloud-foundry-foundation&gt;, with ActiveState, CenturyLink, EMC, HP, IBM, Rackspace, SAP and VMware all joining as sponsors (and 
interest is growing).
 - Closed the largest deal in Pivotal history! Special thanks to Andrew Ettinger, Ian Andrews, Carlos Castro and many others for helping with this eight-figure win.


We also had fun at WWSKO &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/sales-kick-off-2014&gt; with a session on Enterprise PaaS, GTM and Sales Plays &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B8gq5KRcTGfWNFdMMG1HNHVzcmc/edit&gt;. A highlight for me was sharing the stage with Hugh Williams to demo what’s possible when we work together. Of course, I couldn’t resist pulling Andrew Ettinger up on the stage as well.


Pivotal CF In One 
Slide
 Based on great customer and POC feedback, there are four major benefits of Pivotal CF: 


 - Easy to learn, industry standard application management CLI/API. 
 - Operational benefits built into every application on the platform.
 - Data services native to the platform – available from Pivotal, the ecosystem or customer packaging. 
 - Cross-cloud portability of the entire platform to any major IaaS.


 We will be publishing a more detailed blog &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/&gt; on this topic soon.


AGILE UPDATE
Farhan Thawar
 VP Engineering, Canada, Pivotal Labs Toronto

Together Under One Roof in Toronto

 On February 17th, the Toronto team moved a few blocks down the street to a central downtown location, close to 
transit and other amenities. True to the Pivotal way, we have a large (45,000 square foot) open space spread across two floors, joined by an internal staircase. The space includes 33 meeting rooms and phone booths, a games area, 1/3 standing desks, 317 benches and a snack selection to rival even San Francisco!

 With 360-degree views of the city and Lake Ontario, everyone is very pleased with the bigger, brighter space – a great place to 
work on our ongoing projects with companies like Bitstrips, BellTV, CIBC, Facebook, and Viacom.

 We are already 70% full with over 300 people, including the Pivotal Field team. A large lounge and games area is still under construction. When complete, we look forward to hosting events, meetups and other outreach activities.

 For those who don&apos;t know, the old office was four floors, plus another office a short walk away, and approximately half the size. It’s great to have everyone together under one roof. I&apos;d like to personally thank all who helped make this happen – from Facilities to IT to the various other groups who provided feedback, helped pack and made the move relatively painless.

 Here are a few pictures of the new office. Please feel free to visit!

PEOPLE UPDATE
Zehava Vardy
 Director of Pivotal Platform,
 Emerging Technology Product Division, EMC

Making it Happen with Pivotal and EMC!

 I lead the engineering team responsible for building the DCA &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-dca&gt; (Data Computing Appliance), which fully integrates Pivotal software (Pivotal Greenplum Database, Pivotal Hadoop, Pivotal GemFire) with EMC hardware. Our platform software supports deployment, network connections, security, hardware, expansion and monitoring.

 The majority of our team is located in Palo Alto or Hopkinton, MA. We have 24 team members working on hardware, software, architecture and solutions, QA, program management, and product management.

 Last quarter, David Goulden, CEO of EMC Information Infrastructure (one of the businesses in the EMC Federation that also includes VMware and Pivotal) 
made an exciting announcement involving our team:

 &quot;… in the 3rd platform we believe that storage, network and compute will increasingly be deployed as converged infrastructure (CI). Most of you are aware of the phenomenal success that we have seen with VCE – our joint venture with VMware and Cisco, which we will continue to invest in and grow globally … We have decided to consolidate these EMC II CI initiatives into our Emerging Technology Product Division 
(ETPD), led by CJ Desai. As a result, Gil Shneorson (VSPEX) and Zehava Vardy (DCA, Pivotal) will join CJ’s team. This move makes it easier for us to build, articulate and execute upon a consistent and integrated CI strategy for the company, maximize the effectiveness of the resources we currently have deployed on these projects, and create a base of technology and capabilities that we can build upon moving 
forward.&quot;

 Our team’s mission is to create a compelling “Pivotal One Appliance” converged-infrastructure business, supporting: 


 - Traditional structured data storage/compute/analytics
 - Unstructured data storage/compute/analytics
 - In-memory databases
 - Virtualized environments
 - Private clouds


In the past month, the DCA team released security updates, supportability enhancements and platform integration with Pivotal HD, strengthened our Big Data capabilities for federal customers. These releases would not have been possible without the tremendous effort of the DCA team – as well as close collaboration with the Data Fabric team across the globe. Kudos to all of you for making it happen!

Currently, the team is working on: 


 - Supportability improvements to improve customer success
 - Next Generation Platform (V3) with EMC
 - Building the software appliance framework for hardware abstraction and the integration with pivotal applications
 - Security update
 - V2 features – including integration with Pivotal GemFireXD application and integration with EMC products, such Isilon and ViPR.


The DCA team is growing …
 I also would like to take this opportunity to welcome two new members of the DCA team: Naveen Zalpuri (DCA Software and John Graubner (DCA Program Manager).

 If you have questions related to platform or need to escalate anything, 
please use our team alias: platform-engineering@gopivotal.com &lt;mailto:platform-engineering@gopivotal.com&gt;.

 We are very excited about this cross-Federation opportunity and happy to be working in a startup environment. We look forward to building successful converged infrastructure technology and capabilities, with EMC and Pivotal, to truly make an impact and drive change throughout the industry!

HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Cornelia Davis
 Platform Engineer, Cloud Foundry

At Pivotal, I…
 I am in a Field-facing engineering role, going deep with customers and partners, to make sure they are successful with Cloud Foundry (and Pivotal CF), and bringing those 
experiences back into the product.

You can find me…
 Theoretically, in a home office in California, but more likely at the Pivotal office in San Francisco or at a customer site.

Currently, I’m working on…
 
I’ve recently been advising a large financial institution on their PaaS strategy. They are now joining the Cloud Foundry Foundation and we’re working a significant Pivotal CF deal. I’m engaged with SAP (a Platinum Foundation member) on integrations between HANA and CF. I am also jointly developing a strategy and integration between CF and VMware offerings such as vCAC. I am speaking quite a bit at conferences and meetups on all things Cloud Foundry and Pivotal CF.

In my spare time…
 I run, ride, swim, do yoga and watch my son run competitively (distance running). I also enjoy cooking for friends and family.

Something you probably don’t know about me…
 I use cdavisafc as my twitter handle - it stands for “cdavis, allergy free cook.”  My family has been gluten free for far longer than it’s 
been fashionable (more than 15 years).

To me, Pivotal…
 Is THE revolution to the third-generation computing platform.

WELCOME TO PIVOTAL!

Please welcome employees who have joined between 3/18 - 3/31:

Peter Alfvin, Pivotal Labs – Software Engineer, Santa Monica
Joanna Beltowska, Pivotal Labs 
– Product Manager, New York
Mark D&apos;Cunha, Pivotal Labs – Solutions Architect, Toronto
Christophe Fargette, Pivotal Labs – Software Engineer, Toronto
Aleksandr Ladyzhensky, GSS – Customer Engineering, New 
York
Mariana Lenetis, Pivotal Labs – College Intern, Santa Monica
Chunling Wang, Data Fabric QA – College Coop Student, Beijing
Todd Williams, Sales – Account Manager, Americas West
Kim Vu, 
Finance – Financial Analyst, Palo Alto

Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
