<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.1-5-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of January 5, 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of January 5, 2015
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-forrester-operationalizing-data-analytics-webinar&gt;
WEBINAR: OPERATIONALIZING DATA ANALYTICS
Join us Wednesday, January 14th at 8:30 AM PST / 4:30 PM GMT for Operationalizing Data Analytics &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-forrester-operationalizing-data-analytics-webinar&gt;.

Attend to learn about challenges Hadoop introduces, and how the right tools and platforms can help address them, shifts in the industry with regards to SQL and NoSQL systems and their implications to Big Data analytics, and applying in-memory technologies for data management systems, data analytics, transactional processing and operational databases.
REGISTER &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-forrester-operationalizing-data-analytics-webinar&gt;
EPISODE #10: WEDNESDAY, JANUARY 7TH, DISCUSSING NATURAL LANGUAGE PROCESSING AND CHURN ANALYSIS WITH MARIANN MICSINAI AND NIELS KASCH
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us this week for Episode #10 of our All Things Pivotal Podcast Series, &quot;Discussing Natural Language Processing and Churn Analysis with Mariann Micsinai and Niels Kasch&quot;.

Mariann Micsinai is a Senior Data Scientist at Pivotal. She holds a PhD in computational biology and has a varied background ranging from linguistics to economics, mathematics, and medicine.

Niels Kasch is a Senior Data Scientist at Pivotal. He holds a PhD in computer science with a heavy emphasis on artificial intelligence and machine learning, and a focus on Natural Language Processing (NLP).
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
PIVOTAL&apos;S TOP 6 PREDICTIONS FOR THE DEVELOPER IN 2015
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/pivotals-top-6-predictions-for-the-developer-in-2015&gt;
The big data and cloud platform thought leaders of Pivotal expect 2015 to be a transformative year, with companies showcasing the benefits of open source, automation and data-driven analytics as the key to real competitive advantage. Last year a significant amount of groundwork was laid to evolve developers productivity with tooling advances, and this year those liberated from legacy development models will shine by creating new futuristic apps that tie mobile and the internet of things into a data-driven, learning experience that will create unparalleled user experiences and separate themselves from the competition.
 
 READ MORE... &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/pivotals-top-6-predictions-for-the-developer-in-2015&gt;
10 AMAZING THINGS TO DO WITH A HADOOP-BASED DATA LAKE
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/10-amazing-things-to-do-with-a-hadoop-based-data-lake&gt;
In this post, Pivotal&apos;s product marketing director, Greg Chase, covers a spectrum of capabilities and scenarios surrounding a data lake based on Hadoop. From the benefits of storage to various types of ingestion to ways of processing data. Ultimately, there is a lot of value to be gained when all the pieces add up and allow companies to achieve continuous innovation at scale.
 
 READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/features/10-amazing-things-to-do-with-a-hadoop-based-data-lake&gt;
- Two keys to superior code quality: Pair programming and mentoring &lt;http://venturebeat.com/2014/12/21/with-new-dev-challenges-programming-cant-be-the-solitary-job-it-used-to-be/&gt;
 - Docker or Rocket for containers? Why not both? &lt;http://www.infoworld.com/article/2865369/open-source-software/docker-or-rocket-for-containers-why-not-both.html&gt;
 - Five Myths About Hadoop &lt;http://www.forbes.com/sites/teradata/2015/01/02/five-myths-about-hadoop/&gt;
 - User experience development is often a lot of X, but not enough U &lt;http://www.zdnet.com/article/ux/&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
