<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>APJ_Summit_Q413.Email 3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Meet Pivotal&apos;s Asia Pacific Data Science Team</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Sir/Madam}},

As Pivotal&apos;s Global Head of Data Science Services, I was in Singapore last November...then as part of Greenplum...and promised we would invest in the build-out of a strong Singapore-based team of Data Scientists for the Asia Pacific Japan region.

Well, fast-forward 9 months, and we have fulfilled that promise. The team is in place, led by Greg Whalen, the Asia Pacific Head of Data Science Services. During this time, Pivotal has emerged, and with access to exciting new cloud, data, and application technologies, the global Pivotal data science team is unlocking value from data in new and exciting ways (ways which have the potential of disrupting some industries as we know them today).

It&apos;s an exciting time! I invite you to come to the Asia Pacific Pivotal Summit on October 23 through 24 to learn about Pivotal, meet Greg and the extended APJ Data Science team, and see real world use-cases of Disruptive Data Science.

Vist our event website &lt;http://www.pivotalsummit.shobiziems.com/&gt; and learn more about how to register &lt;http://www.pivotalsummit.shobiziems.com/register.php&gt; and become part of this discussion!

 

Best Regards,

Annika Jimenez

Global Head of Pivotal Data Science Services



© Pivotal, and the Pivotal logo are registered trademarks or trademarks of GoPivotal, Inc. in the United States and other countries. All other trademarks used herein are the property of their respective owners. 
© 2013 GoPivotal, Inc. All rights reserved. Published in the USA.
Manage &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/CommercialSubscription.html&gt; your subscription preferences or unsubscribe &lt;http://play.gopivotal.com/UnsubscribePage.html&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
