<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.1-21 V2N2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 2, No.2</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 2, No. 2


EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products

Advice and Appreciation
 
Have you read Paul’s Org Announcement &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDo3NjkzZjFkZWU3YWNkYzUx&gt; yet? New year, expanded team, different priorities, more challenges. 2014 will be awesome!
 
 With a fresh new year in front of us, this edition of the biweekly Pivotal Newsletter is sprinkled with advice from some of our top leaders. Paul reminds us of the privilege we have; Scott Yara comments on commitment, accountability, and humility; Bill highlights the importance of balance; and Scott Aronson describes getting it done, embracing change, enjoying the challenge, and appreciating one another.
 
 I have to give a 
special call-out to the “Hello, my name is…” section this week. When it comes to getting stuff done, doing the right thing, and true appreciation, Jason Hurst leads brilliantly by example.
 
 “Appreciation is a wonderful thing: It makes what is excellent in others belong to us as well.”—Voltaire


BUSINESS UPDATE
Paul Maritz
 CEO

Privilege
 
 As we move into 2014, I want to share a letter to the editor that I read recently in the Financial Times: 

“Sir, I applaud Alain de Botton for his article, The case for putting philosophers into company boardrooms &lt;http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/0/a688be46-714d-11e3-8f92-00144feabdc0.html&gt; (January 2). As ‘corporate philosopher in residence’ at the Cass Business School in London, I am pleased to confirm that many business leaders already value the disruptive stimulus of asking philosophical questions as simple as: ‘Why does your business exist?’ Once we get beyond the 
myopic answer ‘to make money’, a rich and deep pattern of critical thinking enables them to see the myriad opportunities available to make the world a little better for the millions of people who enjoy the benefit of their goods and services. Yes, you can make lots of money by screwing other people. But to think of work as a benefit and as a legacy for humanity is to elevate it to a nobility and morality of purpose that will do more for our civilization than any amount of mindless bureaucracy or totalitarian regulation.”
 
–Roger Steare, 
Corporate Philosopher in Residence, Cass Business School, London, UK

We have a lot to do this year, as my recent company memo &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt; laid out. But I personally appreciated the above reminder that we have the privilege of working on something important that can affect how the world operates and make it a little better. I would urge us all to keep this in mind as we deal both with each other, and with our custometracrs and partners.
 
 Looking forward to working with all of you in 2014.
 
 Paul


PRODUCT UPDATE
Scott Yara
 President and Head of Products

Commitment, Accountability, and Humility
 
 Before we get too far into 2014, I would just like to thank our entire team again for 2013. What this company of ours has managed to accomplish in only 12 months time is remarkable. Though we obviously still have much to do, and there are certainly a great number things that we could or should have done better, I’m personally proud of our progress-to-date and the future that lies ahead for Pivotal.
 
 With that being said, I wanted to share three simple 
thoughts that are top of mind for me, and that I consider critical to our success in 2014.
 
 1. We must &quot;walk the walk&quot;:
 We have put forth a very bold vision for the industry around re-imagining Enterprise PaaS and Pivotal One, which is resonating in the market. It’s been affirming to see firsthand from customers and partners over the past year, the genuine level of interest in Pivotal’s direction. 2014 is the year in which we must prove why Cloud Foundry, our Big Data platform, and our agile software development and data services, are the fundamental assets to making this a reality for the enterprise.
 
 As Paul articulated in his 2014 Agenda &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt; document, we must genuinely commit to integrating our technologies in support of Pivotal One. We must also focus our service offerings and OSS assets toward being strategic accelerators for adoption of our core platform and products. In the coming weeks, you will hear about a number of work streams (that we have kicked off over the past several months) in support of simplifying and focusing our business in 2014. I believe that the only way in which Pivotal will be able to realize its potential, is to get our ~1,600 team members acting as a single company, aligned around a common set of products and go-to-market (GTM) initiatives. &quot;One Team&quot; cannot be a corporate cliché at Pivotal; it is fundamental to our success.
 
 2. We must hold each other accountable:
 One of the areas I believe we can and must improve on in 2014 is creating an environment where there’s enough transparency and trust to hold each other more accountable for our respective functions in the company. While we spent a great deal of 2013 standing up the company and coming together as a team, this year we must encourage one another to be better. Whether myself, our executive leadership team, R&amp;D, Product Management, Marketing, Sales, Finance, Corporate Development, Labs, HR, etc. – no individual or team is perfect, beyond making mistakes, and most importantly, incapable of improving. As we start to rally the company around a few core initiatives, and double down on our Pivotal One bet in 2014, conflict and tension will be natural and healthy outgrowths of a team trying to operate at the highest levels. Ignoring the tough issues and challenges in our business is not an option, and it will require the collective effort of everyone involved to bring them to resolution.
 
 3. We must stay humble:
 One of the most rewarding parts of 2013 for me was having the opportunity to meet hundreds of super-intelligent and hardworking individuals across our company, and around the world. While the formation of Pivotal has (obviously) created a great deal of complexity, it has also created one of the most talented and diverse teams assembled in our industry. I would encourage everyone this year to get to know folks in Pivotal outside your &quot;comfort zone,&quot; as our big breakthroughs are going to come from figuring out how to combine our collective strengths in ways the industry never considered possible. Staying humble and having the ability to recognize the unique parts of any team or individual, is one of the things I most admire about Paul. His level of humility and engagement, given his accomplishments in the industry, should be a great lesson to us all. As we continue to have greater success and visibility in the industry, I hope that one of the defining traits of this company will be the level of humility and respect we have for the opportunity and good fortune we’ve been given. This is an area where I’ve seen so many companies in our industry fail and it’s usually resulted in their demise.
 
 Finally, I would like to (again) welcome Hugh Williams! I couldn’t be more thankful about his joining the team. In order to build the great company we envision, we must be relentless in our pursuit of talent, and bring in leaders that are often better at their job, than we are. I can assure you, Hugh definitely fits this bill! I’m excited to have the opportunity to work with Hugh and have the opportunity to spend more time with the other teams across our company. And while I’m deeply committed to serving in the leadership capacity Paul articulated in his executive organization note &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDo3NjkzZjFkZWU3YWNkYzUx&gt;, my personal belief is that roles often change, as the company&apos;s needs change. However, commitment to the company’s mission, accountability for the role you’re expected to play, and humility for the opportunity we’ve been given, do not.
 
 Here’s to a great 2014.
 
 - Scott

PEOPLE UPDATE
Bill Cook
 President and COO

Road Trip! Inspiration from the East.
 
 Greetings! It’s great to have the opportunity to share a few thoughts with all of you. Let me start by telling you about the Pivotal executives’ trip back east to the EMC Federation leadership session in early January. There were two things that stood out for me at this event. One, the spirit and alignment of EMC, VMware, and Pivotal – specifically, the excitement everyone had for Pivotal! The vision that Paul and Scott have been articulating around the third-generation platform shift, including the importance of Hadoop (HDFS), data lakes, security analytics, and 
PaaS was fully supported by the leadership teams across our family of companies.
 
 The second thing that stood out for me was a bit more personal. Clayton Christensen was one of our guest speakers. Clayton is a professor at Harvard and known for his book, The Innovator’s Dilemma &lt;http://www.amazon.com/The-Innovators-Dilemma-Revolutionary-Business/dp/0062060244&gt;. What struck me about his talk was that as he described what he believes to be the attributes for winning companies by way of “disruptive innovation” – he very well could have been describing Pivotal. He reinforced so much of what we believe and what we are actually doing. His most recent book, How Will You Measure Your Life? &lt;http://www.amazon.com/How-Will-Measure-Your-Life/dp/0062102419&gt;, also resonated with me personally. I have been in the industry now for over 30 years and am proud of what I have accomplished. When I look back, the best memories and validation of success for me has mainly been about working with great people to accomplish something meaningful. It takes many shapes and forms. But at the end of the day, working with great people who are smart, work hard, and thrive as a team is what energizes me. I could not be more inspired to be working side by side with the leadership team and, of course, all of you. This journey we are on together will be history changing if we commit fully and do our jobs well. We have all the necessary pieces sitting right before us. As they say, this is ours to lose. We won’t.

If you are interested, here is a link to Clayton&apos;s talk at the EMC Federation meeting.

https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B630Qe8bCp1eRmtNUGhyZEtTT00/edit
 
 I also wanted to share a bit about how I see my role and how I spend my time here at Pivotal. My role in all of this is mainly about leading and helping our team execute. Simply stated, I try to empower you all so you can be successful in doing your job and in the ways you contribute. I spend my time in three primary activities, each of them with approximately equal weighting. I don’t track it in a report on a weekly basis but it is always top of mind. I spend about a 1/3 of my time with the field (meeting with customers and partners), another 1/3 meeting with employees and recruiting (to find the best and brightest talent), and the final 1/3 supporting the functional aspects of running Pivotal. Dividing my time this way helps ensure that I’m in tune with the most important aspects of keeping Pivotal on the right track.
 
 And finally, one additional important point about me: As many of you know, my wife Tracy is my partner on this Pivotal mission. She has helped entertain customers at our home, helped with Greenplum events in the early days, and also accompanies me on many trips, so indeed she is part of the team as well, and rightfully as excited about Pivotal as I am!
 
 Here’s to 2014 and beyond and cheers to 
Pivotal.

PEOPLE UPDATE
Scott Aronson
 SVP, Worldwide Field Operations

Passing on Words of Wisdom
 
 I began my career at basically the lowest level in technology setting up distribution and selling data and fiber cable 
in Northern California. I felt it wise to “move up the stack” and that sure took a while! I landed a job at Nortel Networks and worked in both Enterprise and Service Provider sales and sales management. Pushing “boxes” was still too far down the food chain and I felt I had to get into the software game. Carl Eschenbach, now President and COO at VMware, asked me to join him at Inktomi, a company that was building out a software-based content delivery network and had developed the first search engine, as the Regional VP of Western North America. I was then recruited to join VMware in 2002 and spent the last 10+ years there before joining Pivotal. I have to borrow a line from Scott Yara: “Paul had me at ‘Pivotal’.” After meeting with the leadership team and understanding the market potential in this space, it was an easy decision and I couldn’t be happier to be along with all of you for this amazing ride.
 
 Paul shared our 2014 Agenda &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt; a couple of weeks ago. We all know that across the company, the focus will be on Pivotal One. This will impact our sales motion and how we approach our go-to-market.
 
 Being on the cutting edge of industry waves in the past, I’d like to share a few things I’ve learned from previous CEOs like John Roth at Nortel, David Peterschmidt at Inktomi (who learned from Ross 
Perot), Diane Greene in the early days at VMware and of course from Paul at VMware and now at Pivotal.
 
 Live and die by your word. If you say you’re going to get it done, then get it done. In many respects, the impressive accomplishments in 2013 created an exceedingly dynamic and challenging environment for our organization. Each of you remained focused, adapted when necessary, and executed in a way that allowed us to meet sales expectations in Q2, Q3, and Q4. A truly extraordinary accomplishment!
 
 Embrace and manage through change. As I mentioned to my team last week, if we survived and thrived in 2013 given the chaos during our formation, the changes and asks of us in 2014 will pale in comparison. We have to make changes in the Worldwide Field Operations organization to align on Paul’s 2014 Agenda &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt;; changes around DCA, Professional Services, post-sale interactions, Pivotal Labs, Strategic Alliances, and Sales Ops, just to name a few.
 
 Enjoy the challenge. I’m excited to work through our go-to-market strategy, evolve the way we engage with our customers, and figure out our operationalization and delivery models.
 
 Appreciate your teams and teammates. Our people inspire me every day. I enjoy watching you succeed and fly on your own. THANK YOU for a tremendous year of sales execution in 2013! Thank you for remaining focused on execution in Q1 and beyond in 2014!
 
 More details will follow between now and WWSKO in early February. But, right now, I am looking forward to building an organization that will enable higher revenue performance and greater sustained growth in 2014 and beyond!
 
 Also please note, I picked up an additional strategic advisor last year in my newborn Flynn (who is now 11 weeks old), so 
expect strategies to change - he is opinionated.
 
 As a final thought, I’d like to leave you with a quote from an inspiring man, “No matter what business you’re in, you can’t run in place or someone will pass you by.” – Jim Valvano &lt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jim_Valvano&gt; &lt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jim_Valvano&gt;
 
 So, let’s get out there and make it happen!

HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Jason Hurst
 Chief of Staff

At Pivotal, I…
 strive to pitch in and move things forward in any way that I can. I’m increasingly focusing on executive staff coordination and support of key strategic work streams as we graduate many of the formation projects to subject matter experts (SMEs) and long-term owners across Pivotal.
 
 You can find me…
 bouncing 
between offices (mainly Deer Creek and Howard Street) – wherever I feel I can be most productive any given day. I live just over two miles from the Deer Creek office, so I lean toward Palo Alto when possible.
 
 Currently, I’m working on…
 our Board meeting preparations for February 4th, our efforts to enable selling directly as Pivotal in Q2, our (sometimes 
complicated) partnership with VMware, and a few other cool strategic projects. Every day remains…dynamic.
 
 In my spare time…
 I spend time with my family (just celebrated our 19th anniversary with my wife, Sara), which is often hectic with four kids (ages 5 - 13; two girls followed by two boys) and a high-energy Hungarian 
hunting dog. When I can squeeze it in, I love to run and I’m hoping to complete my tenth marathon this year.
 
 Something you probably don’t know about me…
 I started the morning of September 11, 2001 in my office on the 36th floor of WTC#7 (Salomon). I’ve started most every day since then thinking about how fortunate we really are to do what we do, where we do it!
 
 To me, Pivotal…
 is a unique collection of great people, technologies, customers, and partners – with the potential to change 
the world.
 

Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
