<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.Post Field All Hands</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Field All Hands - Pivotal Mission 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Team –
Thanks for the time and focus you dedicated to our Field Operations All Hands today.
Working to &quot;make it happen&quot; will be a reoccurring theme for us in 2014; therefore I want to briefly recap what we discussed. For those of you who did not attend the live session, the recording is posted it here &lt;https://gopivotal.webex.com/ec0701l/eventcenter/recording/recordAction.do?theAction=poprecord&amp;AT=pb&amp;isurlact=true&amp;renewticket=0&amp;recordID=8046837&amp;apiname=lsr.php&amp;rKey=2383a07ddad9747a&amp;needFilter=false&amp;format=short&amp;&amp;SP=EC&amp;rID=8046837&amp;siteurl=gopivotal&amp;actappname=ec0701l&amp;actname=%2Feventcenter%2Fframe%2Fg.do&amp;rnd=2510950082&amp;entactname=%2FnbrRecordingURL.do&amp;entappname=url0201l&gt;. I recommend listening to the full presentation.
We’re coming off an enormous 2013 – and kicking off what needs to be our breakout year, with a major focus on Pivotal One. The market requirement for what we do is gaining momentum, and so is the interest in Pivotal. Our customers, partners, and industry analysts are telling us the opportunity is huge, and it’s ours to take. IDC’s &lt;http://www.idc.com/&gt; annual  &lt;http://www.idc.com/research/Predictions14/index.jsp&gt;2014 predictions &lt;http://www.idc.com/research/Predictions14/index.jsp&gt; are by the third-generation platform, which they predict – among other things – will be heavily influenced by PaaS and Big Data.
We have a clear goal: Make Pivotal a world-class software company.
World-class software companies look and behave a certain way – and in doing so, realize the most advantageous returns.  The next phase in Pivotal’s evolution is to reflect the best in world-class attributes. These transitions in strategy, and the way we go to market with both products and services, will positively adjust our revenue mix and keep us focused on the goal we set.
If we are going to lead customers to the third-generation platform – to fully exploit Big Data, Analytics, and agile Application Development on highly automated cloud infrastructures – we have to show up as an integrated team. Last year we had silos. This year, we are working to create a new function that will break down those silos and present efficiency and a unified face to the customer. 
In 2014, Pivotal Labs will focus on clients who have potential for Pivotal One, specifically in the enterprise. We believe that platform pull through will be remarkably successful for the company. Therefore, I am asking you to double down and support Pivotal Labs in the field.  
The Pivotal alliances team will focus on ensuring our success with key go-to-market partners, growing their offerings around Pivotal. They will also help us harness the power of the Federation (EMC, VMware, Pivotal and RSA) to accelerate business in 2014. There will be a partner breakout at Kickoff that will provide more detail on how to engage. 
Finally, Sales Operations is putting the required focus around comp plans and individual goals for 2014, as well as implementing process changes to create more efficiencies in this new year.  We expect to have these plans rolled out after Kickoff.
Thanks again for a fantastic year. We are anticipating a terrific agenda of education and networking in Monterey, but in the meantime – Q1 is in play.
Make it happen.
-sa
 













Follow Us: Twitter &lt;http://www.twitter.com/gopivotal&gt; | LinkedIn &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/gopivotal&gt; | Facebook &lt;http://www.facebook.com/gopivotal&gt; | Google+ &lt;https://plus.google.com/105320112436428794490&gt;




© Pivotal - FOR INTERNAL USE ONLY - DO NOT DISTRIBUTE.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
