<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.4-15-15 Employee Referral Program</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Employee Referral Program Update!</subject>
    <textOnly>It goes without saying our success is based on recruiting and retaining people at Pivotal. It is important that we continue to attract smart, hard working and talented people to our company.

Our Employee Referral Program &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/employee-referral-program/&gt; is an important 
element of our plans to hire great people that drive our efforts to meet our ambitious goals. The referral program is designed to reward and thank you for your efforts of referring the best and brightest to join us.

I’m happy to update you on a special incentive around the Pivotal employee referral program for critical hires.

A 
“critical hire” is a job position designated which directly influences Pivotal&apos;s strategic objectives. Eligible employees who refer critical hire candidates that Pivotal hires will receive $US 6,000 (see referral website for localized amounts).


 - All Sales Representatives, Field Engineers, Senior Data Engineers, and Pivotal Cloud Foundry Practice Architects (all positions globally)
 - All Engineering and Software development roles in the Data organization in Palo Alto
 - Pivotal Labs, Software Engineer, Product Manager, and UI/UX designer roles in Chicago, New York, Palo Alto, Santa Monica, Washington DC and Seattle offices



We encourage you to leverage your networks and contacts in LinkedIn, Facebook, your alma mater, and through networking events with peers. There are simple steps &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/presentation/d/1j7P91KMnmm4syJjcuieuWAoXN82Wsew_NpU21bP4xhg/edit#slide=id.p&gt; you can take to find and refer great leads from almost any networking site.

Submitting Referrals
Employees must submit their referrals and the candidates’ resumes directly to employee-referral@pivotal.io &lt;mailto:employee-referral@pivotal.io&gt;.
To 
see a full list of open positions go to:


 - Pivotal job openings: http://pivotal.io/careers &lt;http://pivotal.io/careers&gt;
 - Pivotal Labs openings: http://pivotallabs.com/careers/ &lt;http://pivotallabs.com/careers/&gt;



To learn Learn more about our the referral program and eligibility criteria, head to the Pivotal Employee Referral Program &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/pivotal.io/employee-referral-program/&gt; site on Inside Pivotal.

Pivotal is also committed to employee career advancement through internal transfers, which benefits the company and provides broader development opportunities. Please familiarize yourself with our internal transfer guidelines &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/pivotal.io/file/d/0B-sTH6Ui5i0_WDc4N2MwcE9EeEE/edit&gt;, prior to applying for a new role.

Thanks for your support and 
making recruitment a priority every day.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
