<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>System Master_Sales_Email.SA-Town Hall Follow Up 4-23-15</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Q2 Global Field Ops All Hands</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,

Thank you for joining us at the Field All Hands today, and if you couldn’t make it, please listen to the recording &lt;https://emccorp.webex.com/emccorp/lsr.php?RCID=502579ae61f648669d8a1b4ebfdcde9c&gt;.

As EMC noted in their earnings call yesterday, the cloud is 
central to the strategy of every enterprise. Companies know they have to tackle the cloud in some way, and this puts in the enviable position to have a conversation with any company, anywhere! 

We continue to prove the value of Pivotal, with 
our best Q1 ever - no easy task in context of all the shifts and change in markets and in our business model. You continue to adapt and win, and I love that about this company, and about this team. Thank you again! 

My ask is that you absorb what we covered today so we build on the opportunity: 


 - Labs had runaway success in Q1, and the focus is on working together to leverage this and get companies on PCF from day 1.  
 - In PCF we need to convert the great momentum and pipeline to pick up our pace in Q2, and continue the good work in the field to position and seed opportunities.
 - For data, despite big changes and FUD, you impressed us in both our rotation to subscription and Q1 results. Markets are warming to our open source strategy, and we’ll work that value proposition. 
 - Stay disciplined and execute on our bookings plan, building the pipeline, and hiring to plan.  


I’m super excited for this quarter. In Tyco, to Toshiba, to Time, we see the appetite for  transformation, with a proposition no one else has, and a Federation to leverage. 

As always, do not hesitate to reach out to me personally for help or support.

Be 
bold!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
