<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Corp Comm.3-20-14 V2N6</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal Newsletter Vol. 2, No.6</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
PIVOTAL NEWSLETTER
 Vol. 2, No. 6

EDITOR WELCOME
Rhonda Baldwin
 Chief of Staff, Products

Prioritize, Make it Happen, Repeat

 How often do you review your tasks and prioritize? I have to once a week. For a large portion of our employee population, this is second nature. With so many things on our plates, it’s important to make sure that when we prioritize, we’re aligned on Paul’s 2014 Agenda &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt;. Also, our new Pivotal Corporate Deck &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0Bxf9GmGLCY3nZnljMVJreGJfbVE/edit&gt; provides a great overview of the company and our key messaging.

 This edition of the 
biweekly Pivotal Newsletter provides a snapshot of our priorities around the world. We first stop in Palo Alto to get a Business Update from Field Business Operations, next on to Palo Alto, Beaverton, and India for a Product Update on Pivotal GemFire, followed by a stop in London for our new Agile Update, and then in China for a People Update. We also get to learn a little more about one of our leaders in Israel in our “Hello, my name is…” section. Finally, we round out this edition with another new feature: Welcome to Pivotal!

 To wrap up, big congrats to all involved in launching Pivotal HD 2.0 this week! The launch was timed ahead of several events, including Paul’s talk with Om Malik yesterday at the GigaOm Structure Data &lt;http://events.gigaom.com/structuredata&gt; conference, titled &quot;Why a New Type of Data Needs a New Platform &lt;http://new.livestream.com/accounts/74987/events/2795568/videos/45577724/&gt;.&quot; Check out Nikesh Shah’s Socialcast post &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/messages/19728244&gt; for all the Pivotal HD release details – 
including Sales Collateral &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal-data-services/&gt;, Customer Facing Presentation &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B6bXEicnSkOQY0NjdHVBR1pKT0U/edit?usp=sharing&gt;, FAQ &lt;https://drive.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B6bXEicnSkOQWC0tS1ZCM1lnTlE/edit?usp=sharing%20&gt;, Webpages &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/pivotal-hd&gt;, Press Release &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/press-center/03172014-PHD-20%20&gt; and Blog &lt;http://blog.gopivotal.com/products/pivotal-hd-2-0-to-help-enterprises-to-get-more-out-of-hadoop-with-a-business-data-lake&gt;.

“The key is not to prioritize what’s on your schedule, but to schedule your priorities.”—Stephen 
Covey

BUSINESS UPDATE
Greg Stroud
 Vice President, Field Business Operations

Making it Happen in Field Business Operations!

 As we head into the new fiscal year, there’s a lot going on in Field Business Operations! Much of the activity is related to Pivotal’s core mission to become a software company, as described in Paul’s 2014 Agenda &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/viewer?a=v&amp;pid=sites&amp;srcid=Z29waXZvdGFsLmNvbXxpbnNpZGUtcGl2b3RhbHxneDoyZmQ5NTdjZjMyYjBkYjk2&gt; and was described in more detail at the WWSKO event &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/sales-kick-off-2014&gt;.

 We’ve all signed up for a company target of $322.5M and a stretch target of $185M of software, subscription and support. To do that, we all need to know the Pivotal One story, and be able to tell it through specific sales plays. It is this focus on our Big Data Suite, PaaS/Pivotal CF and our strategic services – in conjunction with Pivotal Labs, Pivotal Data Labs and Customer Success/GSS services – that will lead us into increased platform sales and improve customer satisfaction.

Subscription
 In Field Business Operations, it’s our job to align compensation and provide an operating model to support our new business strategy. With subscription, we have a fundamentally different way of conducting business. We’re seeing changes in: 


 - GTM
 - Pricing, Quoting, and Delivering
 - Customers and Use Cases
 - Sales Rep Activity
 - Systems


Operationally, handling subscriptions is not only new for us, but also for EMC and VMware. We are working closely with Todd Paoletti’s Product Marketing team to make sure we get this right for the new Data Suite &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B8gq5KRcTGfWMWJTWWxpZmRqMEU/edit&gt;. Eric Landon and his team are driving new Deal Desk processes to align to the new motions.

Services
 Pivotal understands that services are critical to customer success. In Q1 we moved some of our services team to Pivotal Services @ EMC, under Chris Birtwhistle. This will allow our company to focus on delivering world-class software, while still delivering the full breadth of services that customers expect.

 Faced with so many services and customer touchpoints, we have to ensure our customers enjoy great customer experiences; a video &lt;https://docs.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/file/d/0B8gq5KRcTGfWa09GLTh3NVUzczg/edit&gt; played at WWSKO humorously describes why we set up a new Customer Success Organization at Pivotal. Keith Salisbury has been spearheading a tremendous effort to bring everyone together and set up this organization. Our team has been working with Keith and EMC to activate the part numbers that will clarify our services and Pivotal Services @ EMC.

Systems
 Field Business Operations views Salesforce.com as the critical app for tracking and forecasting pipeline. In the past few months, we have been partnering with our GTM Teams to provide insight into specific products – which is key to setting targets in the Field, R&amp;D and Product Marketing.

 Finally, I’d like to send a special shout out to Teresa Safe, who has been working 
with Field Operations and EMC to put us in a position to launch our new Quote to Cash platform in Q2. We anticipate leveraging the synergy we’re enjoying with EMC and VMware’s platforms and augment where appropriate with our own.

 I’m very proud of the team as they continue to drive the success of Pivotal through operationally enabling a world-class sales force.


PRODUCT UPDATE
Mak Gokhale
 Senior Director of Engineering,
 Pivotal Real-Time Database

In-Memory: Making it Happen with Pivotal GemFire XD

 Our launch of rebranded Pivotal GemFire and Pivotal SQLFire kicked off 2014. Cross-cloud pricing and packaging, which debuted in February, now provides a simpler way to sell GemFire and SQLFire with single pricing model. We also launched a community edition to seed the market and allow folks to just download and use the product (no license required). With the public launch of Data Suite on April 2nd, our pricing will be further simplified.

 The Pivotal In-Memory team is making it happen by bringing the power of in-memory, real-time technology to Pivotal HD. Pivotal GemFire XD launched this week, ahead of the GigaOm Structure Data Conference in New York, and the response has been great.

 Pivotal GemFire XD is the industry’s first in-memory SQL transactional database with seamless persistence to Pivotal HD. GemFire XD allows creation of linearly scalable, high throughput, low latency applications and enables processing of real-time events with Big Data for closed loop analytics.

 The Pivotal GemFire XD release would not have been possible without the tremendous coordinated effort from 
the GemFire team in India and the US – as well as close collaboration with the Data Fabric team across the globe. Kudos to the entire team for getting it done! A shout out to Sudhir Menon for keeping the release on track and simultaneously jumping in to help the GTM effort in 2013, to Jags Ramnarayan for charting the technology vision and keeping the focus on technology adoption, to Sumedh Wale for 
tirelessly working on the SQL engine and solving tough POC/customer issues in SQLFire, to Hitesh Khamesra for excellent handling of challenging customer engagements (like AmDocs), and to the Enterprise Architect &amp; Sustenance team for keeping the “*Fire burning” while we worked on 
the release.  Many members of Pivotal’s cross-functional teams came to our aid to make it happen for the GemFire XD release. To all of those folks, thank you…we could not have done it without you!

 Pivotal GemFire scored some critical wins in 2013. Several of those were results of close collaboration between the field and engineering around the world. For example, the GemFire team in India is collaborating with the field team to make it happen for Indian Railways’ e-Ticket application. The success at China Railways and Indian Railways is simply captured in a quote from Paul Maritz, “Soon a third of mankind with depend on Gem for a ride.”

 We have put together an aggressive program to realize the vision of Pivotal Data Fabric and Pivotal One in 2014. Our approach is threefold: 


 - With Pivotal GemFire XD, establish in-memory a differentiated capability in Pivotal HD, along with tighter integration with HAWQ and Hadoop.
 - Add Pivotal GemFire XD to Pivotal CF and make it part of Pivotal One.
 - Continue to keep our leadership in the in-memory data grid, NoSQL and key-value markets with Pivotal GemFire.


Customers like GE, Fannie Mae, American Express and others have already expressed interest in Pivotal GemFire XD and want to see us succeed.

 Together, we will make it happen in 2014!

AGILE UPDATE
JB Steadman
 Director, Pivotal Labs London

Making it Happen in London, the Agile Way

 I&apos;m excited to be writing the inaugural &quot;Agile Update&quot; section of the Pivotal Newsletter. In keeping with our international theme, I&apos;d like to tell you about some of our initiatives in the London office.

 On March 5th, we hosted Pivotal&apos;s official UK launch party. The event was attended by companies such as Capital One, Barclays, TRG, Deutsche Bank, MBNL and Skills Matter. Many clients and prospects enjoyed the party, and we made key progress towards closing a Pivotal Labs deal.

 We&apos;re fully settled into our new office, helping us work more closely with Pivotal colleagues. It&apos;s been particularly helpful to be under one roof with the Pivotal sales team. We&apos;ve made good progress on some interesting accounts, and hope to soon report success on projects we sell together.

 We&apos;ve also expanded our team recently, adding Martina Schell as Senior Design Manager, John Brookmyre as Senior Sales Manager, and developers Craig Furman, Nadia 
Odunayo and Tom Brand. Some colleagues from the US have come through recently to work on client projects, providing a fun chance to learn about other offices.

 In closing, here are a few photos from the office opening party. I hope to meet all of you in person either here or at your own office. Stay agile!

PEOPLE UPDATE
Ray Feng
 Head, China R&amp;D Center

Making it Happen in China!

 When the Pivotal Initiative was announced almost a year ago, we united all of the China-based engineering and support 
groups (distributed in EMC and VMWare offices across Beijing and Shanghai) to build a single Pivotal R&amp;D team in China. Heading up our Pivotal China R&amp;D Center, I oversee the operations for various engineering and services projects. I’ve also been working with our US executives in various general and administrative (G&amp;A) functions to form our local G&amp;A team – including Admin, HR and IT.

 As the first Greenplum R&amp;D hire in China, it is amazing to see how far we’ve come! The local 
engineering leadership team sought to build a world-class R&amp;D institute for Big Data and the China R&amp;D center has successfully executed a series of strategic projects for Chorus, Cetas, Pivotal Greenplum Database, HAWQ and Pivotal HD.

 On behalf of all the engineering leaders 
here in China, I’d like to congratulate our teammates around the world and wish Pivotal a very happy birthday on April 1st! We are very excited about promoting the R&amp;D center as a thought leader in the third platform and look forward to helping the industry transition.

HELLO, MY NAME IS…
Eliran Malki
 Head, Israel R&amp;D Center and Pivotal VRP

At Pivotal, I…
 I manage the Israel R&amp;D Center, as well as Pivotal VRP – a Big Data tool &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com/big-data/data-tools&gt; built on the technology of MoreVRP, a company of which I was the founder and CEO prior to its acquisition by EMC. To strengthen Pivotal locally, I work with developers, sales, field engineering, marketing, partners and customers on a weekly basis. I also take care of operations at the R&amp;D Center and try to be as involved as possible in order to build up the local team.

You can find me…
Lately, I spend a bit more time at our new facility. It is still a work in progress, but we are eager to move in. So, my time is still divided between the new facility and the Israeli EMC Center of Excellence (COE). I travel quite a bit, too. When I’m not working I like to spend my time off-roading and sailing. 

Currently, I’m working on…
 A lot of varied and interesting projects. As the local manager, I work closely with the EMC Federation, our management, EMC’s Corporate VP of Innovation (Orna Berry) and the COE. We have smaller projects involving startups and global companies, as well as larger endeavors for customers such as Motorola, Lockheed Martin, MOD and Clalit, just to name a few. I am also involved in volunteer community projects and partnering with youth programs.

 On the Pivotal VRP front, we are pushing very hard to port to a Linux environment – delivering an amazing, unparalleled solution for the future that will provide insight into Hadoop and other offerings – all while staying on track with current development and evolution of the product in order to provide added value to the Pivotal offering. 

In my spare time…
I’m hyperactive… :) 
 I enjoy traveling, extreme sailing, off-roading, sports and I’m first and foremost a family man.

Something you probably don’t know about me…
In 
addition to learning and working as a manager for many years now, I’m a hard coding developer, a DBA and (in the past) a CPU designer and RT expert. I believe that attention to detail is critical and professionalism is a must.  As I said, I’m hyperactive, with all the challenges that brings…and a true competitor (IPSC national champion for many years). I expect a lot, but push myself equally. 

To me, Pivotal…
 Is a great adventure.

WELCOME TO PIVOTAL!

Jaclyn Anderson, Pivotal Labs - Product Designer, San Francisco
Thomas Brand, Pivotal Labs - Software Engineer, London
Michele Jear, Pivotal CF - Admin, 
San Francisco
Sowjanya Kamatam, GSS - Customer Engineering, Palo Alto
Tommy Sela Meron, Pivotal VRP - Software Engineer, Israel
Jyothi Sequeira, APJ Sales - Admin, Sydney
Jeremiah Shakelford, Marketing - 
Program Management, San Francisco
Venkata Karunakar Uppalapati, GSS - Customer Engineering, Palo Alto

Want more? Try InsidePivotal.com &lt;https://sites.google.com/a/gopivotal.com/inside-pivotal/&gt; or Socialcast: @PivotalNewsletter &lt;https://gopivotal-com.socialcast.com/groups/89753-pivotalnewsletter&gt;
 &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;
 BUILT FOR THE SPEED OF BUSINESS | www.gopivotal.com &lt;http://www.gopivotal.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
