<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.5-11-15 WITH TRAINING</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of May 11, 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of May 11, 2015
&lt;http://2015.hadoopsummit.org/san-jose/register/&gt;
Please join Pivotal June 9-11, 2015 

in San Jose, California.
Come see us at Hadoop Summit where we will be featuring Big Data Suite &lt;http://pivotal.io/big-data/pivotal-big-data-suite&gt; and participating in Open Data Platform &lt;http://opendataplatform.org/&gt; activities including meet-ups, technology sessions and member BOF’s.



Pivotal’s own Sarah Aerni, Principal Data Scientist, will present: IoT: How Data Science-Driven Software is Eating the Connected World.

Discount Expo-only Passes $499

Code: EXPOsj15h



(20% off) All Access to Hadoop Summit

Code: 15Disc20Spon 
REGISTER &lt;http://2015.hadoopsummit.org/san-jose/register/&gt;
Pivotal Perspectives - Pivotal Cloud Foundry on Amazon Web Services
May 13, 2015



 
Whilst you have always been able to deploy Cloud Foundry onto Amazon Web Services using BOSH—you needed good BOSH skills to make it happen. With version 1.4 of Pivotal Cloud Foundry, this is now all handled by the Ops Manager.

 
Subscribe &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/podcasts-pivotal&gt;
New GE Performance Whitepaper Shows Pivotal GemFire To Be Industrial Strength
May 12, 2015



 
A technical white paper recently published by GE Power &amp; Water and GE Global Research highlights the benefits of running Pivotal products for storing large amounts of data, while simultaneously taking in new data and deploying real-time analysis.

 
Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/case-studies-2/new-ge-performance-whitepaper-shows-pivotal-gemfire-to-be-industrial-strength&gt;
Pivotal HD Adds Apache Hadoop Components, Cozies Up to ODP
May 11, 2015



 
Less than 90 days after helping establish and joining the Open Data Platform initiative, Pivotal has announced the availability of Pivotal HD 3.0, now aligned with the standardized Open Data Platform (ODP) core consisting of Apache Hadoop® and Apache Ambari. 

 
Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/big-data-pivotal/products/pivotal-hd-adds-apache-hadoop-components-cozies-up-to-odp&gt;
VISIT OUR P.O.V. BLOG &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io&gt;
Pivotal People - Mark Secrist on Big Data Education, Open Source Software, and Free Training
May 13, 2015



 
Training on big data, in-memory, data science tools have never been more popular. With over 25 years of development and training in his background, Pivotal’s Mark Secrist, the first U.S. based trainer for the Spring Framework at VMware, Mark Secrist spentthe first U.S.-based Spring trainer, gives us a question and answer session about Pivotal Education. He explains why he is passionate about training, where Spring overlaps with Pivotal’s Big Data Suite, and the differences between open and closed source product training. He also explains that we are hiring in his department.

 
Read More &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/?p=12073&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
