<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>POV.10-20-14</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Pivotal P.O.V. Week of October 27, 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Week of October 27, 2014
&lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/microservices-and-paas-a-match-made-in-the-cloud&gt;
REDMONK AND PIVOTAL MICROSERVICES WEB SEMINAR
Join RedMonk analyst Donnie Berkholz, and Pivotal Cloud Architect Matt Stine for for a Webinar November 18th 10:00am PST, to learn how a microservices approach, working in concert with new cloud platforms and a DevOps culture, is the engine that drives innovation at speed.
REGISTER &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/platform-as-a-service/microservices-and-paas-a-match-made-in-the-cloud&gt;
HEADLINE IN ALL CAPS FOR UPCOMING PODCAST
&lt;http://pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
Join us Wednesday, October 29 for Episode #4 of our ongoing podcast series, All Things Pivotal, covering technology at the intersection of cloud, agile development, and big data, and what it all means for business. Every week, host Simon Elisha will share the latest news, interview Pivotal technologists, and explore how people are harnessing sophisticated data and cloud technologies to build applications that achieve extraordinary things.
SUBSCRIBE &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/podcasts&gt;
TEXT ANALYTICS AND NATURAL LANGUAGE PROCESSING IN THE ERA OF BIG DATA
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/text-analytics-and-natural-language-processing-in-the-era-of-big-data&gt;
Significant growth in the volume and variety of data is due to the accumulation of unstructured text data—in fact, up to 80% of all your data is unstructured text data &lt;http://breakthroughanalysis.com/2008/08/01/unstructured-data-and-the-80-percent-rule/&gt;. Companies collect massive amounts of documents, emails, social media, and other text-based information to get to know their customers better, offer customized services, or comply with federal regulations. However, most of this data is unused and untouched. Text analytics, through the use of natural language processing (NLP), holds the key to unlocking the business value with these fast data assets.

 

READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/data-science-pivotal/features/text-analytics-and-natural-language-processing-in-the-era-of-big-data&gt;
CLOUD FOUNDRY FOUNDATION BYLAWS AND RELATED DOCUMENTS NOW AVAILABLE TO THE PUBLIC ON CLOUDFOUNDRY.ORG &lt;http://cloudfoundry.org&gt;
&lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/cloud-foundry-foundation-bylaws-and-related-documents-now-available-to-the-public-on-cloudfoundry-org&gt;
When Paul Martiz announced that Pivotal would establish an open governance model for Cloud Foundry &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/pivotal/news-2/pivotal-moves-to-establish-open-governance-model-for-cloud-foundry&gt; back in February, it was clear that momentum was building around Cloud Foundry as the open cloud platform of choice.  Not just for Pivotal, but for the industry. Since then, momentum has skyrocketed with over 35 new members joining the Cloud Foundry Foundation as 
Gold and Silver Members. Today, we are happy to share the results of Pivotal&apos;s collaboration with these open source stalwarts. Namely, the release of the Cloud Foundry Foundation bylaws and related documents &lt;http://www.cloudfoundry.org/about/index.html#the-cloud-foundry-foundation&gt; for 
public review by the open source community.

 

READ MORE… &lt;http://blog.pivotal.io/cloud-foundry-pivotal/news-2/cloud-foundry-foundation-bylaws-and-related-documents-now-available-to-the-public-on-cloudfoundry-org&gt;
- 8 Big Trends in Big Data Analytics &lt;http://www.computerworld.com/article/2690856/8-big-trends-in-big-data-analytics.html&gt;
 - Will Cloud Foundry Be Key to Computing&apos;s History? &lt;http://www.cmswire.com/cms/information-management/will-cloud-foundry-be-key-to-computings-history-026800.php&gt;
 - Hortonworks Updates Hadoop Data Platform &lt;http://www.informationweek.com/big-data/big-data-analytics/hortonworks-updates-hadoop-data-platform/d/d-id/1316712&gt;
 - Ebola: Can Big Data Analytics Help Contain its Spread? &lt;http://www.bbc.com/news/business-29617831&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
