<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>EMC Women In Technology Event.Invitation (Current Customers)</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Exclusive invitation: Join us for Women of Impact - Transforming the Face of IT</subject>
    <textOnly>PIVOTAL PRESENTS
JOIN US FOR WOMEN OF IMPACT - TRANSFORMING THE FACE OF IT!

Hello {{lead.First Name:default=Sir/Madam}},

The EMC Federation will be hosting a Women in Technology networking event in Toronto on October 29th.  The theme of the evening is “Women of Impact – Transforming the Face of IT,” and will feature a panel discussion featuring EMC’s Chief Sustainability Officer, Kathrin Winkler.  

The goal of this event is to continue to foster and accelerate our diversity efforts and build a close relationship with the WITI organization.

You’re cordially invited to attend. Spaces are limited so register to reserve your 
spot. 

AGENDA:
4:00pm - Dinner and Networking
5:45pm - Welcome Message and EMC Federation Overview
6:00pm - Panel Leader Introduction - Cheryl McGrath
6:05pm - Panel Discussion and Q&amp;A 
7:15pm - Panel Closing
7:20pm - Networking and Drinks    

This unique evening will include a brief panel discussion from key local leaders in technology 
including Kathrin Winkler, EMC’s Chief Sustainability Officer. Our panel will discuss the following topics:   




 - Get Connected:  Expand your network of professional contacts, skills and mentors.
 - Get Empowered: Build your knowledge of leadership positions in technology and a personal path for success.
 - Get Inspired:  Meet and learn from powerful women who have succeeded and advanced in their careers.



Kindly register to reserve your spot! &lt;https://emcinformation.com/280701/SI/00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000.ashx?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRomrfCcI63Em2iQPJWpsrB0B%2FDC18kX3RUrJr6dfkz6htBZF5s8TM3DV1BFXrlU6kEISrk%3D&gt; 

If you have any queries about this email, please contact Emma Logue &lt;mailto:elogue@pivotal.io&gt; or Anisa Berisha &lt;mailto:aberisha@pivotal.io&gt;.
EVENT DETAILS
Malaparte, Bell Lightbox Building, 6th floor, Toronto
WEDNESDAY
 October 29, 2014
4 - 9 pm.
REGISTER &lt;https://emcinformation.com/280701/SI/00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000.ashx&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
