<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>SpringOne2GX 2014.Thank You for Attending SpringOne 2GX 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank you for attending SpringOne 2GX 2014 - Join us again next year in Washington, DC</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank You for Attending!
 Save the date for SpringOne 2GX 2015
See You Next Year!
September 14-17, 2015
Thank You For Attending SpringOne 2GX 2014
 
It was great to see the Spring/Groovy/Grails/Cloud Foundry communities together at one exceptional event. If you did not get your instant access code for InfoQ’s Early Access Session Recordings, please email phumphrey@pivotal.io for your code, and specify the email you used to register for the conference, or direct message @springcentral. SpringOne2GX sessions will complete publishing on Monday, Sept 22. The Groovy / Grails Sessions (2GX) will complete publishing Friday, Sept 26. Look for publicly viewable SpringOne2GX 2014 videos you can share with colleagues at http://spring.io/video &lt;http://spring.io/video&gt;, starting in just a few weeks! Slides will be published at http://www.springone2gx.com &lt;http://www.springone2gx.com&gt; and at http://www.slideshare.net/SpringCentral/ &lt;http://www.slideshare.net/SpringCentral/&gt; within the next 30 days. 

It is our goal that each session provide valuable insight and techniques relevant to your projects. Now that you have left the event with a head full of ideas and new skills; we wish you the best in your endeavors for the coming year. Subscribe to the Spring Newsletter in the footer of http://spring.io &lt;http://spring.io&gt; to stay connected, and/or follow us on Twitter @SpringCentral. 

Learn about Spring + PaaS at Pivotal’s Cloud Platform at U.S. City Near You!
 &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/cloud-platform-roadshow&gt; Join &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/cloud-platform-roadshow&gt; Pivotal technologists and learn how to build and deploy great software on a modern cloud platform. At this workshop, you’ll get hands-on experience as you test drive Pivotal’s CF platform. In just a few hours, you’ll realize the speed and ease of pushing an application on Pivotal CF, the world&apos;s leading enterprise PaaS, powered by Cloud Foundry. 

The day is set up to fit your needs and time availability. Come for the first half and learn how Spring and Pivotal CF can help you build transformative software. Stay for the second half and learn about the power of Spring, Continuous Delivery and Microservices. 

The event is free of charge, but space is limited! Click here &lt;http://www.pivotal.io/cloud-platform-roadshow&gt; for more information and to register.

Join us for SpringOne 2GX 2015
 
 We hope you will mark your calendar and join us again! SpringOne2GX 2015 will be held September 14 - 17, 2015 at the Marriott Marquis in Washington DC &lt;http://www.marriott.com/hotels/travel/wasco-marriott-marquis-washington-dc/&gt;. 

 SpringOne 2GX Photos SpringOne 2GX photos are available on Flicker. 
View SpringOne 2GX Photos &lt;https://flickr.com/photos/nofluffjuststuff/sets/72157647030884089/&gt;

NFJS, the Magazine SpringOne 2GX 2014 attendees will receive a complimentary 1-year subscription. Click the link below to read issues. We created NFJS, the Magazine to extend your NFJS experience year round. NFJS, the Magazine features articles about the latest technologies, tools, career tips, and best practices. 
 Read NFJS, the Magazine Issues  &lt;https://nofluffjuststuff.com/home/magazine_subscribe&gt;

We hope to see you at SpringOne2GX 2015! 

The Spring Team at Pivotal and Jay Zimmerman SpringOne 2GX Symposium Director</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
